<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="hu_HU.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Reset</string>
		<translation>Visszaállítás</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="159"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Reset</string>
		<translation>Visszaállítás</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="159"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>that allows you to assign keywords to module items (taxonomy) and to look up items by keyword. Enable its hooks for any module where you want to use it...</string>
		<translation>ami lehetőséget biztosít a tartalmi elemekhez kulcsszavak kapcsolására, és  keresésére ezen kulcsszavak alapján. Az lehetőség bekapcsolásához a Kulcsszavak modult hurkoljuk a kívánt modulokhoz.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="14"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>After enabling the keywords hooks for a particular module, you'll see an input box where you can fill in relevant keywords whenever you create or modify a module item.
Afterwards, when viewing an item, you can retrieve a list of other items having the same keyword(s).</string>
		<translation>Miután a kívánt modulokhoz a kulcsszavakat hurokkal hozzákapcsoltuk, új elemek felvételekor megjelennek a kulcsszavak megadására vagy kiválasztására használható mezők. Egy ilyen elem megjelenítésekor, a kulcsszavak alapján, a kapcsolódó elemek azonnal listázhatóak.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This module, now, may also restrict keywords to a predefined set of words, tipical for each hooked module.</string>
		<translation>A modul képes a kulcsszavakat egy korlátozott listából kezelni, ezek a listák a hurkolt modulonként külön is meghatározhatóak.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>In the future thi module may try to extract keywords
automatically from other fields on create/update. Contributions in that or other directions are welcome :-)</string>
		<translation>A későbbiekben ez a modul képes lehet a kulcsszavak automatikus kikeresésére a szövegből azok felvételekor vagy módosításakor. Szívesen fogadjuk az erre irányuló javítófoltokat. :-)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="24"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included blocks at this time</string>
		<translation>Nincsenek kapcsolódó blokkok.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>További információk a modulról:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="43"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
