<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Wat is het?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Help Desk is system which enables system admin support to its users though a web based interface. It allows admin to track the progress of tickets.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Hoe te gebruiken?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>From the menu, you have three choices. &quot;Overview&quot;, &quot;View Items&quot;, and &quot;Modify Configuration&quot;.</string><translation>Vanuit het menu heeft u drie keuzes. &quot;Overzicht&quot;, &quot;Bekijk Items&quot; en &quot;Wijzig Configuratie&quot;.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Overview -- Allows you to view this screen.</string><translation>Overzicht -- Hiermee krijgt u dit scherm te zien.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>View Items -- Allows you to manage any helpdesk item.</string><translation>Bekijk Items -- Hiermee kunt u elke Helpdesk item managen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modify Configuration -- Allows you to set certain configuration routines.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Important Setup Instructions!</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are currently two ways to setup the Help Desk module. The easy way which sets just about everything
up for you using a simple wizard. Then there is the hard way, which is not recommend unless you know
what you are doing.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Easy Setup</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Security Setup Wizard</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Hard Setup</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Helpdesk Techs have changed since using the security module. Techs need to be set as a default group in the security module for helpdesk tickets with Overview thru Write privileges.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Once you create a &quot;Techs&quot; group in the roles module, goto AdminMenu -&gt; Security -&gt; Modify Hook Settings</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select helpdesk - 1 and click the reload button. More options should then appear.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The security module is a Unix style privilege system for xaraya based items, except that security has different levels and more of them. In security you have three types of &quot;groups&quot;, User(just you), Groups(roles based group), and World(everyone).</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>When an item is created, every group the user is in a set of privileges is created unless one of the groups is in the modules exclude list. It is recommended that you add the &quot;Users&quot; group to this list.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>It is recommended to have the &quot;Default Group Level&quot; set to 60 for the helpdesk module, but you may decide to use a different value once you get the hang how that works.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>In the Security field set give the &quot;User&quot; column Overview thru Manage access by checking the check boxes. Then Add your helpdesk techs group and give them Overview thru Write. Then give World nothing at all. This will make it so that User can and techs can see and write to the ticket and no one else can see it.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Security module does make the Help Desk a little more complicated to get setup at first, but it expands the capabilities of the helpdesk. It allows you to define who should be able to see tickets once they are created w/o modifing code. Help Desk now has a very flexible security system.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Meegeleverde blokken</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no included blocks</string><translation>Er zijn geen meegeleverde blokken</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Meegeleverde hooks</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no included hooks</string><translation>Er zijn geen meegeleverde hooks</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the Helpdesk module can be found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.abrasiontechnology.com/&quot;&gt;Abrasion Technology&lt;/a&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Help Desk Extension page at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Help Desk Module - Xaraya Extension 910</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on Help Desk found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on Help Desk</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Help Desk Module - Overview</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
