<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="fi_FI.utf-8">
<entry><string>Administration - xarBB</string><translation>xarBB ylläpito</translation></entry>
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Mikä tämä on?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>xarBB provides basic forum functions provided mainly from Xaraya utility modules (topics are provided by xarBB and reply posts by the comments module, for example). The forum itself is very light weight, but designed to handle large volume postings.</string><translation>xarBB sisältää foorumien perusominaisuudet, jotka pohjautuvat suurimmaksi osaksi Xarayan työkalumoduuleihin (esimerkiksi aiheet ovat xarBB:n ominaisuus, mutta vastausviestit käyttävät Kommentit-moduulia). Moduuli on hyvin kevyt, mutta suunniteltu käsittelemään suuriakin viestimääriä.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Miten tätä käytetään?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>xarBB allows users to post Topics and reply posts to those topics. There are a number of options available from the administration menu.</string><translation>xarBB antaa käyttäjille mahdollisuuden kirjoittaa Aiheita ja vastata niihin. Ylläpitäjät voivat muokata useita eri asetuksia tarpeidensa mukaan.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add Forums -- Allows you to add new forums to your system. Each forum has a number of configuration options.</string><translation>Lisää foorumeita -- Mahdollistaa uusien foorumien lisäämisen järjestelmääsi. Jokaisen foorumin asetuksia voidaan muokata erikseen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>View Forums -- Allows you to view the forums that you have configured on your system.</string><translation>Katsele foorumeita -- Mahdollistaa asettamiesi foorumeiden katselemisen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modify Configuration -- Allows you to set certain master configuration routines for forums.</string><translation>Muokkaa asetuksia -- Mahdollistaa foorumeiden pääasetusten muokkaamisen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Reorder Forums -- Allows you to reorder your existing forums</string><translation>Järjestele foorumeita -- Mahdollistaa käytössä olevien foorumeiden uudelleenjärjestelyn.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can add additional functionality to xarBB forums as you require it.</string><translation>Voit tarvittaessa lisätä xarBB foorumeille uusia ominaisuuksia.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Hook BBCode or HTML to allow formatted user input and also the option to supply linebreaks for plain text.</string><translation>Jos haluat sallia käyttäjille viestien muotoilun, aseta BBCode- ja HTML-koukut päälle.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Turn off modify 'stamps' in topics and posts and hook Changelog module to allow enhanced changelog management of posts and topics</string><translation>Poista 'muokattujen aiheiden leima' käytöstä ja aseta Muutosloki-koukut päälle. Näin saat käyttöösi laajemmat tiedot kaikkien aiheiden ja vastausten muutoksista.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you have imported the extra default User dynamic data such as avatars, msn, irc and so on, to your user roles, then these attributes will automatically be displayed in xarbb topics and posts.</string><translation>Jos olet tuonut järjestelmäsi Rooleihin toisesta foorumiohjelmasta käyttäjien dynaamista dataa, kuten avataria sekä msn- ja irc-tunnuksia, näkyvät ne automaattisesti xarBB:n aiheissa ja vastauksissa.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Set priviliges for Comments module and xarBB to allow or disallow viewing, posting of topics and replies, editing of their own posts by users, and setup of moderator groups.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Administrators and moderators have additional functionality including deleting posts, marking posts as announcements or sticky topics, moving posts, and locking topics from further postings.</string><translation>Ylläpitäjät ja moderaattorit voivat lisäksi poistaa, siirtää ja lukita viestejä sekä merkitä ne tiedotteiksi tai kiinnitetyiksi aiheiksi.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can build the functionality you would like into xarBB and use override templates to customize every aspect of the xarBB templates.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Sisältyvät blokit</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There is currently one block provided called Latest Posts. If the block is not
showing as an option when adding a Block instance it may not have been registered. In this case
please add the block type through Admin Blocks-Add Block Type</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Sisältyvät koukut</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There is currently a Search hook. If you hook xarBB to the Search module, users will be able to search through topics and posts, and more specifically for topic and post authors.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation>Lisätietoja</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the XarBB module can be found at</string><translation>Lisätietoja xarBB-moduulista löydät</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xarbb Extension page at</string><translation>xarBB Laajennuksen sivulta</translation></entry>
<entry><string>xarBB Module - Xaraya Extension 300</string><translation>xarBB-moduuli - Xaraya Laajennus 300</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation>Lue uusimmat tiedot Version History -välilehdeltä sivun alaosasta.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on XarBB found at</string><translation>Aiheeseen liittyvistä tutoriaaleista ja dokumentaatiosta</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on xarBB</string><translation>xarBB:hen liittyvää dokumentaatiota</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation>Xarayan Dokumentaatio -sivuilta.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>xarBB Module - Overview</string><translation>Yleiskatsaus moduulille xarBB</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation>Versio</translation></entry>
</translations>
