<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="8" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="15" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Blogger API is a XML-RPC API used for blogging. The API is very simple and is 
              basically a way to exchange strings between xmlrpc clients and servers.</string>
		<translation>Zee Blugger EPI is a XML-RPC EPI used fur bluggeeng. Zee EPI is fery seemple-a und is beseecelly a vey tu ixchunge-a streengs betveee xmlrpc cleeents und serfers.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="19" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>In Xaraya the xmlrpcserver module is responsible for providing the xmlrpc transport
              needed for the Blogger API functionality. This module will not function without
              that module activated.</string>
		<translation>In Xereya zee xmlrpcserfer mudoole-a is respunseeble-a fur prufeeding zee xmlrpc trunspurt needed fur zee Blugger EPI fooncshuneleety.Thees mudoole-a veell nut fooncshun veethuoot thet mudoole-a ecteefeted.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>In addition to that, the xmlrpcserver module needs one or more API modules
        activated to actually do anything. The bloggerAPI is one such module. It is advised that the
        xmlrpcsystemAPI module is also activated.</string>
		<translation>In eddeeshun tu thet, zee xmlrpcserfer mudoole-a needs oone-a oor mure-a EPI mudooles ecteefeted tu ectooelly du unytheeng. Zee bluggerEPI is oone-a sooch mudoole-a. It is edfeesed thet zee xmlrpcsystemEPI mudoole-a is elsu ecteefeted.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can find the specification of the Blogger API at</string>
		<translation>Yuoo cun feend zee speceefficeshun ooff zee Blugger EPI et</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Little survival guide for using Blogging tools with Xaraya</string>
		<translation>Leettle-a soorfeefel gooeede-a fur useeng Bluggeeng tuuls veet Xereya</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Make sure you have enabled the following modules</string>
		<translation>Meke-a soore-a yuoo hefe-a inebled zee fullooeeng mudooles</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="37" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>XmlRpcServer</string>
		<translation>XmlRpcSerfer</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Categories</string>
		<translation>Cetegureees</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="41" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Articles</string>
		<translation>Erteecles</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>When these modules are activated, configure the categories modules and create some
              categories which should hold the postings made from Blogs. While not necessary, it 
              is advised to create a publication type for blog postings specifically and link this
              type to the category-tree you created for blog postings.</string>
		<translation>Vhee zeese-a mudooles ere-a ecteefeted, cunffeegoore-a zee cetegureees mudooles und creete-a sume-a cetegureees vheech shuoold huld zee pusteengs mede-a frum Blugs. Vheele-a nut necessery, it is edfeesed tu creete-a a poobleeceshun type-a fur blug pusteengs speceefficelly und leenk thees type-a tu zee cetegury-tree-a yuoo creeted fur blug pusteengs. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="49" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Go into the config section of the BloggerAPI module and configure the publication type
              to use for blog postings. Select either News articles or your publication type which 
              you created.</string>
		<translation>Gu intu zee cunffeeg secshun ooff zee BluggerEPI mudoole-a und cunffeegoore-a zee poobleeceshun type-a tu use-a fur blug pusteengs. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Select ieezeer Noos erteecles oor yuoor poobleeceshun type-a vheech yuoo creeted.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="54" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Basically you're all set now to start blogging. Use your favorite tool for managing your
              blog postings. For windows we recommend</string>
		<translation>Beseecelly yuoo're-a ell set noo tu stert bluggeeng. Use-a yuoor fefureete-a tuul fur munegeeng yuoor blug pusteengs. Fur veendoos ve-a recummend</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="58" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>and
              for other operating systems</string>
		<translation>und fur oozeer oopereteeng systems</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="59" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>These two are the ones we test the API with and make sure that it at least works with those.</string>
		<translation>Zeese-a tvu ere-a zee oones ve-a test zee EPI veet und meke-a soore-a thet it et leest vurks veet thuse-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="60" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Point your blogging client to the url: http://www.yourxaraya.com/ws.php?type=xmlrpc and use
              your Xaraya account for authentication. The rest should be self-explanatory.</string>
		<translation>Pueent yuoor bluggeeng cleeent tu zee url: http://www.yourxaraya.com/ws.php?type=xmlrpc und use-a yuoor Xereya eccuoont fur oozeenteeceshun. Zee rest shuoold be-a selff-ixplunetury. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="64" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="67" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included blocks.</string>
		<translation>Zeere-a ere-a nu inclooded blucks.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="69" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="72" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included hooks.</string>
		<translation>Zeere-a ere-a nu inclooded huuks. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="74" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Extended inffurmeshun ebuoot thees mudoole-a cun be-a fuoond here-a. [mudooles mudoole-a]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bloggerapi/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="79" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
