<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>You are currently enrolled in this course</string>
		<translation>Yuoo ere-a coorrently inrulled in thees cuoorse</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/courses/xaruser/display.php" line="112" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You are currently enrolled in '. $courses[$courseid] ));
    }


    // Note : module variables can also be specified directly in the
    // blocklayout template by using &amp;xar-mod-&lt;modname&gt;-&lt;varname&gt;;
    // Note that you could also pass on the $item variable, and specify
    // the labels directly in the blocklayout template. But make sure you
    // use the &lt;xar:ml&gt;, &lt;xar:mlstring&gt; or &lt;xar:mlkey&gt; tags then, so that
    // labels can be translated for other languages...
    // Save the currently displayed item ID in a temporary variable cache
    // for any blocks that might be interested (e.g. the Others block)
    // You should use this -instead of globals- if you want to make
    // information available elsewhere in the processing of this page request
    xarVarSetCached('Blocks.courses</string>
		<translation>Yuoo ere-a coorrently inrulled in '. $courses[$courseid] )); } // Nute-a : mudoole-a fereeebles cun elsu be-a speceeffied durectly in zee // bluckleyuoot templete-a by useeng &amp;xar-mod-&lt;modname&gt;-&lt;varname&gt;; // Nute-a thet yuoo cuoold elsu pess oon zee $item fereeeble-a, und speceeffy // zee lebels durectly in zee bluckleyuoot templete-a. Boot meke-a soore-a yuoo // use-a zee &lt;xer:ml&gt;, &lt;xer:mlstreeng&gt; oor &lt;xer:mlkey&gt; tegs zeen, su thet // lebels cun be-a trunsleted fur oozeer lungooeges. Um gesh dee bork, bork!.. // Sefe-a zee coorrently deespleyed item ID in a tempurery fereeeble-a ceche-a // fur uny blucks thet meeght be-a interested (i.g. zee Oozeers bluck) // Yuoo shuoold use-a thees -insteed ooff glubels- iff yuoo vunt tu meke-a // inffurmeshun efeeeleble-a ilsoohere-a in zee prucesseeng ooff thees pege-a reqooest xerFerSetCeched('Blucks. Um gesh dee bork, bork!cuoorses</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/courses/xaruser/display.php" line="144" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
