<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
<entry><string>Overview</string><translation>Περίληψη</translation></entry>
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Τι είναι;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The LogConfig Module controls the Xaraya logging system.</string><translation>Η Μονάδα LogConfig ελέγχει το σύστημα καταγραφής του Xaraya.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Πως χρησιμοποιείται;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>From the menu, you have three choices.</string><translation>Από το menu έχετε τρείς επιλογές</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add logger -- Allows you add a new logger to the configuration.</string><translation>Προσθήκη καταγραφέα -- Επιτρέπει την προσθήκη ενός νέου καταγραφέα στις ρυθμίσεις</translation></entry>
<entry><string>List loggers -- List the loggers that are currently configured.</string><translation>Κατάλογος καταγραφέων -- Εμφάνιση καταλόγου με τους καταγραφείς που είναι ρυθμισμένοι.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Turn logging on/off -- Makes Xaraya log according to the loggers configured or not.</string><translation>Ενεργοποίηση/απενεργοποίηση καταγραφέα - Κάνει το Xaraya να καταγράφει ανάλογα με τους καταγραφείς που έχουν ρυθμιστεί ή όχι.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Fallback System:</string><translation>Σύστημα Ανάγκης:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>If the logging is set to off in this module (if this module is not active, it turns off logging automatically) and there is no logging configuration in config.system.php (old configuration style) then there is a fallback system that will log to var/logs/log.txt whenever it is present .</string><translation>Αν το σύστημα καταγραφής έχει απενεργοποιηθεί (αν η μονάδα δεν είναι ενεργή, τότε απενεργοποιείται η καταγραφή) και δεν υπάρχει ρύθμιση καταγραφής στο config.system.php (παλιό σύστημα καταγραφής), τότε υπάρχει ένα σύστημα ανάγκης που θα κάνει καταγραφή στο /var/logs/log.txt όταν αυτό είναι παρόν.</translation></entry>
</translations>
