<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Administration - Headlines</string>
		<translation>Edmeenistreshun - Heedleenes</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="1" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="9" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Headlines module allows you to syndicate content from other website.  It also allows you to use predetermined hooks from Xaraya if you have them installed and activated.</string>
		<translation>Zee Heedleenes mudoole-a elloos yuoo tu syndeecete-a cuntent frum oozeer vebseete-a. It elsu elloos yuoo tu use-a predetermeened huuks frum Xereya iff yuoo hefe-a zeem instelled und ecteefeted. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have three choices.  &quot;Modify Configuration&quot;, &quot;Add Headlines&quot;, and &quot;View Headlines&quot;.</string>
		<translation>Frum zee menoo, yuoo hefe-a three-a chueeces. Um gesh dee bork, bork! &quot;Mudeeffy Cunffeegooreshun&quot;, &quot;Edd Heedleenes&quot;, und &quot;Feeoo Heedleenes&quot;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Configuration -- Allows you to update the global configuration for the module.</string>
		<translation>Mudeeffy Cunffeegooreshun -- Elloos yuoo tu updete-a zee glubel cunffeegooreshun fur zee mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>View Headlines -- Allows you to view, edit and delete headlines that you have active for your site.</string>
		<translation>Feeoo Heedleenes -- Elloos yuoo tu feeoo, ideet und delete-a heedleenes thet yuoo hefe-a ecteefe-a fur yuoor seete-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="26" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Add Headlines -- Allows you to add a new syndication headline for processing.</string>
		<translation>Edd Heedleenes -- Elloos yuoo tu edd a noo syndeeceshun heedleene-a fur prucesseeng.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>rss</string>
		<translation>rss</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="43" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included hooks</string>
		<translation>Zeere-a ere-a nu inclooded huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="47" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Credits</string>
		<translation>Credeets</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="51" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The RSS Block is using</string>
		<translation>Zee RSS Bluck is useeng</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>PHP feedParser</string>
		<translation>PHP feedPerser</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>as its backend.   The notes for the feedParser by Reverend Jim are as follows</string>
		<translation>es its beckend. Bork bork bork! Zee nutes fur zee feedPerser by Referend Jeem ere-a es fulloos</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>feedParser was created due to the lack of a good, flexible, class-based RSS feed parser for PHP. It has been built as a class, and currently handles RSS 0.91, RSS 0.92, RSS 0.93, RSS 1.0, and RSS 2.0 feeds. For channels it grabs the title, description, link, and creator. For items it grabs the title, description, link, and date. It also provides a form of the date converted into the local timezone to facilitate cronological sorting of items. The dates are provided in UNIX timestamp format for easy manipulation by other PHP functions.</string>
		<translation>feedPerser ves creeted dooe-a tu zee leck ooff a guud, flexeeble-a, cless-besed RSS feed perser fur PHP. It hes beee booeelt es a cless, und coorrently hundles RSS 0.91, RSS 0.92, RSS 0.93, RSS 1.0, und RSS 2.0 feeds. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Fur chunnels it grebs zee teetle-a, descreepshun, leenk, und creetur. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! Fur items it grebs zee teetle-a, descreepshun, leenk, und dete-a. It elsu prufeedes a furm ooff zee dete-a cunferted intu zee lucel teemezune-a tu feceelitete-a crunulugeecel surteeng ooff items. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Zee detes ere-a prufeeded in UNIX teemestemp furmet fur iesy muneepooleshun by oozeer PHP fooncshuns. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/headlines/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="59" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
