<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
<entry><string>Release translations package</string><translation>Geef vertaling vrij</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Languages and Locales</string><translation>Talen en locales</translation></entry>
<entry><string>While translating you will be confronted with a lot of information. The settings below allow you to configure what is displayed during translation.</string><translation>Gedurende het vertalen wordt u met veel informatie geconfronteerd. De instellingen hieronder laat u kiezen wat wordt getoond tijdens het vertalen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Number of lines to display in reference</string><translation>Aantal regels om te laten zien in de verwijzing</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Choose a translation to work on</string><translation>Kies een vertaling om aan te werken</translation></entry>
<entry><string>While working inside the translations module, you always work on the translation of one particular
locale. You choose that locale below. It will activate the proper storage location for the translated
items while you are working on a translation.</string><translation>Binnen de vertaalmodule wordt altijd met een bepaalde locale gewerkt. U kiest deze locale hieronder. Dit zal de juiste opslaglocatie activeren voor de vertaalde items terwijl u aan het vertalen bent.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you don't see the locale you want in the dropdown below, you will need to create it and activate it in the Modify Config page of the Base module.</string><translation>Als de gewenste locale niet beschikbaar is in het onderstaande lijstje, moet u de locale aanmaken en activeren in de basismodule.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Translation jobs</string><translation>Vertaaltaken</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Translations Bulk Operations</string><translation>Massa vertaal acties</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The directories under #(1) must be writeable by PHP.</string><translation>De folders onder #(1) moeten beschrijfbaar zijn door de webserver.</translation></entry>
</translations>
