<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>The var/cache/output directory must be writable 
                       by the web server for output caching to work.  
                       The xarCacheManager module has not been installed, 
                       please make the var/cache/output directory 
                       writable by the web server before re-trying to 
                       install this module.</string>
		<translation>Zee var/cache/output durectury moost be-a vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer fur ooootpoot cecheeng tu vurk. Zee xerCecheMuneger mudoole-a hes nut beee instelled, pleese-a meke-a zee var/cache/output durectury vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer beffure-a re-a-tryeeng tu instell thees mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xarinit.php" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The var/cache directory must be writable 
                   by the web server for the install script to 
                   set up output caching for you.
                   The xarCacheManager module has not been installed, 
                   please make the var/cache directory 
                   writable by the web server before re-trying to 
                   install this module.  
                   Alternatively, you can manually create the 
                   var/cache/output directory and copy the 
                   xarcachemanager/config.caching.php.dist 
                   file to var/cache/config.caching.php - the output 
                   directory and the config.caching.php file must be 
                   writable by the web server for output caching to work.</string>
		<translation>Zee var/cache durectury moost be-a vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer fur zee instell screept tu set up ooootpoot cecheeng fur yuu. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! Zee xerCecheMuneger mudoole-a hes nut beee instelled, pleese-a meke-a zee var/cachedurectury vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer beffure-a re-a-tryeeng tu instell thees mudoole-a. Elterneteefely, yuoo cun munooelly creete-a zee var/cache/output durectury und cupy zee xarcachemanager/config.caching.php.dist feele-a tu var/cache/config.caching.php - zee ooootpoot durectury und zee cunffeeg.cecheeng.php feele-a moost be-a vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer fur ooootpoot cecheeng tu vurk.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xarinit.php" line="67" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>That is strange.  The default, distributed configuration 
                   file, normally #(1), seems to be 
                   missing.</string>
		<translation>Thet is stronge-a. Zee deffoolt, deestribooted cunffeegooreshun feele-a, nurmelly #(1), seems tu be-a meessing.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xarinit.php" line="90" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The var/cache directory must be writable 
                   by the web server for the install script to 
                   set up output caching for you.
                   The xarCacheManager module has not been installed, 
                   please make the var/cache directory 
                   writable by the web server before re-trying to 
                   install this module.  
                   Alternatively, you can manually copy the 
                   xarcachemanager/config.caching.php.dist 
                   file to var/cache/config.caching.php - the 
                   config.caching.php file must be writable by the
                   web server for output caching to be managed with
                   the xarcachemanager module.</string>
		<translation>Zee var/cache durectury moost be-a vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer fur zee instell screept tu set up ooootpoot cecheeng fur yuu. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! Zee xerCecheMuneger mudoole-a hes nut beee instelled, pleese-a meke-a var/cache durectury vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer beffure-a re-a-tryeeng tu instell thees mudoole-a. Elterneteefely, yuoo cun munooelly cupy zee xarcachemanager/config.caching.php.dist feele-a tu var/cache/config.caching.php - zee config.caching.php feele-a moost be-a vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer fur ooootpoot cecheeng tu be-a muneged veet zee xercechemuneger mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xarinit.php" line="116" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The xarCacheManager module upgrade has failed.  
                   Please make #(1) writable by the web server process 
                   owner to complete the upgrade.  If #(1) does not exist, 
                   please make #(2) writable by the web server process and 
                   #(1) will be created for you.</string>
		<translation>Zee xerCecheMuneger mudoole-a upgrede-a hes feeeled. Bork bork bork! Pleese-a meke-a #(1) vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer prucess oovner tu cumplete-a zee upgrede-a. Iff #(1) dues nut ixeest, pleese-a meke-a #(2) vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer prucess und #(1) veell be-a creeted fur yuu. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xarinit.php" line="254" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The xarCacheManager module upgrade has failed.  
                               The #(1) directory is missing, and the #(2) is not 
                               writable by the web server process owner. Please 
                               make #(2) writable by the web server process owner 
                               to complete the upgrade.  Alternatively, the #(1) 
                               directory can be manually created.  #(1) must be 
                               writable by the web service process owner for 
                               output caching to work.</string>
		<translation>Zee xerCecheMuneger mudoole-a upgrede-a hes feeeled. Bork bork bork! Zee #(1) durectury is meessing, und zee #(2) is nut vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer prucess oovner. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! Pleese-a meke-a #(2) vreeteble-a by zee veb serfer prucess oovner tu cumplete-a zee upgrede-a. Elterneteefely, zee #(1) durectury cun be-a munooelly creeted. Bork bork bork! #(1) moost be-a vreeteble-a by zee veb serfeece-a prucess oovner fur ooootpoot cecheeng tu vurk.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xarinit.php" line="461" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
