<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
<entry><string>The #(1) directory is not writable by the web
web server. The #(1) must be writable by the web
server process owner for output caching to work.
Please change the permission on the #(1) directory
so that the web server can write to it.</string><translation>Το directory #(1) δεν είναι εγγράψιμο από τον web server. Το #(1) πρέπει να είναι εγγράψιμο από τον web server για να δουλέψει το output caching. Παρακαλούμε αλλάξτε τα δικαιώματα στο directory #(1) ώστε ο web server να γράφει σε αυτό.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>That is strange. The #(1) file seems to be
missing.</string><translation>Το αρχείο #(1) φαίνεται ότι απουσιάζει.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Flush</string><translation>Καθαρισμός</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Block level output caching does not have the same dynamic content limitations. It is purpose-built to allow Xaraya to fully load the core and active module(s) with each page request. Block output caching can be configure on a per block instance basis, so you can have some block instances be fully dynamic (never cached), while other instances are cached for varying lifetimes. The cache of each block instance can be configure to be or not be shared between users (or groups of users) and pages. This allows for very flexible output caching behaviors for sites with mixed static and dynamic pages, but the tradeoff is a much higher fixed cost (page generation time). Where page level output caching can reduce a site's page generation time by 65 to 80% (YMMV depending on site configuration), block level output caching general only reduced page generation time by 20 to 30%.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string><translation>Επεκτατεμένοι πληροφορίες για την μονάδα μπορούν να βρεθούν εδώ.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enable the Output Caching System:</string><translation>Ενεργοποίηση του Συστήματος Output Caching:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Cache the Output of this Theme:</string><translation>Cache αυτού του Theme:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Cache Size Limit (in MB):</string><translation>Ορίο Μεγέθους Cache (σε MB):</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enable Page Output Caching:</string><translation>Ενεργοποίηση Cache Σελίδων</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Page Cache Expiration Time (in hh:mm:ss):</string><translation>Χρόνος Λήξης Cache Σελίδας (σε ωω:λλ:δδ):</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Cache Item Display Pages:</string><translation>Cache Σελίδων</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Flush Cached Display Page on New Comment:</string><translation>Καθάρισμο Cache Σελίδας σε Νέο Σχόλιο:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Flush Cached Display Page on New Hooked Poll Vote:</string><translation>Καθάρισμο Cache Σελίδας σε Νέα Ψήφο Συνδεδεμένης Ψηφοφορίας</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Show the &quot;Last Modified&quot; Stamp on Cached Pages:</string><translation>Εμφάνιση Σφραγίδας &quot;Τελευταίας Τροποποίησης&quot; στις Αποθηκευμένες Σελίδες</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Allow clients to reuse locally cached pages without re-validation:</string><translation>Να επιτρέπεται στους χρήστες η επαναχρήση τοπικά αποθηκευμένων χωρίς επαλήθευση</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Auto-regenerate cache of session-less URL list:</string><translation>Αυτόματη δημιουργία cache του κατάλογου URL εκτός συνεδρίας</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Only cache pages of modules hooked to xarCacheManger:</string><translation>Μόνο αποθήκευση των σελίδων των μονάδων που είναι συνδεδεμένος στο xarCacheManager:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Block Cache Expiration Time (in hh:mm:ss):</string><translation>Χρόνος Λήξης Block Cache (σε ωω:λλ:δδ):</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Block Cache Size Limit (in MB):</string><translation>Όριο Μεγέθους Block Cache (σε MB):</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Block caching is currently disabled...</string><translation>Το Block caching είναι απενεργοποιημένο...</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Expiration Time</string><translation>Χρόνος Λήξης</translation></entry>
</translations>
