<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="it_IT.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Administration - Example</string>
		<translation>Amministrazione - esempio</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Sommario</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="5" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Che cos'e'?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="11" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This module allows you to create and display sub-items for any module item. In the words of the author :</string>
		<translation>Questo modulo ti permette di creare e mostrare sottoelementi per ciascun elemento di un modulo.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="15" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;p&gt;For example, if you want to have a pubtype &quot;cooking recipe&quot;. This
pubtype could be to store the ingredients of the meal, thus there would
be required a list of input fields: ingredient1, quantity1,
pic1(extended info :-) ) , ingredient2, quantity2, pic2,...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The disadvantage of this is the high number of fields to ensure, that
there your users aren't going against the limit. Furthermore there are
always displayed all input fields. And of course it's not a very nice
way to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I didn't know how to do this better, I had a dream about a module,
which can be hooked from any other module and which is able to display /
provide editing / etc. for subitems to an item. I had a dream about a
table, which saves the information, which DD-Object stores the subitems
of &quot;module&quot; / &quot;itemtype&quot; combination and another table containing which
DD-Itemids belong to &quot;module&quot; / &quot;itemtype&quot; / &quot;itemid&quot; in this DD-Object
(1 to n Relation). I had the dream to share my module with the community.
Now, the module is here, and all dreams got true. If you didn't get my
technical information, don't worry. &lt;/p&gt;</string>
		<translation>&lt;p&gt;Per esempio, se vuoi avere un tipo di pubblicazione &quot;ricette&quot;, devi avere una serie di campi input per gli ingredienti (ingrediente1, quantita'1, figura1, ingrediente2, quantita2, figura2, etc...)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lo svantaggio e' che questo richiede un alto numero di campi, che vengono mostrati anche se rimarranno vuoti. Questo modulo invece ti permette di richiedere campi solo se necessari.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="34" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Come si usa?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt; install module&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; goto dynamicdata admin area, new object, create a dynamic data object
, which should hold the subitem information (you must have one field
with the ItemID, default 0, display only) -&gt; remember the objectid, edit
label (used for display) and name (used for custom default template)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; goto subitems module, admin area -&gt; add link -&gt; type in objectid (from
previsously created dd-object), module name, itemtype&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; goto module modules, hooks -&gt; subitems -&gt; enable the hook for the
module /itemtype combination, you created the link for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
-&gt; now it should work (tested with custom pubtype)</string>
		<translation>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;installa modulo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;vai all'amministrazione dati dinamici, nuovo oggetto, crea un oggetto dati dinamici; questo oggetto conterra' le informazioni del sottoelemento; includi un campo con l'identificatore elemento (ItemID), predefinito 0, sola visualizzazione (display only); ricorda l'identificatore oggetto, etichetta e nome (per usarlo nel modello di visualizzaizone) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;vai al modulo sottelementi, area dmin, aggiungi link, inserisci l'identificatore oggetto (dall'oggetto dati dinamici appena creato), il nome modulo, il tipo di elemento&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;vai al modulo moduli, agganci, sottoelementi, abilita l'aggancio per il modulo e tipo di elemento desiderato&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Blocchi inclusi</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="59" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>none</string>
		<translation>nessuno</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="63" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Agganci inclusi</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="67" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>new/create/modify/update/delete -- Allows you to create/update sub-items</string>
		<translation>new/create/modify/update/delete -- Ti permette di creare e aggiornare i sottoelementi</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="72" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>display -- Allows you to display sub-items</string>
		<translation>visualizza -- Ti permette di visualizzare i sottoelementi</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="73" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="78" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
