<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="sv_SE.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>select the keywords for this item.</string>
		<translation>välj nyckelord för denna post.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-modifyhook.xd" line="11" />
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-newhook.xd" line="3" />
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-newhook.xd" line="11" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>select the keywords for this item.</string>
		<translation>välj nyckelord för denna post.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-modifyhook.xd" line="11" />
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-newhook.xd" line="3" />
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-newhook.xd" line="11" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>that allows you to assign keywords to module items (taxonomy) and to look up items by keyword. Enable its hooks for any module where you want to use it...</string>
		<translation>som låter dig tilldela nyckelord till modulposter (taxonomi) och för att slå upp poster efter nyckelord. Aktivera dess kopplingar för någon modul där du vill använda den...</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="14" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>After enabling the keywords hooks for a particular module, you'll see an input box where you can fill in relevant keywords whenever you create or modify a module item.
Afterwards, when viewing an item, you can retrieve a list of other items having the same keyword(s).</string>
		<translation>Efter att ha aktiverat nyckelordskopplingar för en viss modul, kommer du se en indataruta där du kan fylla i relevanta nyckelord när du skapar eller ändrar en modulpost. Efter detta, när en post visas,kan du hämta en lista över andra poster som har samma nyckelord.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This module, now, may also restrict keywords to a predefined set of words, tipical for each hooked module.</string>
		<translation>Den här modulen, kan nu även begränsa nyckelord till en fördefinierad uppställning ord, typiska för varje kopplad modul.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>In the future thi module may try to extract keywords
automatically from other fields on create/update. Contributions in that or other directions are welcome :-)</string>
		<translation>I framtiden, kan den här modulen försöka ta fram nyckelord automatiskt från andra fält vid skapning/uppdatering. Medverkan för detta eller andra för annat välkomnas :-)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="24" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included blocks at this time</string>
		<translation>Det finns inga medföljande block</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Ytterligare information om den här modulen finns här. [modules module]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/keywords/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="43" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
