<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsql/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsql/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The AuthSQL module allows you to authenticate a user with an SQL server.  The AuthSQL module forwards the username and password from the login screen to the SQL server for authentication.</string>
		<translation>Zee OothSQL mudoole-a elloos yuoo tu oozeenteecete-a a user veet un SQL serfer. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! Zee OothSQL mudoole-a furverds zee userneme-a und pessvurd frum zee lugeen screee tu zee SQL serfer fur oozeenteeceshun.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsql/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsql/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Authentication by AuthSQL is automatically set once the the AuthSQL module has been initialized.   To remove AuthSQL authentication, you must remove the module.</string>
		<translation>Oozeenteeceshun by OothSQL is ootumeteecelly set oonce-a zee zee OothSQL mudoole-a hes beee ineetielized. Bork bork bork! Tu remufe-a OothSQL oozeenteeceshun, yuoo moost remufe-a zee mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsql/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have one choice.  &quot;Modify Config&quot;.</string>
		<translation>Frum zee menoo, yuoo hefe-a oone-a chueece-a. &quot;Mudeeffy Cunffeeg&quot;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsql/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Config -- From here, you can allow a user that has account information in SQL to be automatically added to the Xaraya database and allowed to login.</string>
		<translation>Mudeeffy Cunffeeg -- Frum here-a, yuoo cun elloo a user thet hes eccuoont inffurmeshun in SQL tu be-a ootumeteecelly edded tu zee Xereya detebese-a und ellooed tu lugeen. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsql/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsql/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included blocks with the AuthSQL Module</string>
		<translation>Zeere-a ere-a nu inclooded blucks veet zee OothSQL Mudoole</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsql/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
