<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="uk_UA.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Огляд</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="4" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Що це?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="14" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Base Module controls the behind the scenes processing for your Xaraya installation.</string>
		<translation>Модуль основи (base) керує процесами, що проходять у Вашій Зарайї поза сценою.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Як цим користуватись?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have two choices.</string>
		<translation>З меню можна вибрати дві дії.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>View System Information -- Allows you to print your server and php set-up for trouble shooting.</string>
		<translation>Переглянути системну інформацію - Дозволяє друкувати налаштування сервера і php для вирішення проблем.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Config -- Allows you to change some of the settings controlling the core behaviour of the site.</string>
		<translation>Змінити Конфігурацію - Дозволяє міняти деякі параметри, які керують поведінкою ядра сайту.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="26" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Включені блоки</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>RSS Class</string>
		<translation>Клас RSS</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The RSS capabilities in Xaraya use &lt;a href=&quot;http://freshmeat.net/projects/phpfeedparser/?topic_id=914&quot;&gt;PHP feedParser&lt;/a&gt; as their backend.   The notes for the feedParser by Reverend Jim are as follows:</string>
		<translation>Для RSS в Зарайї використовується сервер &lt;a href=&quot;http://freshmeat.net/projects/phpfeedparser/?topic_id=914&quot;&gt;PHP feedParser&lt;/a&gt;. Примітки Reverend Jim для feedParser:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>feedParser was created due to the lack of a good, flexible, class-based RSS feed parser for PHP. It has been built as a class, and currently handles RSS 0.91, RSS 0.92, RSS 0.93, RSS 1.0, and RSS 2.0 feeds. For channels it grabs the title, description, link, and creator. For items it grabs the title, description, link, and date. It also provides a form of the date converted into the local timezone to facilitate chronological sorting of items. The dates are provided in UNIX timestamp format for easy manipulation by other PHP functions.</string>
		<translation>feedParser був створений, бо невистарчало доброго, гнучкого й основаного на сласах аналізатора подачі RSS для PHP. Він був збудований як клас, і зараз підтримує подачі RSS 0.91, RSS 0.92, RSS 0.93, RSS 1.0 і RSS 2.0. Для каналів, він схоплює заголовок, опис, link, and creator. For items it grabs the title, description, посилання і дату. Він також постачає дату в формі місцевих часових зон для забезпечення хронологічного сортування елементів. Дати подаються в форматі часових міток UNIX для легкого маніпулювання іншими функціями PHP.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Expire a Block</string>
		<translation>Завершити термін блока</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Currently, the HTML and Text blocks can both expire content if you wish.  If you have a message that you would like to only have visible for a certain period of time, you can expire the block.  This functionality can be used in conjunction with any placement or block group that you assign the block.</string>
		<translation>На даний час, блоки HTML і тексту можуть, на Ваше бажання, закінчувати термін вмісту. Якщо Ви маєте поідомлення, яке має бути видимим тільки певний перід часу, Ви можете завершити термін блока. Ці функційні можливості можуть викормстовуватись сумісно з будь-яким вмістом чи блоковою групою, до якої приписаний блок.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="45" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Включені хуки</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="48" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Base Module has no hooks included at this time.</string>
		<translation>Модуль основи поки що не включає хуків.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="51" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Детальнішу інформацію про цей модуль можна знайти тут. [modules module]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="54" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
