<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Τι είναι;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Courses is the documented Xaraya Courses Module.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>It is currently responsible for accomplishing these main tasks:</string><translation>Είναι αυτή την στιγμή υπεύθυνη για τα παρακάτω:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Manages the course offerings to students.</string><translation>Διαχειρίζεται τις προσφορές μαθημάτων σε σπουδαστές.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Users can enroll into courses.</string><translation>Οι χρήστες μπορούν να εγγραφούν στα μαθήματα.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Produces overviews of courses, participants and the planning.</string><translation>Παράγει περιλήψεις μαθημάτων, συμμετοχόντων και τον προγραμματισμό.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Sends out registration emails.</string><translation>Στέλνει e-mail εγγραφής.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Allow teachers to be attached to a course, so they can manage their own course.</string><translation>Επιτρέπει στους καθηγητές να συνδεθούν σε ένα μάθημα, ώστε να μπορούν να διαχειριστούν τα μαθήματά τους.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Πως χρησιμοποιείται;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>First define at least one coursetype. Most of the time you will only need one type: your own. However, you can define other ones, like external courses that you want to display as well. Hooks are added to these coursetypes, eg categories are taking the coursetype settings as the main setting.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>To set up the course offerings you will need to understand the way courses are setup.</string><translation>Για να ορίσετε τα μαθήματα, θα πρέπει να καταλάβετε πως είναι ορισμένα τα μαθήματα.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Courses are single entities that are present in the system. The information regarding a course is rather fixed. Courses are offered to users in Xaraya, this means they are planned. Another word for this planning can be a delivered course.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Once the course is planned, you can attach more information to the planned course like a start date, maximum number of participants, location etc.</string><translation>Αφού ένα μάθημα προγραμματιστεί, μπορείτε να ορίσετε περισσότερες πληροφορίες, όπως ημερομηνία έναρξης, μέγιστος αριθμός συμμετεχόντων, τοποθεσία κλπ.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>A good working order would be:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Create a coursetype and save it.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Set the correct parameters for the coursetype by going to the modify option for the coursetype.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Create a course when you have selected the appropriate coursetype it holds.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Once the course it created and saved you can plan the course (create a delivered course). Set the start and enddate. Set the number of participants. When a maximum number is not 0, the coursesubcription will automatically use this maximum number of participants and use a waiting list if the course becomes overbooked.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Turn on short urls and access your course via [yourdomain]/courses/course/[coursecode].</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Watch the number of studends grow via the planning page.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add the upcoming courses block to your site and advertise the courses that are not fully booked.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Block που συμπεριλαμβάνονται</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Upcoming courses. This is a block which shows the courses in the near future</string><translation>Επόμενα μαθήματα. Αυτό το block εμφανίζει μαθήματα στο κοντινό μέλλον</translation></entry>
<entry><string>We plan to offer another Admin Block with short term information</string><translation>Σχεδιάζουν να εμφανίζει ένα άλλο Block Διαχείρισης με πληροφορίες σύντομου χρονικού ορίζονται</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Hooks που συμπεριλαμβάνονται</translation></entry>
<entry><string>usermenu -- Allows interface with the &quot;My Account Page&quot;</string><translation>usermenu -- Επιτρέπει σύνδεση με την σελίδα &quot;Ο Λογαριασμός Μου</translation></entry>
<entry><string>search -- Allows interface with Search Module</string><translation>search -- Επιτρέπει την σύνδεση με την μονάδα Αναζήτηση</translation></entry>
<entry><string>In these cases, the Courses module provides the hook functionality.
To activate the hooks go to</string><translation>Σε αυτές τις περιπτώσεις η μονάδα Μαθήματα παρέχει την λειτουργικότητα hook. Για να την ενεργοποιήσετε πηγαίντε στο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modules - Configure Hooks - Courses Module</string><translation>Μονάδες - Ρύθμιση Hooks - Μονάδα Μαθήματα</translation></entry>
<entry><string>From there click on the checkbox in either Roles or
the Search module to activate the respective hooks.</string><translation>Εκεί πατήστε στο checkbox στην μονάδα Ρόλοι ή στην μονάδα Αναζήτηση για να ενεργοποιήσετε το σχετικό hook.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Dynamic Data Properties</string><translation>Ιδιότητες Δυναμικών Δεδομένων που συμπεριλαμβάνονται</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Courselisting -- Provides a dropdown of courses</string><translation>Courselisting -- παρέχε μια μπάρα κύλισης με τα μαθήματα</translation></entry>
<entry><string>This listing can be used in other modules or in your own template. It will show a listing of courses found when you set the validation.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The validation rules are:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The coursetype as a number. These are the coursetypes defined in the coursetypes.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The courselevel as a number.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>you can add extra categories by adding catids and use a + or - to glue them.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation>Περισσότερες πληροφορίες</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the Courses module can be found at</string><translation>Περισσότερεςπ πληροφορίες για την μονάδα Μαθήματα μπορεί να βρεθεί στο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Courses Extension page at</string><translation>Σελίδα Επέκτασης Μαθημάτων στο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Courses Module - Xaraya Extension 179</string><translation>Μονάδα Μαθήματα - Επέκταση Xaraya 179</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation>Πατήστε στην Ιστορία Εκδόσεων στο κάτω τμήμα της σελίδας για να λάβετε τις τελευταίες πληροφορίες έκδοσης.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on Courses found at</string><translation>Τα σχετικά μαθήματα και τεκμηρίωσης μπορούν να βρεθούν στο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on Courses</string><translation>Σχετική τεκμηρίωση για τα μαθήματα</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation>Τεκμηρίωση Xaraya</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Courses Module - Overview</string><translation>Μονάδα Μαθήματα - Περίληψη</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation>Έκδοση</translation></entry>
</translations>
