<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="sv_SE.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Introduction</string>
		<translation>Introduktion</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our
web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as &quot;Data&quot; below)
that may be collected by us on our site. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own
or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control.</string>
		<translation>Vi tar din rätt till integritet på allvar och vill att du ska känna dig bekväm med att använda vår webbplats. Den här Integritetspolicyn beskriver vilken identifierbar (nedan kallad som &quot;Data&quot;) som kan komma samlas in av oss på vår webbplats. Den här policyn gäller inte för andra enheter som vi inte äger eller kontroller eller personer som inte är våra anställda, representanter eller utom vår kontroll.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="41" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Please take time to read our &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;Terms of Use&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Vänligen, ta dig lite tid att läsa webbplatsens &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;Användarvilkor&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="46" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Collection of Data</string>
		<translation>Insamling av Data</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Our registration process requires only a valid e-mail address and a unique user ID and
password. Providing us with other information is at your option. Please take note that
your user name, e-mail address, or other submissions that you make on this site may contain
your real name or other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear on
this site. Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that
is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie information. Information
about how advertising may be served on this site (if at all) is set forth below.</string>
		<translation>Vår registreringsprocess kräver endast en giltig e-postadress och ett unikt användar-ID och lösenord. Att fylla i mer information är frivilligt. Vänligen notera att ditt användarnamn, e-postadress eller annan information som du skickar in till den här webbplatsen kan innehålla ditt riktiga namn eller annan personlig identifierbar information och, som ett resultat kan visas på den här webbplatsen. Som mnga andra webbplatser, kanvi även få åtkomst till generell information som finns i våra serverloggfiler så som din IP-adress och kak-information. Information om hur annonser kan presenteras på den här webbplatsen (om överhuvudtaget) beskrivs nedan.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Use of Data</string>
		<translation>Användning av Data</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="69" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>We may use Data to customize and improve your user experience on this site.
We will make efforts so that your Data will not be provided to third parties unless (i)
provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when
you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our
site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an
Application Service Provider; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (v) we find
that your use of this site violates our this Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines
or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property; (vi) or (vi)
this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the Data
in the same manner as we can as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links
that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies
that appear on those sites.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="83" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Cookies</string>
		<translation>Kakor</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="87" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience,
such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so,
may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties
providing the advertisement. However, the companies serving the advertising do not have access to
our cookies. These companies usually use non-personally identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain
information about your visits to our site.</string>
		<translation>Som många andra webbplatser, använder vi oss av kakor till att förbättra din upplevelse, så som komma ihåg dina personliga inställningar. Annonser kan visas på vårwebbplats och, om så, kan använda kakor på din dator och är föremål för integrietspolicyn för de parter som tillhandahåller annonsen. Företagen som tillhandahåller annonsen har, hur som helst, ingen tillgång till våra kakor. Dessa företag använder icke-personligt identifierbara eller anonyma koder till att anskaffa information om dina besök på vår webbplats.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="94" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to find out more information about
your options including from the following companies that may serve advertising on our site:</string>
		<translation>Du kan &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;klicka här&gt;/a&gt; för att få mer information om dina alternativ inklusive följande bolag som kan visa annonser på vår webbplats:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="102" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>AffiliateShop</string>
		<translation>AffiliateShop</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="107" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>AssociatePrograms.com</string>
		<translation>AssociatePrograms.com</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="108" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Be Free</string>
		<translation>Be Free</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="109" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Click Trade</string>
		<translation>Click Trade</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="110" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Commission Junction</string>
		<translation>Commission Junction</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="111" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>DoubleClick</string>
		<translation>DoubleClick</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="112" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Linkshare</string>
		<translation>Linkshare</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="113" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Children</string>
		<translation>Minderåriga</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="117" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>We do not allow persons who are aged #(1) (#(2)) or younger to become members of this site.</string>
		<translation>Vi tillåter inte personer som är #(1) (#(2)) eller yngre att bli medlemmar på den här webbplatsen.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="119" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>For more information, please contact &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(1)&quot;&gt;our webmaster&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>För mer information, vänligen kontakata &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(!)&quot;&gt;vår webbansvarige&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="125" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Editing or Deleting Your Account Information</string>
		<translation>Ändra eller ta bort din kontoinformation</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="133" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>We provide you with the ability to edit the information in your user account information
that you provided to us in registration by using &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;your personal page configuration area&lt;/a&gt;.
You may request deletion of your user account by contacting &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(2)&quot;&gt;our webmaster&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Vi tillhandahåller dig möjligheten att redigera informationen för ditt användarkonto som du angav vid registreringen genom att använda &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;din personliga sidas konfigurationsfunktion&lt;/a&gt;. Du kan begära att få ditt konto borttaget genom att kontakta &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(2)&gt;vår webbansvarige&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="139" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that is not contained within your
user account, such as posts that may appear within our forums, may continue to remain on our site at our
discretion even though your user account is deleted.</string>
		<translation>Innehåll eller annan data som du kan ha tillhandahållit oss och som inte finns i ditt användarkonto, så som inlägg som visas i våra forum, kan fortsätta att kvarligga på vår webbplats efter vårt eget godtycke även om ditt konto är borttaget.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="148" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Changes to this Privacy Policy</string>
		<translation>Ändringar av den här integritetspolicyn</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="152" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial
changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message
to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.</string>
		<translation>Vi kan komma att göra förändringar av den här policyn från tid till tid. Vi kommer meddela dig större ändringar av den här policyn antingen genom att lägga upp ett framträdande meddelande på vår webbplats och/eller genom att skicka ett meddelande till e-postadressen som du har tillhandahållit oss och som finns bland dina personliga inställningar.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="156" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>NO GUARANTEES</string>
		<translation>INGA GARANTIER</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="161" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make
efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond
our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or
representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.</string>
		<translation>MEdan den här Integritetspolicyn upplyser om våra underhållsstandarder av data och vi kommer anstränga oss för att uppnå dem, är vi inte i en position att vi kan garantera dessa standarder. Det kan finnas faktorer utom vår kontroll som kan leda till avslöjande av data. Som en konsekvens, friskriver vi oss från eventuella garantier relaterade till underhåll eller icke avslöjande av data.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="166" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Contact Information</string>
		<translation>Kontaktinformation</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="171" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free
to contact &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(1)&quot;&gt;our Webmaster&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Om du har några frågor om den här policyn eller vår webbplats, vänligen känn dig välkommen att kontakta &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(1)&gt;vår webbansvarige&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="176" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Privacy Policy Not Active</string>
		<translation>Integritetspolicyn är inte aktiverad</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="182" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
