<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="pt_BR.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Name &lt;e-mail&gt;</string>
		<translation>Nome &lt;email&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xarsetup.php" line="152" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Allowed HTML tags</string>
		<translation>Comandos HTML permitidos</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-modify.xd" line="92" />
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-new.xd" line="81" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If this is your first visit to this part of your Xaraya site,
please take a minute to read through the following introduction,
in order to explore the different possibilities offered by the
articles module.</string>
		<translation>Se esta é sua primeira visita a esta parte do Xaraya, por favor, leia as instruções a seguir para explorar as diferentes possibilidades do módulo Artigos.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The articles module can manage 'articles' of different types at
the same time, for instance news articles, longer documents in
different sections, frequently asked questions, and so on.</string>
		<translation>O módulo Artigos por gerenciar &quot;artigos&quot; de diferentes tipos ao mesmo tempo, por exemplo: notícias, documentos longos em diferentes seções, dúvidas freqüentes e assim por diante.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>These types are called 'publication types', and each type of article
can make use of a different set of data fields, with a different
meaning for each data field. For example, the 'summary' field
could be used for an Introduction in news articles, for providing
some details about a question in FAQs, or not be used at all for
section documents.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There is a specific menu where you can manage those &lt;strong&gt;publication types&lt;/strong&gt;,
change the description that will appear in navigation menus, enable and
disable data fields or change their meaning for a particular type, or
even create or delete publication types according to your needs.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Each publication type also has its own templates, so that you can
customize the look &amp;amp; feel of how each article will appear to your
visitors.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="44" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>A default set of publication types and templates (corresponding
to the old News, Sections and FAQs modules, if you're familiar with
earlier versions of PostNuke or PHP-Nuke) is included as part of the
installation.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="49" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Articles (of any type) can be organised into categories. You could use
one or more common categories across different publication types, or
use specific categories for each type of article, or any combination
that you might prefer for your site.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="56" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Before you start specifying which article types will be using what categories,
you should create the categorization you want via the
&lt;a href=&quot;index.php?module=categories&amp;amp;type=admin&quot;&gt;Categories&lt;/a&gt;
administration menu. A default set of categories has been defined for
articles when you installed this module, as an example to get you started.
(You can adapt the categories later on, of course.)</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="63" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Once you have a set of categories you would like to use for your articles,
you can go to &lt;strong&gt;Articles Configuration&lt;/strong&gt;, and specify the number
of categories that can be used for each publication type, and the 'base
categories' to be used.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="68" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>A 'base category' is any starting point somewhere in your tree of categories,
below which you will have the actual list (or subtree) of categories people
can choose from when they submit or view articles. For example, you could have
a 'base category' called Topics, with a list of different topics relevant to
your site below it, and another 'base category' called Cities, with a
list of cities or places that you would provide regional news for.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="75" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>One topic might be 'Good Restaurants', and one city might 'Brussels', so people
would be able to browse through any articles about good restaurants in Brussels,
for instance.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="79" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>status = submitted, rejected, approved or on frontpage
(for those pubtypes that use it !)</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="84" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>In &lt;strong&gt;Articles Configuration&lt;/strong&gt;, set start view (list/browse), # of
columns and items, show category links + # of comments (+ performance impact)</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="89" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>overall enable/disable in 'base' admin + specific enable/disable in 'articles'
admin + use of module aliases</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="108" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Module aliases seem to be disabled at the moment - uncomment the line in
includes/xarServer.php if you want to try it out</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="111" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Default Publication Type for the Articles &quot;Front Page&quot;</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="32" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Some examples : (assuming your users have read access by default)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
- In order to allow 'Friends' to submit News Articles (and only that), define a privilege 'SubmitNews'
(or whatever name you prefer), and choose the publication type &quot;News Articles&quot; (instance 1:All:All:All) and
access level &quot;Submit (Comment)&quot; above. Press &quot;Finish and Apply to Privilege&quot;, and then assign that privilege to the 'Friends' role.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
- In order to stop 'Strangers' from viewing Documents, define some privilege 'NoDocuments' with publication type
&quot;Documents&quot; (instance 2:All:All:All) and access level &quot;No Access&quot;. Then assign that privilege to the 'Strangers' role.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
- ...
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</string>
		<translation>Alguns exemplos (assumindo que seus usuários tenham acesso a leitura por padrão) &lt;br /&gt; - Para permitir que &quot;Amigos&quot; enviem Notícias (e apenas isso), defina um privilégio 'EnviarNotícia' (use o nome que preferir), e escolha a publicação &quot;Notícias&quot; (ocorência 1:Todos:Todos:Todos) e nível de acesso &quot;Enviar / Comentar&quot; acima. Pressione &quot;Concluir e Aplicar ao Privilégio&quot;, e então designe esse privilégio para o papel &quot;Amigos&quot;. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - Para impedir que &quot;Estranhos&quot; vejam Documentos, defina um privilério 'SemDocumentos' para a publicação &quot;Documentos&quot; (ocorrência 2:Todos:Todos:Todos) e nível de acesso &quot;Sem Acesso&quot;. Então designe esse privilégio ao papel &quot;Estranhos&quot;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; - ...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-privileges.xd" line="133" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Note: if you want to deny access to all articles in a particular category with ID 123, you can also define a privilege
for module 'categories', component 'Category', category name 'All' and category ID '123'. This will remove the category
from the articles map and categories navigation as well.</string>
		<translation>Atenção: se quiser negar acesso a todos os artigos em uma categoria específica com ID 123, você pode definir um privilégio para o módulo 'categorias', componente 'Categoria', nome da categoria 'Todos' e ID da categoria '123'. Isso também vai remover a categoria do mapa do site e da navegação por categorias.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-privileges.xd" line="139" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt; articles of this publication type will use the templates &lt;i&gt;user-display-[publicationtype].xd&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;user-summary-[publicationtype].xd&lt;/i&gt; by default.&lt;br /&gt;Don't forget to provide those templates before trying to add new articles...</string>
		<translation>&lt;strong&gt;Atenção:&lt;/strong&gt; artigos desta publicação usam os modelos &lt;em&gt;user-display-[tipodepublicacao].xd&lt;/em&gt; e &lt;em&gt;user-summary-[tipodepublicacao].xd&lt;/em&gt; por padrão. &lt;br /&gt;Não se esqueça de fornecer esses modelos antes de tentar adicionar novos artigos.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-pubtypes.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Alternate Title:</string>
		<translation>Título Alternativo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/blocks/modify-random.xd" line="91" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Alternate Summary:</string>
		<translation>Resumo Alternativo:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/blocks/modify-random.xd" line="100" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
