<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="de_DE.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Removed from Privilege</string>
		<translation>Von Privilegien entfernt</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xaradmin/removemember.php" line="49" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>View Privilege:</string>
		<translation>Privileg anzeigen:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-displayprivilege.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>All privileges in the system can be changed or removed. (For those protected by GeneralLock above this takes a bit more doing.) You can also combine privileges by using them as elements to create compound privileges, or make new privileges of your choosing. There is no limit to the number of privileges you can create or their levels of nesting.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="68" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found in</string>
		<translation>Weitere Informationen zu diesem Modul können gefunden werden in</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="90" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Module to which this provilege will apply</string>
		<translation>Modul, für das dieses Privileg gilt</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-newprivilege.xd" line="120" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya's privileges are extremely flexible. You can define privileges at the level of site, modules, component classes within modules, or single instances of those classes.</string>
		<translation>Xaraya's Privilegien sind extrem flexibel. Berechtigungen können auf der Stufe von Websites, Modulen, Komponentenklassen innerhalb von Modulen oder einzelnen Instanzen eben dieser Klassen definieren werden.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="26" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Clicking on the View Privileges link gives you an overview of all the privileges on your system. Compound privileges are collapsed, but you can click on them to open them up and view their components.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="44" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Administration: a privilege that gives a role complete access to all resources on the site. At installation this privilege is assigned to the role Administrators and is inherited by the user Admin.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="57" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>CasualAccess: this is the privilege assigned to unregistered users on the site. It is initially defined to allow viewing access of the front page, as well as access to the login block.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="60" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>GeneralLock: a privilege that restricts access to certain basic roles and privileges the system requires, such as the default admin. This is to avoid inadvertent removal.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="63" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>All privileges in the system can be changed or removed. (For those protected by GeneralLock
above this takes a bit more doing.) You can also combine privileges by using them as elements to create
compound privileges, or make new privileges of your choosing. There is no limit to the number of privileges
you can create or their levels of nesting.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="71" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Remember that you can assign privileges to the Myself role, and those privileges will
only apply to a specific user and the content owned or authored by that specific eg they could edit
their own articles, or comments but not articles or comments created by others.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="96" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Privileges Module - Overview</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="128" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>(applies only to the Text Value option above)</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="235" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
