<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The AuthURL module allows you to authenticate a user based on their access to another URL/site.  The AuthURL module sends a HTTP basic authentication request to the specified URL with the credentials supplied from the login form.</string>
		<translation>Zee OothOoRL mudoole-a elloos yuoo tu oozeenteecete-a a user besed oon zeeur eccess tu unuzeer URL/seete-a. Zee OothOoRL mudoole-a sends a HTTP beseec oozeenteeceshun reqooest tu zee speceeffied URL veet zee credenteeels sooppleeed frum zee lugeen furm.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Authentication by AuthURL is automatically set once the the AuthURL module has been initialized.  To remove AuthURL authentication, you must remove the module.</string>
		<translation>Oozeenteeceshun by OothOoRL is ootumeteecelly set oonce-a zee zee OothOoRL mudoole-a hes beee ineetielized. Bork bork bork! Tu remufe-a OothOoRL oozeenteeceshun, yuoo moost remufe-a zee mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have one choice.  &quot;Modify Config&quot;.  From here, you:</string>
		<translation>Frum zee menoo, yuoo hefe-a oone-a chueece-a. &quot;Mudeeffy Cunffeeg&quot;. Frum here-a, yuoo:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Set the URL to authenticate users against.</string>
		<translation>Set zee URL tu oozeenteecete-a users egeeenst. Um de hur de hur de hur.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Allow a user that successfully authenticates to be automatically added to the Xaraya database and allowed to login.</string>
		<translation>Elloo a user thet sooccessffoolly oozeenteecetes tu be-a ootumeteecelly edded tu zee Xereya detebese-a und ellooed tu lugeen.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="32" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Set the default group that users are added to if they are automatically created.</string>
		<translation>Set zee deffoolt gruoop thet users ere-a edded tu iff zeey ere-a ootumeteecelly creeted. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Set the level of output that this module logs (useful for seeing what is happening under the hood).</string>
		<translation>Set zee lefel ooff ooootpoot thet thees mudoole-a lugs (useffool fur seeeeng vhet is heppeneeng under zee huud).</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="34" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included blocks with the AuthURL Module</string>
		<translation>Zeere-a ere-a nu inclooded blucks veet zee OothOoRL Mudoole</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="43" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Extended inffurmeshun ebuoot thees mudoole-a cun be-a fuoond here-a. [mudooles mudoole-a]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authurl/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="47" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
