<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="fi_FI.utf-8">
<entry><string>Related documentation on Blocks</string><translation>Lohkoihin liittyvää dokumentaatiota</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Blocks Module - Xaraya Extension 13</string><translation>Lohkot-moduuli - Xarayan laajennus 13</translation></entry>
<entry><string>official icon</string><translation>virallinen kuvake</translation></entry>
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Mikä tämä on?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Blocks Module controls the configuration, display position and grouping of 'blocks'
of content or functionality on your website. From version 1.1.2, the Blocks module also can control access and levels of accessto blocks. The Blocks module is a core module within Xaraya and cannot be removed.</string><translation>Lohkot-moduulilla hallitaan sivustollasi näkyvien 'lohkojen' asetuksia, näkyvyyttä, järjestystä ja ryhmittelyä. 'Lohkon' sisällä voi olla sivustollasi näytettävää sisältöä tai se voi suorittaan jonkin toiminnon. Versiosta 1.1.2 lähtien Lohkot-moduulissa voidaan määritellä myös lohkojen valtuuksia. Lohkot-moduuli on Xarayan ydinmoduuli eikä sitä voida poistaa.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Miten tätä käytetään?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Each module can provide a block type along with the code and templates for it. A block type defines a specific display
of content or functionality that you can place on your site. For example the Articles module provides a 'featured article' block type,
and a 'top items' block type. The Base module provides a 'menu' block type, among others.</string><translation>Jokainen moduuli voi sisältää lohkotyypin, sekä sen koodin ja mallineen. Lohkotyyppi määrittelee sivustollasi näytettävän sisällön tai toiminnallisuuden. Esimerkiksi, Artikkelit-moduuli sisältää lohkotyypit 'valitut artikkelit' ja 'suosituimmat'. Pohja-moduuli puolestaan sisältää mm. 'valikko'-lohkotyypin.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>These different block types are installed at the time of module installation, and removed when a module is uninstalled.
The block types are also upgraded when a module is upgraded.</string><translation>Nämä eri lohkotyypit asennetaan moduulin asennusvaiheessa ja poistetaan kun moduulin asennus poistetaan.  Moduulia päivitettäessä myös lohkotyypit päivitetään.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Blocks module enables you to work with &lt;strong&gt;Block Types&lt;/strong&gt; to:</string><translation>Lohkot-moduulissa tehtävät toiminnot &lt;strong&gt;lohkotyypeille&lt;/strong&gt;:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;View Block Types:&lt;/strong&gt;</string><translation>&lt;strong&gt;Näytä lohkotyypit:&lt;/strong&gt;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>lists all the registered block types in your Xaraya installation with reference to which
module they belong.</string><translation>listaa Xaraya-asennuksesi kaikki rekisteröidyt lohkotyypit sekä näyttää mihin moduulin ne kuuluvat.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Add a New Block Type:&lt;/strong&gt;</string><translation>&lt;strong&gt;Lisää uusi lohkotyyppi:&lt;/strong&gt;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>scans a module for a new block type. This option is added mainly for Developer convenience.
Sometimes a developer provides a block type or upgrade of a block outside of a normal module release or
upgrade. This option allows the block to be loaded and registered in your Xaraya installation. Normally
you should never need to use this option in the process of administering your site.</string><translation>skanna moduulin uusien lohkotyyppien varalta. Tämä toiminto on lähinnä kehitystyön helpottamiseksi. Joskus kehittäjä luo lohkotyypin moduulin julkaisun tai päivityksen ulkopuolella. Tällä toiminnolla voit ladata uuden lohkotyypin Xaraya-asennukseesi. Tätä toimintoa ei tarvita yleensä normaalissa sivuston ylläpitoprosessissa.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Using Blocks and Block Groups</string><translation>Lohkojen ja lohkoryhmien käyttäminen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are a number of steps required to create a new block of content or functionality for your site, and display it:</string><translation>Ennen kuin voit luoda ja näyttää uuden lohkon sivustollasi, sinun täytyy käydä läpi seuraavat vaiheet:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Create a new block instance based on any of your installed block types</string><translation>Luo uusi lohkoinstanssi mistä tahansa asennetusta lohkotyypistä.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Assign the block instance to an existing block group during block creation or modification (optional)</string><translation>Sijoita lohkoinstanssi olemassa olevaan lohkoryhmään. Voit tehdä tämän luodessasi tai muokatessasi lohkoa. (valinnainen)</translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you need a new block group, create one and then assign the block instance to it</string><translation>Jos tarvitset uuden lohkoryhmän, luo se ja sijoita lohkoinstanssi siihen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add a &lt;strong&gt;blockgroup tag&lt;/strong&gt; in your theme template so Xaraya knows where to display your blocks. eg
&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;xar:blockgroup name=&quot;right&quot; id=&quot;right&quot; /&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.</string><translation>Lisää &lt;strong&gt;blockgroup-tagi&lt;/strong&gt; teemasi mallineeseen, jotta Xaraya tietää missä haluat näyttää lohkosi. Esim. &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;xar:blockgroup name=&quot;right&quot; id=&quot;right&quot; /&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya has pre-configured block groups created at installation time that include &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt;,
&lt;em&gt;left&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;center&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;topnav&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;header&lt;/em&gt; block groups. Special block group tags are used in the default Xaraya theme to
place and display them and the block instances already assigned to them. In the case of the default block groups
their name reflects the position where they are located in the default theme. You can rename these block groups as the names are not significant in themselves</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Note: you do not have to allocated a block instance to a blockgroup. You can place the block instance display directly
into your theme templates using a &lt;strong&gt;block&lt;/strong&gt; tag. Please check &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;RFC0010&lt;/a&gt; for details on using this tag.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Creating and Viewing Block Groups</string><translation>Lohkoryhmien luonti ja  näyttäminen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Blocks module provides a number of options to work with &lt;strong&gt;Block Goups&lt;/strong&gt;:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;View Block Groups:&lt;/strong&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>displays all the defined Block Groups on your site with links to Edit or Delete options</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Add Block Group:&lt;/strong&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>option presents a simple input screen so you can add a new block group</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Creating, Viewing and Modifying Block Instances</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Creating and modifying block instances with Xaraya is simple:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;View Block Instances:&lt;/strong&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>displays all current block instances that are available for use in your Xaraya site. From this menu option
you can &lt;code&gt;modify&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;delete&lt;/code&gt; any of the listed block instances.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Add New Block Instance:&lt;/strong&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Create and make available a new block instance for display on your site. As part of this process you
may nominate which block type to use for creation of the block instance, and optionally assign the block instance to a Block Group.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Modify a Block Instance:&lt;/strong&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>from the View Block Instance listing provides the option to allocate the block instance
to one or more Block Groups. In addition, you can optionally specify whether the block instances should use an
override block instance (inner) template or block group (outer) template (see Templating Blocks and Block Groups). Each module also specifies any special content here that is available for configuration for this specific block type.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Templating Blocks and Block Groups</string><translation>Lohkojen ja lohkoryhmien mallineet</translation></entry>
<entry><string>As with other Xaraya content, you can provide your own override templates for block
instances and create your own templates for block groups. To do this note the following:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Inner template&lt;/strong&gt; is used for display of the content in a block instance and
supplied by the module that provides the block type. They can be overridden like any other Xaraya template.
Overrides for for block instance &lt;strong&gt;inner&lt;/strong&gt; templates should be be placed in
&lt;code&gt;themes/[yourtheme]/modules/[themodule]/blocks&lt;/code&gt; where &lt;code&gt;[themodule]&lt;/code&gt; is the module providing
the block type. The general name for the template is &lt;code&gt;blocktype-innertemplatename.xt&lt;/code&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt; Outer template&lt;/strong&gt; is the name given to the template used for the block instance's block group.
Some 'outer' templates are installed by default with Xaraya, but you can also create your own 'outer'
templates. The &lt;strong&gt;outer templates&lt;/strong&gt; are stored in your &lt;code&gt;theme/[yourtheme]/blocks&lt;/code&gt;
directory. If there is no specific block group template the block group will use the preinstalled 'default'
block group template.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to tell Xaraya which inner and outer templates to use</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can tell Xaraya which inner and outer templates to use when you create a
new block instance or modify an existing one. Using the Blocks module, there are two places you can set either the inner
template, the outer template or both.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The field labelled &lt;strong&gt;Instance Template (optional):&lt;/strong&gt; sets the default
inner and outer template used for the block instance and any block group. You can specify inner, outer, both inner and outer or none.
You use the following format: &lt;code&gt;[outer-template][semi-colon][inner-template]&lt;/code&gt;. Both are specified without the file extension.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you add a block instance to a block group, another input field will appear, labelled with the name of the block group.
You can also add a specific inner, outer or both inner and outer template in this field using the same syntax. Specifying
an inner or outer template in this block group template field will override any other templates.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;An example:&lt;/strong&gt; if you create an articles' featureditems block instance and you are using the Xaraya_Classic default theme</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>By default, this block instance will use the article module's inner template called &lt;code&gt;featureditems.xd&lt;/code&gt; located in modules/articles/xartemplates/blocks</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you have allocated the featured article block instance to a block group called 'right' it will use, by default, the outer template
located at &lt;code&gt;themes/Xaraya_Classic/blocks/right.xt&lt;/code&gt;. If the 'right' outer template did not exist it will use one called 'default.xt'
in that same directory.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you wish to override both outer and inner templates for the featureditems block then the syntax example of:
&lt;strong&gt;left;weeklyfeature&lt;/strong&gt; would mean means the outer template is one created and called &lt;code&gt;&lt;strong&gt;left&lt;/strong&gt;.xt&lt;/code&gt; in the &lt;code&gt;themes/Xaraya_Classic/blocks&lt;/code&gt; directory.
The article module's featureditems block instance will be displayed using the &lt;code&gt;themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/articles/blocks/featureditems-&lt;strong&gt;weeklyfeature&lt;/strong&gt;.xt&lt;/code&gt; template.
You could just specify outer or inner template if required by adding &lt;code&gt;left;&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;;weeklyfeature&lt;/code&gt; to specify outer and inner respectively.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Mukana tulevat lohkot</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Blocks Module has no blocks included at this time.</string><translation>Lohkot-moduulin mukana ei tule tällä hetkellä lohkoja.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Mukana tulevat koukut</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Blocks Module has no hooks included at this time.</string><translation>Lohkot-moduulin mukana ei tule tällä hetkellä koukkuja.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation>Lisätiedot</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the Blocks module can be found at</string><translation>Lisätietoja Lohkot-moduulista löydät seuraavilta sivuilta</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Blocks Module Extension page at &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot; title=&quot;#(2)&quot; &gt;Xaraya Extension and Releases&lt;/a&gt;.
Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation>Lohkot-moduulin laajennuksen kotisivu osoitteessa &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot; title=&quot;#(2)&quot; &gt;Xaraya Extension and Releases&lt;/a&gt;. Viimeisimmät laajennuksen julkaisutiedot saat esille napsauttamalla Version History -välilehteä.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on Blocks found at &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot; title=&quot;#(2)&quot;&gt;Xaraya Documentation.&lt;/a&gt;</string><translation>Aiheeseen liittyvät ohjeet ja dokumentaatio sijaitsevat &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot; title=&quot;#(2)&quot;&gt;Xarayan dokumentaatiossa&lt;/a&gt;.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Blocks Module Overview</string><translation>Lohkot-moduulin yleiskatsaus</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation>Versio</translation></entry>
</translations>
