<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="de_DE.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>The base module provides you with configuration and informational options in the Administration menu, as well as additional functionality through use of its templates and blocks.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="19" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Administration menu is key to controlling global functionality on your site and includes:</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="24" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extension Releases: View recently releasedextensions from the xaraya.com Extension and Release RSS feed.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Cookie settings, and other defaults such as WYWIWYG editor</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Custom Templates</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="58" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Base Module provides a number of custom tags that can be used by theme creators and module developers to incorporate javascript into templates. These include the &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;xar:base-render-javascript ... /&amp;gt;, &amp;lt;xar:base-include-javascript ... /&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;xar:base-trigger-javascript ... /&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tags. See the documentation for more information.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya is currently in Beta Production. If you notice any unexpected functionality, please use our bug tracker at &lt;a href=&quot;http://bugs.xaraya.com&quot;&gt;http://bugs.xaraya.com&lt;/a&gt;. Thank you for your support, and feel free to join our development or user discussions to become involved in our community.</string>
		<translation>Xaraya ist aktuell im Beta-Entwicklungsstadium. Wenn Sie eine unerwartete Funktionalität bemerken, melden Sie diese bitte bei unserem Bugtracker auf &lt;a href=&quot;http://bugs.xaraya.com&quot;&gt;http://bugs.xaraya.com&lt;/a&gt;. Wir danken Ihnen für Ihre Unterstützung. Beteiligen Sie sich auch an der Entwickler- bzw. Nutzerdiskussion und werden so Teil unserer Gemeinschaft.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="10" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
