<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="4" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="14" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The mail module controls the ways that your Xaraya system sends mail to users or groups of users.  This module is a utility module and takes information from other modules installed on your Xaraya system and formats the mail for them.  This module at its heart is using the</string>
		<translation>Zee meeel mudoole-a cuntruls zee veys thet yuoor Xereya system sends meeel tu users oor gruoops ooff users. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Thees mudoole-a is a uteelity mudoole-a und tekes inffurmeshun frum oozeer mudooles instelled oon yuoor Xereya system und furmets zee meeel fur zeem. Thees mudoole-a et its heert is useeng zee</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>phpmailer</string>
		<translation>phpmeeeler</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>classes for processing.  These classes extend Xaraya to allow you to use SMTP, SendMail or the normal PHP Mail functions.</string>
		<translation>clesses fur prucesseeng. Zeese-a clesses ixtend Xereya tu elloo yuoo tu use-a SMTP, SendMeeel oor zee nurmel PHP Meeel fooncshuns. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have two choices.</string>
		<translation>Frum zee menoo, yuoo hefe-a tvu chueeces. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&quot;Modify Configuration&quot;.  From this menu option, you can update the necessary configuration options, such as the email address that you want to send from, reply to address, type of mail system to use, etc.</string>
		<translation>&quot;Mudeeffy Cunffeegooreshun&quot;. Frum thees menoo oopshun, yuoo cun updete-a zee necessery cunffeegooreshun oopshuns, sooch es zee imeeel eddress thet yuoo vunt tu send frum, reply tu eddress, type-a ooff meeel system tu use-a, itc.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="24" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&quot;Test Configuration&quot;.  From this menu option you can test your mail system configuration.</string>
		<translation>&quot;Test Cunffeegooreshun&quot;. Frum thees menoo oopshun yuoo cun test yuoor meeel system cunffeegooreshun.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Scheduling mail</string>
		<translation>Schedooleeng meeel</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Other modules can request that a certain mail be sent no earlier than a specific time.</string>
		<translation>Ozeer mudooles cun reqooest thet a certeeen meeel be-a sent nu ierleeer thun a speceeffic teeme-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This will have no effect unless you install the 'scheduler' module first.</string>
		<translation>Thees veell hefe-a nu iffffect unless yuoo instell zee 'schedooler' mudoole-a furst. Um de hur de hur de hur.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>In order to support that, you can configure the mail module to use the 'scheduler' and check if any mails need to be sent e.g. every x hours. Otherwise, those mails will be sent immediately.</string>
		<translation>In oorder tu sooppurt thet, yuoo cun cunffeegoore-a zee meeel mudoole-a tu use-a zee 'schedooler' und check iff uny meeels need tu be-a sent i.g. ifery x huoors. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Oozeerveese-a, thuse-a meeels veell be-a sent immedeeetely. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Mail Module has no blocks included at this time.</string>
		<translation>Zee Meeel Mudoole-a hes nu blucks inclooded et thees teeme-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="43" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="46" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The mail hook allows you to send an email to the site admin when something (content, users, etc) is created or deleted.  This can be configured in the modules module.</string>
		<translation>Zee meeel huuk elloos yuoo tu send un imeeel tu zee seete-a edmeen vhee sumetheeng (cuntent, users, itc) is creeted oor deleted. Bork bork bork! Thees cun be-a cunffeegoored in zee mudooles mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="49" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Extended inffurmeshun ebuoot thees mudoole-a cun be-a fuoond here-a. [mudooles mudoole-a]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="52" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
