<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
<entry><string>No Feed Url Specified</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Problem with supplied feed</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Administration - Headlines</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Headlines module allows you to syndicate content from other website. It also allows you to use predetermined hooks from Xaraya if you have them installed and activated.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>From the menu, you have three choices. &quot;Modify Configuration&quot;, &quot;Add Headlines&quot;, and &quot;View Headlines&quot;.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modify Configuration -- Allows you to update the global configuration for the module.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>View Headlines -- Allows you to view, edit and delete headlines that you have active for your site.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add Headlines -- Allows you to add a new syndication headline for processing.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>rss</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no included hooks</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>feedParser was created due to the lack of a good, flexible, class-based RSS feed parser for PHP. It has been built as a class, and currently handles RSS 0.91, RSS 0.92, RSS 0.93, RSS 1.0, and RSS 2.0 feeds. For channels it grabs the title, description, link, and creator. For items it grabs the title, description, link, and date. It also provides a form of the date converted into the local timezone to facilitate cronological sorting of items. The dates are provided in UNIX timestamp format for easy manipulation by other PHP functions.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can change the order of the feeds to be displayed on individual category pages.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Number of items per page to show.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Show short urls for the headlines.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Latest Headlines</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Import Headlines to News Queue</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>No Headlines in database, please add a site.</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
