<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
<entry><string>Reset</string><translation>Καθαρισμός</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Administration - Headlines</string><translation>Διαχείριση - Επικεφαλίδες</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Headlines module allows you to syndicate content from other website. It also allows you to use predetermined hooks from Xaraya if you have them installed and activated.</string><translation>Η μονάδα Επικεφαλίδες επιτρέπει την εμφάνιση περιεχομένου από άλλα website. Επίσης επιτρέπει την χρήση προκαθορισμένων hooks του Xaraya, αν αυτά έχουν εγκατασταθεί και ενεργοποιηθεί</translation></entry>
<entry><string>From the menu, you have three choices. &quot;Modify Configuration&quot;, &quot;Add Headlines&quot;, and &quot;View Headlines&quot;.</string><translation>Από το menu έχετε τρείς επιλογές. &quot;Τροποποίηση Ρυθμίσεων&quot;, &quot;Προσθήκη Επικεφαλίδων&quot; και &quot;Εμφάνιση Επικεφαλίδων&quot;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modify Configuration -- Allows you to update the global configuration for the module.</string><translation>Τροποποίηση Ρυθμίσεων -- Επιτρέπει την αλλαγή των καθολικών ρυθμίσεων της μονάδας.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>View Headlines -- Allows you to view, edit and delete headlines that you have active for your site.</string><translation>Εμφάνιση Επικεφαλίδων -- Επιτρέπει την εμφάνιση, τροποποίηση και διαγραφή επικεφαλίδων τις οποίες έχετε ενεργοποιήσει για το site.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add Headlines -- Allows you to add a new syndication headline for processing.</string><translation>Προσθήκη Επικεφαλίδων -- Επιτρέπει την προσθήκη μιας νέας επικεφαλίδας syndication για επεξεργασία</translation></entry>
<entry><string>rss</string><translation>rss</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no included hooks</string><translation>Δεν συμπεριλαμβάνονται hooks</translation></entry>
<entry><string>feedParser was created due to the lack of a good, flexible, class-based RSS feed parser for PHP. It has been built as a class, and currently handles RSS 0.91, RSS 0.92, RSS 0.93, RSS 1.0, and RSS 2.0 feeds. For channels it grabs the title, description, link, and creator. For items it grabs the title, description, link, and date. It also provides a form of the date converted into the local timezone to facilitate cronological sorting of items. The dates are provided in UNIX timestamp format for easy manipulation by other PHP functions.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Latest Headlines</string><translation>Τελευταίες Επικεφαλίδες</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Import Headlines to News Queue</string><translation>Εισαγωγή Επικεφαλίδων στην Ουρά Νέων</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Source</string><translation>Πηγή</translation></entry>
<entry><string>RSS File URL:</string><translation>URL αρχείου RSS:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Max Headlines to display</string><translation>Μέγιστος αριθμός Επικεφαλίδων για εμφάνιση</translation></entry>
</translations>
