<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Τι είναι;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Uploads is a Xaraya Utility Module.</string><translation>Το Uploads είναι μία Βοηθητική Μονάδα του Xaraya</translation></entry>
<entry><string>It is currently responsible for accomplishing these tasks:</string><translation>Αυτή τη στιγμή είναι υπέυθυνη για την πραγματοποίηση αυτών των εργασιών:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Allows for the importing of files into the Xaraya system either locally or externally.</string><translation>Επιτρέπει την εισαγωγή αρχείων στο σύστημα του Xaraya είτε τοπικά είτε εξωτερικά.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Allows the managing of access to files via privileges.</string><translation>Επιτρέπει την διαχείριση της πρόσβασης στα αρχεία μέσω προνομίων.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Πως χρησιμοποιείται;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>External Imports and Uploads</string><translation>Εξωτερικές Εισαγωγές και Διαβιβάσεις</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Files that are uploaded or imported from external locations can be saved in the database (DB)
or stored in the filesystem (FS). Use the options (FS/DB) under each form to select the
storage location for your file.</string><translation>Τα αρχεία που διαβιβάζονται ή εισάγωνται από εξωτερικές τοποθεσίες μπορούν να αποθηκευθούν στη βάση δεδομένων (ΒΔ) ή στο σύστημα αρχείων (ΣΑ). Χρησιμοποιείστε τις επιλογές (ΒΔ/ΣΑ) σε κάθε φόρμα για να διαλέξετε την τοποθεσία αποθήκευσης του αρχείο σας.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The import engine will try to make a best guess for the name of the file you are trying to import.
In the event that it cannot figure out what the file name is it will use the following methods:</string><translation>Η μηχανή εισαγωγής θα προσπαθήσει να κάνει την καλύτερη δυνατή εικασία για το όνομα του αρχείου που προσπαθείτε να εισάγετε. Στην περίπτωση που δεν μπορέσει να βρεί το όνομα του αρχείου θα χρησιμοποιήσει τις παρακάτω μεθόδους.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;HTTP and HTTPS&lt;/strong&gt;</string><translation>&lt;strong&gt;HTTP και HTTPS&lt;/strong&gt;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>In the event that the filename for an HTTP import can not be determined, the file will be
named based on the host name of the server the file was imported from. For example, importing
http://www.xaraya.com/ would return a file with the name of www_xaraya_com.html</string><translation>Στην περίπτωση που το όνομα αρχείου για εισαγωγή από HTTP δεν μπορεί να καθοριστεί, το αρχείο θα ονομαστεί με βάση το όνομα του διακομιστή από τον οποίο το αρχείο εισάγεται. Για παράδειγμα, εισάγωντας το http://www.xaraya.com/ θα επιστρέψει ένα αρχείο με όνομα www_xaraya_com.html</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Due to the underlying nature of the FTP protocol, it is impossible to successfully access a file
on a system without providing a viable file name. In this case, no file name 'guessing' will be
attempted and the import will fail.</string><translation>Λόγω της φύσης του προτοκόλλου FTP, είναι αδύνατη η επιτυχής πρόσβαση σε ένα σύστημα χωρίς την παροχή ενός βατού ονόματος αρχείου. Σε αυτή την περίπτωση, δεν γίνεται προπάθεια μαντέματος του ονόματος του αρχείου και η εισαγωγή θα αποτύχει.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Local Imports Sandbox</string><translation>Αμμοδοχείο Τοπικών Εισαγωγών</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Files can be inserted into your local import sandbox and used immediately by users with sufficient access to
add files and attach them to hooked objects (articles, comments, etc). Files you place in your local import
sandbox can be seen in the 'Import Local Files' form immediately upon adding them.</string><translation>Τα αρχεία μπορούν να προστεθούν στο αμμοδοχείο τοπικών εισαγωγών και να χρησιμοποιηθούν άμεσα από χρήστες με επαρκή πρόσβαση να τα προσθέσουν και να τα επισυνάψουν σε αναρτημένα (hooked) αντικείμενα (άρθρα, σχόλια, κλπ). Τα αρχεία που τοποθετούνται στο αμμοδοχείο τοπικών εισαγωγών είναι ορατά από τη φόρμα 'Εισαγωγή Τοπικών Αρχείων' αμέσως μετά την προσθήκη τους.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Privileges</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Uploads has the following privilege levels:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>A role needs the ViewUploads privilege to view a file that has been uploaded and approved by the admin/editor.
If the file has not been approved, but submitted, the Edit privilege is needed to access the file.
You can use the autoapprove option to automatically approve all files uploaded by a certain user.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Περιλαμβανόμενα Blocks</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no included blocks.</string><translation>Δεν υπάρχουν περιλαμβανόμενα blocks.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Περιλαμαβανόμενα Hooks</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Uploads module does provide a transform hook. You can activate the uploads hook for a module or itemtype by going to</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modules - Configure Hooks - Uploads Module</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>From there check the radio buttons next to the modules and itemtypes where you wish to activate the uploads module hooks.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you combine the hook with the upload property, then you can add parameters to the dynamic property. Set the options with:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>This option will allow for a single upload, with external, uploaded and stored files, but not trusted ones. The basedir to look for stored files is the user dir, and new files will be placed there as well.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the Uploads module can be found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Uploads Extension page at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Uploads Module - Xaraya Extension 666</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on Uploads found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on Uploads</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
