<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
<entry><string>Modify Uploads Configuration</string><translation>Τροποίηση Ρυθμίσεων Uploads</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Upload Options</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Full path to your upload directory</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Uploads Directory</string><translation>Κατάλογος Uploads</translation></entry>
<entry><string>This is the full path to the directory where uploaded and external import files will be placed.
It is stronly recommended that this directory be located outside of your web directory.
&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: This directory MUST be writable by the webserver.</string><translation>Αυτή είναι η πλήρης διαδρομή στον κατάλογο που θα τοποθετούνται τα διαβιβασμένα και εξωτερικά εισηγμένα αρχεία. Συνίσταται έντονα αυτός ο κατάλογος να τοποθετηθεί εκτός του web καταλόγου. &lt;br /&gt;ΣΗΜΕΙΩΣΗ: Αυτός ο κατάλογος ΠΡΕΠΕΙ να είναι εγγράψιμος από τον διακομιστή web.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Full path to the local trusted directory</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Trusted Directory:</string><translation>Έμπιστος Κατάλογος:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>This is the full path to the local trusted directory. Files located in this directory will
be immediately available for users to attach to other objects (ie: articles). Files in this directory
are &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; counted in the disk usage summary totals. It is strongly recommended
that this directory be located outside of your web directory.
&lt;br /&gt;NOTE: This directory MUST be readable and should also be writable by the webserver.</string><translation>Αυτή είναι η πλήρης διαδρομή στον τοπικό έμπιστο κατάλογο. Το αρχεία που τοποθετούνται σε αυτόν τον κατάλογο θα είναι άμεσα διαθέσιμα στους χρήστες για να τα επισυνάψουν σε άλλα αντικείμενα (π.χ. άρθρα). Τα αρχεία αυτού του καταλόγου &lt;strong&gt;δεν&lt;/strong&gt; καταμετρούνται στα περιληπτικά σύνολα χρήσης του δίσκου. Συνίσταται έντονα αυτός ο κατάλογος να τοποθετηθεί εκτός του web καταλόγου. &lt;br /&gt;ΣΗΜΕΙΩΣΗ: Αυτός ο κατάλογος ΠΡΕΠΕΙ να είναι εγγράψιμος από τον διακομιστή web.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Auto approve files</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Maximum Upload Size :</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>This is the maximum size an uploaded file may be.&lt;br /&gt;
NOTE: The server wide PHP setting, if set to a lower value, &lt;em&gt;will&lt;/em&gt; override this setting.
Please ask your web host provider for details on the settings that they use for uploaded files.</string><translation>Αυτό είναι το μέγιστο μέγεθος αρχείου για ένα διαβιβασμένο αρχειο.&lt;br /&gt;ΣΗΜΕΙΩΣΗ: Η γενική ρύθμιση PHP για τον διακομιστή, αν τεθεί σε μία μικρότερη αξία, &lt;em&gt;θα&lt;/em&gt; υπερισχύσει αυτής της ρύθμισης. Παρακαλούμε ζητήστε από τον πάροχο φιλοξενίας πληροφορίες για τις ρυθμίσεις που χρησιμοποιεί για την μεταφόρτωση αρχείων.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Auto approve files added by:</string><translation>Αυτόματη έγκριση διαβιβασμένων αρχείων από:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>No one</string><translation>Κανένα</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Everyone</string><translation>Οποιονδήποτε</translation></entry>
<entry><string>This option allows you to make all newly added files' status set to approved for Everyone (not recommended), Admins only, or No One.</string><translation>Αυτή η επιλογή σας επιτρέπει να καθορίσετε την κατάσταση όλων των νέων αρχείων ώς εγκεκριμένα για Οποιονδήποτε (δεν συνίσταται), για τους Διαχειριστές ή για Κανένα.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Confirm deletion of files</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Confirm deletion of files:</string><translation>Επιβεβαίωση διαγραφής των αρχείων:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Yes</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>No</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Confirmation must be provided before files are deleted.</string><translation>Πρέπει να δωθεί επιβεβαίωση πριν την διαγραφή των αρχείων.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Auto purge files marked as rejected</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Auto purge 'rejected' files:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Normally, when you reject files, you have to manually purge them by clicking on
the 'Purge Rejected' button located on the &lt;em&gt;Admin-&gt;Uploads-&gt;View page&lt;/em&gt;. This
option forces any file you set to 'rejected' status to be deleted right away.</string><translation>Κανονικά, όταν απορρίπτετε αρχεία, πρέπει να κάνετε χρειρωνακτικά εκκαθάριση επιλέγοντας το κουμπί 'Εκκαθάριση Αποριφθέντων' στη σελίδα &lt;em&gt;Διαχείριση-&gt;Μεταφοτρώσεις-&gt;Προβολή&lt;/em&gt;. Αυτή η επιλογή επιβάλλει την άμεση διαγραφή των απορριφθέντων αρχείων.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Obfuscate/Secure Imported Files</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Secure Imported Files:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>If Yes, imported files will be stored with their original names obfuscated for added security.</string><translation>Αν καθοριστεί, τα εισηγμένα αρχεία θα αποθηκεύονται με τα αυθεντικά ονόματά τους συσκοτισμένα για πρόσθετη ασφάλεια.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Obfuscate/Secure Uploaded Files</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Secure Uploaded Files:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>If Yes, uploaded files will be stored with their original names obfuscated for added security.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong style=&quot;color: red;&quot;&gt;NOTE:&lt;/strong&gt;Setting this option to 'No' can open a possible route for users
to upload and run malicious scripts on your site. It is &lt;strong&gt;highly&lt;/strong&gt;
recommended that you leave this option on unless you have a thorough understanding
of the implications behind turning it off.</string><translation>Αν καθοριστεί, τα διαβιβασμένα αρχεία θα αποθηκεύονται με τα αυθεντικά ονόματά τους συσκοτισμένα για πρόσθετη ασφάλεια.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong style=&quot;color: red;&quot;&gt;ΣΗΜΕΙΩΣΗ:&lt;/strong&gt;Αν δεν καθοριστεί, μπορεί να ανοίξει για τους χρήστες ένα πιθανό δρόμο μεταφότωσης κακόβουλων εκτελέσιμων αρχείων στο site σαε. Είναι &lt;strong&gt;έντονα&lt;/strong&gt; προτεινόμενο να αφήσετε αυτή την επιλογή ενεργοποιημένη εκτός αν έχετε πλήρη κατανόηση των επιπλοκών πίσω από την απενεργοποίηση της.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Reaction to Duplicate Filenames</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Allow Duplicate Filenames?</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>No upload allowed</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Save as new version</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Replace original</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>For new version, files with the same name of existing files will be stored alongside the originals.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Cache trusted file information</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Cache trusted file information:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>seconds</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Items per page in admin view</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Items per page in admin view:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Dynamic File Upload Property Configuration</string><translation>Ρύθμιση Δυναμικής Ιδιότητας File Upload</translation></entry>
<entry><string>These settings allow you to redefine certain characteristics of the FileUpload DynamicData Property.
These settings only take effect if you have 'hooked' the uploads module to the module using the
FileUpload property.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select file sources for the FileUpload Property:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Note: be sure to choose at &lt;strong&gt;least&lt;/strong&gt; one!</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Files located in the Trusted directory</string><translation>Αρχεία τοποθετημένα στον Έμπιστο κατάλογο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Externally located files (http / ftp / file)</string><translation>Εξωτερικά αρχεία (http / ftp / file)</translation></entry>
<entry><string>User uploaded files</string><translation>Αρχεία διαβιβάσεων χρήστη</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Files previously stored</string><translation>Προηγουμένως αποθηκευμένα αρχεία</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Hook configuration for uploaded files</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>No hooks configured.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Configure hooks now</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
