<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
<entry><string>The Wizards module is a handy way of making advanced, specific Xaraya functionality available to your &lt;b&gt;users&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;admins&lt;/b&gt;. Wizards are a collection of simple &quot;one-click&quot; scripts, each of which performs a specific task.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Wizards let you take advantage of the entire Xaraya API and put that functionality at the disposal of your users in a flexible way you define and control.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Wixards are &lt;b&gt;extensible&lt;/b&gt;. The module comes with a number of predefined wizards, but you can easily create more.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can configure wizards to be available to your admins, users, or both.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>First, use the Modify Config menu option on the Wizards admin menu to define whether wizards will be available to users, admins or both.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The module comes with a predefined RunScripts privilege that allows access to the wizards. Assign this privilege to whatever user group that you want to give access to. (Note: Admins automatically have access to wizards if they are enabled.)</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The wizard scripts that appear on the user and admin menus of the module are located in /modules/wizards/xarwizards/admin and /modules/wizards/xarwizards/user respectively. Removing a script from its directory will remove it from the menu.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>By using the existing scripts as templates, you can create new wizards with your own chosen functionality and add them to either menu. A simple Example wizard script is included for this purpose.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>none.</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
