<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>The Newsletter module allows an individual or organization to compile and distribute news and research updates to interested parties via email.  This module gives writers, editors, and publishers a comprehensive process to easily assemble the stories for a newsletter and subsequently publish the information to a subscription base.</string>
		<translation>Zee Noosletter mudoole-a elloos un indeefidooel oor oorguneezeshun tu cumpeele-a und deestriboote-a noos und reseerch updetes tu interested perteees feea imeeel. Thees mudoole-a geefes vreeters, ideeturs, und poobleeshers a cumprehenseefe-a prucess tu ieseely essemble-a zee stureees fur a noosletter und soobseqooently poobleesh zee inffurmeshun tu a soobscreepshun bese-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt;  This overview is focused on the administrative tasks that must be performed before a publication can be created.  For an overview of Newsletter, please refer to the overview in the main menu.</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;Nute-a:&lt;/b&gt; Thees ooferfeeoo is fucoosed oon zee edmeenistretife-a tesks thet moost be-a perffurmed beffure-a a poobleeceshun cun be-a creeted. Fur un ooferfeeoo ooff Noosletter, pleese-a reffer tu zee ooferfeeoo in zee meeen menu. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>As the module administrator, you will need to complete the following steps before you can start using the Newsletter module:</string>
		<translation>Es zee mudoole-a edmeenistretur, yuoo veell need tu cumplete-a zee fullooeeng steps beffure-a yuoo cun stert useeng zee Noosletter mudoole-a:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>1.  Configure Roles and Privileges</string>
		<translation>1. Cunffeegoore-a Rules und Preefileges</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="41" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>As the module administrator, you must configure the necessary roles and privileges for the Newsletter publishers, editors and writers.  You can create the groups and privileges manually or can you use the administration modify configuration menu to easily create the default groups and privileges.  After these groups and privileges have been created, you can then add a user to the publisher, editor or writer group.</string>
		<translation>Es zee mudoole-a edmeenistretur, yuoo moost cunffeegoore-a zee necessery rules und preefileges fur zee Noosletter poobleeshers, ideeturs und vreeters. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Yuoo cun creete-a zee gruoops und preefileges munooelly oor cun yuoo use-a zee edmeenistreshun mudeeffy cunffeegooreshun menoo tu ieseely creete-a zee deffoolt gruoops und preefileges. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Effter zeese-a gruoops und preefileges hefe-a beee creeted, yuoo cun zeen edd a user tu zee poobleesher, ideetur oor vreeter gruoop.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="43" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>To add the groups and privileges, select Modify Config from the Newsletter administration menu followed by the Modify Privileges tab.  By default, the groups are assigned to the Everybody role.  You can select the default groups and privileges to be created or you can set which role to assign these groups and change the default privilege for each group.</string>
		<translation>Tu edd zee gruoops und preefileges, select Mudeeffy Cunffeeg frum zee Noosletter edmeenistreshun menoo fullooed by zee Mudeeffy Preefileges teb. By deffoolt, zee gruoops ere-a esseegned tu zee Iferybudy rule-a. Yuoo cun select zee deffoolt gruoops und preefileges tu be-a creeted oor yuoo cun set vheech rule-a tu esseegn zeese-a gruoops und chunge-a zee deffoolt preefilege-a fur iech gruoop.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="45" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;NewsletterPublisher&lt;/b&gt; (AdminNewsletter privilege)</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;NoosletterPoobleesher&lt;/b&gt; (EdmeenNoosletter preefilege-a)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="49" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;NewsletterEditor&lt;/b&gt; (DeleteNewsletter privilege)</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;NoosletterEdeetur&lt;/b&gt; (DeleteNoosletter preefilege-a)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="52" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;NewsletterWriter&lt;/b&gt; (AddNewsletter privilege)</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;NoosletterVreeter&lt;/b&gt; (EddNoosletter preefilege-a)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Once the groups and privileges are created, you do not need to modify the privileges again unless you want to change the privilege of a group.</string>
		<translation>Once-a zee gruoops und preefileges ere-a creeted, yuoo du nut need tu mudeeffy zee preefileges egeeen unless yuoo vunt tu chunge-a zee preefilege-a ooff a gruoop.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="59" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.  Add a Newsletter user</string>
		<translation>2. Edd a Noosletter user</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="63" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>After the Newsletter groups and privileges have been successfully created, you can add users to these groups.  Select the Modify Users tab from the Modify Config administrative menu.  This will display a list of currently assigned users and allow you to add a new user.  Select the user to add and the group that the user will inherit privileges from.  Once a user has been added to the appropriate group, that user will have writer, editor or publisher privileges and will be able to start creating content for a publication.</string>
		<translation>Effter zee Noosletter gruoops und preefileges hefe-a beee sooccessffoolly creeted, yuoo cun edd users tu zeese-a gruoops. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Select zee Mudeeffy Users teb frum zee Mudeeffy Cunffeeg edmeenistretife-a menu. Thees veell deespley a leest ooff coorrently esseegned users und elloo yuoo tu edd a noo user. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! Select zee user tu edd und zee gruoop thet zee user veell inhereet preefileges frum. Oonce-a a user hes beee edded tu zee epprupreeete-a gruoop, thet user veell hefe-a vreeter, ideetur oor poobleesher preefileges und veell be-a eble-a tu stert creeteeng cuntent fur a poobleeceshun.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt;  You will not be able to create a publication until at least one user is added to the Newsletter Publisher group.</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;Nute-a:&lt;/b&gt; Yuoo veell nut be-a eble-a tu creete-a a poobleeceshun unteel et leest oone-a user is edded tu zee Noosletter Poobleesher gruoop.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="67" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>3.  Add publication and story categories</string>
		<translation>3. Edd poobleeceshun und stury cetegureees</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="71" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>When the module is first activated, a category named &quot;Newsletter&quot; is created.  You must create sub-categories of this master category before a publication can be created.   Each sub-category of &quot;Newsletter&quot; will be a publication category.  Under each publication category, you will want to create another set of categories corresponding to the story categories for each publication.</string>
		<translation>Vhee zee mudoole-a is furst ecteefeted, a cetegury nemed &quot;Noosletter&quot; is creeted. Yuoo moost creete-a soob-cetegureees ooff thees mester cetegury beffure-a a poobleeceshun cun be-a creeted. Iech soob-cetegury ooff &quot;Noosletter&quot; veell be-a a poobleeceshun cetegury. Bork bork bork! Under iech poobleeceshun cetegury, yuoo veell vunt tu creete-a unuzeer set ooff cetegureees currespundeeng tu zee stury cetegureees fur iech poobleeceshun.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="73" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>For example:</string>
		<translation>Fur ixemple-a:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="75" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>master category</string>
		<translation>mester cetegury</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="81" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Learning Differences</string>
		<translation>Leerneeng Deefffferences</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="86" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>publication category</string>
		<translation>poobleeceshun cetegury</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="87" />
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="116" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>LD Experts in the News</string>
		<translation>LD Ixperts in zee Noos</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="92" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>story category</string>
		<translation>stury cetegury</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="93" />
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="99" />
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="105" />
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="111" />
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="122" />
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="128" />
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="134" />
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="140" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Education / Schools</string>
		<translation>Edooceshun / Schuuls</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="98" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Successful People</string>
		<translation>Sooccessffool Peuple</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="104" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Controversial Treatment</string>
		<translation>Cuntruferseeel Treetment</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="110" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Internet Technology</string>
		<translation>Internet Technulugy</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="115" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Design and Architecture</string>
		<translation>Deseegn und Ercheetectoore</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="121" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Emerging Technologies</string>
		<translation>Emergeeng Technulugeees</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="127" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Networks and Infrastructure</string>
		<translation>Netvurks und Inffrestrooctoore</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="133" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Standards and Practices</string>
		<translation>Stunderds und Precteeces</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="139" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt;  The stories within a publication will ordered in the same order as the story categories, so place the story categories accordingly.</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;Nute-a:&lt;/b&gt; Zee stureees veethin a poobleeceshun veell oordered in zee seme-a oorder es zee stury cetegureees, su plece-a zee stury cetegureees eccurdeengly. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="144" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="150" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The following blocks are included:</string>
		<translation>Zee fullooeeng blucks ere-a inclooded:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="154" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;information&lt;/b&gt; - This block provides the following:</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;eenffurmeshun&lt;/b&gt; - Thees bluck prufeedes zee fullooeeng:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="156" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>- General information about the publications that a user can subscribe to.  This information is created in the Newsletter user modify configuration screen in the text fields &quot;Publisher or Company Name&quot; and &quot;Information about Newsletter&quot;</string>
		<translation>- Generel inffurmeshun ebuoot zee poobleeceshuns thet a user cun soobscreebe-a tu. Thees inffurmeshun is creeted in zee Noosletter user mudeeffy cunffeegooreshun screee in zee text feeelds &quot;Poobleesher oor Cumpuny Neme-a&quot; und &quot;Inffurmeshun ebuoot Noosletter&quot;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="157" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>- Allows non-registered users to view past issues.</string>
		<translation>- Elloos nun-regeestered users tu feeoo pest issooes.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="158" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>- Allows logged in users to modify their subscription(s) to the publications.</string>
		<translation>- Elloos lugged in users tu mudeeffy zeeur soobscreepshun(s) tu zee poobleeceshuns. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="159" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="165" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Newsletter provides all the necessary hooks to be present within other modules.  But these hooks have not been thoroughly tested.</string>
		<translation>Noosletter prufeedes ell zee necessery huuks tu be-a present veethin oozeer mudooles. Boot zeese-a huuks hefe-a nut beee thuruooghly tested. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/newsletter/xartemplates/admin-configdesc.xd" line="169" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
