<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
<entry><string>How To Use It?</string><translation>Hoe te gebruiken?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You are about to delete a subscription.</string><translation>U gaat een inschrijving verwijderen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>(overrides publication default)</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Subscribe to a Newsletter</string><translation>Schrijf in voor een nieuwsbrief</translation></entry>
<entry><string>master category</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>- General information about the publications that a user can subscribe to. This information is created in the Newsletter user modify configuration screen in the text fields &quot;Publisher or Company Name&quot; and &quot;Information about Newsletter&quot;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>- Allows non-registered users to view past issues.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>- Allows logged in users to modify their subscription(s) to the publications.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You are about to delete a disclaimer.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You are about to delete an issue.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You are about to delete an Newsletter user.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Confirm removal of Newsletter user:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You are about to delete a publication.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You are about to delete a story.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Newsletter module allows an individual or organization to compile and distribute news and research updates to interested parties via email. This module gives writers, editors and publishers a comprehensive process to easily assemble the stories for an newsletter and subsequently publish the information to a subscription base.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;If you have not yet configured the module, please do so.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;b&gt;Default Groups&lt;/b&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>As a user of the Newsletter module, you will be added to either the publisher, editor or writer group. Once the module administrator has added you to one of these groups, you will be able to create content for a publication.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;b&gt;Publication Items&lt;/b&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>A publication is the top-level wrapper for each issue and sets default information for each issue and story within the issue.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Each publication should have a disclaimer or confidentiality clause. Once a disclaimer is created, it can be used by multiple publications.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>An issue contains the news and research updates that have been compiled as stories. Once the issue is ready to be published, the issue will be sent to the subscription base. After an issue has been published, it can be view by non-registered users from the Newsletter information block.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Each issue will have multiple stories relating to the news and research updates that will be presented to the subscription base.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>publication</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The admin or publisher should first update the module's configuration within the Newsletter &lt;i&gt;modify configuration&lt;/i&gt; before publishing an issue. If the Newsletter information block has been added, then the &lt;i&gt;Publisher or Company Name&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;Information&lt;/i&gt; fields will be displayed within the information block. &lt;i&gt;Information&lt;/i&gt; should contain a general description about the publications that are available to the subscription base.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add a signature block if you wish to include a signature in each issue. Do not include a user name in your signature block as this will be automatically included in the template. By default, the signature block will be displayed after your user name.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Each publication can have it's own HTML and text email template. To create a new template, you will need to copy one of the existing templates and modify the template for the desired appearance. A README file is included in the templates directory with the necessary information on creating a new template.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The default templates are located the directory &lt;i&gt;&quot;modules/newsletter/templates&quot;&lt;/i&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Either create a new publication or choose a publication that already exists. (publisher)</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can continue adding stories to the issue until you have finished and are ready to publish the issue.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select an issue to preview. The publication's HTML template will be used to display the issue.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;b&gt;Subscriptions&lt;/b&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Normally, a user cannot subscribe to a publication unless they are a registered user on your site. If the Newsletter information block has been added, then a registered user will be able to subscribe to a publication and modify their subscriptions.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you wish to add a subscription that is not a registered user, then you can add a subscription from the &lt;i&gt;add subscription&lt;/i&gt; menu. You will need to provide a user name and email address. This provides an alternative way of adding subscriptions to a publication for users that are not registered.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>From the main menu, you have the following choices based on your privileges:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;b&gt;Publication&lt;/b&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;b&gt;Field&lt;/b&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;b&gt;Description&lt;/b&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Active Users</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Send newsletter only to active users. This does not include alternative subscriptions.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Send to active users:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Short URL Support</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modify the following for display in the information block.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>(turn off to display by order of category id)</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you want to use the default groups and privileges for Newsletter, set the groups accordingly.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;firstname,lastname,email</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You are about to publish an issue.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Confirm publication of issue:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Show all subscriptions for a publication:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Search by name:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Search by email address:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Choose Publication:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select if you would like a publication received in HTML format.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select if you would like the Newsletter received in HTML format.</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
