<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Administration - Example</string>
		<translation>Edmeenistreshun - Ixemple</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="5" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="11" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This module allows you to create and display sub-items for any module item. In the words of the author :</string>
		<translation>Thees mudoole-a elloos yuoo tu creete-a und deespley soob-items fur uny mudoole-a item. In zee vurds ooff zee oothur :</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="15" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;p&gt;For example, if you want to have a pubtype &quot;cooking recipe&quot;. This 
pubtype could be to store the ingredients of the meal, thus there would 
be required a list of input fields: ingredient1, quantity1, 
pic1(extended info :-) ) , ingredient2, quantity2, pic2,...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The disadvantage of this is the high number of fields to ensure, that 
there your users aren't going against the limit. Furthermore there are 
always displayed all input fields. And of  course it's not a very nice 
way to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I didn't know how to do this better, I had a dream about a module, 
which can be hooked from any other module and which is able to display / 
provide editing / etc. for subitems to an item. I had a dream about a 
table, which saves the information, which DD-Object stores the subitems 
of &quot;module&quot; / &quot;itemtype&quot; combination and another table containing which 
DD-Itemids belong to &quot;module&quot; / &quot;itemtype&quot; / &quot;itemid&quot; in this DD-Object 
(1 to n Relation). I had the dream to share my module with the community.
Now, the module is here, and all dreams got true. If you didn't get my 
technical information, don't worry. &lt;/p&gt;</string>
		<translation>&lt;p&gt;Fur ixemple-a, iff yuoo vunt tu hefe-a a poobtype-a &quot;cuukeeng receepe-a&quot;. Thees poobtype-a cuoold be-a tu sture-a zee ingredeeents ooff zee meel, thoos zeere-a vuoold be-a reqooured a leest ooff inpoot feeelds: ingredeeent1, qoounteety1, peec1(ixtended inffu :-) ) , ingredeeent2, qoounteety2, peec2,...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Zee deesedfuntege-a ooff thees is zee heegh noomber ooff feeelds tu insoore-a, thet zeere-a yuoor users eren't gueeng egeeenst zee leemit. Um de hur de hur de hur. Foorzeermure-a zeere-a ere-a elveys deespleyed ell inpoot feeelds. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Und ooff cuoorse-a it's nut a fery neece-a vey tu du it. Um de hur de hur de hur.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Es I deedn't knoo hoo tu du thees better, I hed a dreem ebuoot a mudoole-a, vheech cun be-a huuked frum uny oozeer mudoole-a und vheech is eble-a tu deespley / prufeede-a ideeting / itc. fur soobeetems tu un item. I hed a dreem ebuoot a teble-a, vheech sefes zee inffurmeshun, vheech DD-Oobject stures zee soobeetems ooff &quot;mudoole-a&quot; / &quot;eetemtype-a&quot; cumbeeneshun und unuzeer teble-a cunteeening vheech DD-Itemeeds belung tu &quot;mudoole-a&quot; / &quot;eetemtype-a&quot; / &quot;eetemid&quot; in thees DD-Oobject (1 tu n Releshun). I hed zee dreem tu shere-a my mudoole-a veet zee cummooneety. Bork bork bork! Noo, zee mudoole-a is here-a, und ell dreems gut trooe-a. Iff yuoo deedn't get my techneecel inffurmeshun, dun't vurry. Bork bork bork! &lt;/p&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="34" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt; install module&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; goto dynamicdata admin area, new object, create a dynamic data object 
, which should hold the subitem information (you must have one field 
with the ItemID, default 0, display only) -&gt; remember the objectid, edit 
label (used for display) and name (used for custom default template)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; goto subitems module, admin area -&gt; add link -&gt; type in objectid (from 
previsously created dd-object), module name, itemtype&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt; goto module modules, hooks -&gt; subitems -&gt; enable the hook for the 
module /itemtype combination, you created the link for&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
-&gt; now it should work (tested with custom pubtype)</string>
		<translation>&lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt; instell mudoole-a&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; gutu dynemeecdeta edmeen erea, noo oobject, creete-a a dynemeec deta oobject , vheech shuoold huld zee soobeetem inffurmeshun (yuoo moost hefe-a oone-a feeeld veet zee ItemID, deffoolt 0, deespley oonly) -&gt; remeembur zee oobjecteed, ideet lebel (used fur deespley) und neme-a (used fur coostum deffoolt templete-a)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; gutu soobeetems mudoole-a, edmeen erea -&gt; edd leenk -&gt; type-a in oobjecteed (frum prefeesuoosly creeted dd-oobject), mudoole-a neme-a, itemtype-a&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; gutu mudoole-a mudooles, huuks -&gt; soobeetems -&gt; ineble-a zee huuk fur zee mudoole-a /itemtype-a cumbeeneshun, yuoo creeted zee leenk fur&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; -&gt; noo it shuoold vurk (tested veet coostum poobtype-a)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="59" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>none</string>
		<translation>nune</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="63" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="67" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>new/create/modify/update/delete -- Allows you to create/update sub-items</string>
		<translation>noo/creete-a/mudeeffy/updete-a/delete-a -- Elloos yuoo tu creete-a/updete-a soob-items</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="72" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>display -- Allows you to display sub-items</string>
		<translation>deespley -- Elloos yuoo tu deespley soob-items</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="73" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Extended inffurmeshun ebuoot thees mudoole-a cun be-a fuoond here-a. [mudooles mudoole-a]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/subitems/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="78" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
