<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="de_DE.utf-8">
<entry><string>Mailqueue definition needed</string><translation>Definition für die Mail-Warteschlange erforderlich</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-queue-newdef.xt" line="10"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>There seems to be no mailqueue definition yet, or the right object could not be found.</string><translation>Es scheint noch keine Definition für die Mail-Warteschlange zu geben oder dass richtige Objekt konnte nicht gefunden werden.</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-queue-newdef.xt" line="14"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>The mail module operates on mailqueues which are temporary stores for either outgoing or incoming mail items. Typically outgoing mail items are created (in outgoing queues obviously) for notifications or newsletters etc. Incoming mail items could be used to create an article or register a trouble ticket. In general the mail module handles the items in each queue defined and, based on the configuration of the mail module and the hook configuration passes the items on to something else.</string><translation>Das Mail-Modul funktioniert mit Mail-Warteschlange, die als temporäre Speicher für eingehende oder ausgehende Mail-Items. Normalerweise werden ausgehende Mail-Items</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-queue-newdef.xt" line="18"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>At this moment there does not seem to be an object which can hold our queue definitions. We need this to be able to continue for basically every operation in the mail module. This is the reason we are a bit verbose on this page.</string><translation>Zu diesem Zeitpunkt scheint es kein Objekt zu geben, welches Warteschlangen-Definitionen enthält. Wir benötigen dies für nahezu jegliche Funktion des Mail-Moduls. Das ist der Grund, warum wir auf dieser Seite etwas langatmig sind. </translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-queue-newdef.xt" line="22"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>Create object to hold queue definitions</string><translation>Objekt erstellen, welches die Warteschlange-Definitionen enthält</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-queue-newdef.xt" line="32"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>Queue definition name</string><translation>Definitionsname der Warteschlange</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-queue-newdef.xt" line="40"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>Create</string><translation>Erstellen</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-queue-newdef.xt" line="82"/>
		</references>
</entry>
</translations>
