<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="it_IT.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Che cos'&amp;egrave;?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="14" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Privileges module lets you manage &lt;b&gt;access rights&lt;/b&gt; on your site.  Privileges give roles access to certain resources of your choosing. They are the basic components of the security system.</string>
		<translation>Il modulo Privileges (privilegi) ti permettere di amministrare i &lt;b&gt; diritti di accesso&lt;/b&gt; sul tuo sito. Il modulo ti permette di assegnare l'accesso alle risorse del tuo sito a ciascun ruolo secondo la tua scelta. I privilegi sono una componente essenziale del sistema di sicurezza di Xaraya</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Here are some of the things you can do with privileges</string>
		<translation>Queste sono alcune cose che puoi fare con i privilegi</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="18" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya's privileges are extremely flexible. You can define privileges at the level of site, modules, component classes within modules, or single instances of those classes.</string>
		<translation>I privilegi di Xaraya sono estremamente flessibili. Puoi definire privilegi a livello di sito, modulo, classi di componenti del modulo, o singoli elementi di quelle classi</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can use privileges as building blocks. Assemble them into compound privileges tailored to any specific role on the site.</string>
		<translation>Puoi usare i privilegi come elementi da assemblare in privilegi multipli, disegnati per essere assegnati a qualsiasi ruolo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can assign privileges to roles which then pass them on to their children in the roles hierarchy through inheritance.</string>
		<translation>I privilegi assegnati a ciascun ruolo vengono trasferiti a tutti i ruoli discendenti di esso nella gerarchia dei ruoli definita attraverso l'albero ereditario dei ruoli</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="22" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Using the realms functionality you can subdivide one site into many &quot;virtual&quot; sites sharing the same resources.</string>
		<translation>Usando la componente &quot;domini&quot; dei privilegi, puoi dividere il sito in molti siti &quot;virtuali&quot; che condividono le stesse risorse</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Come usarlo?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Clicking on the View Privileges link gives you an overview of all the privileges on your system. Compound privileges are collapsed, but you can click on them to open them up and view their components.</string>
		<translation>Cliccando su &quot;Mostra Privilegi&quot; potrai vedere un sommario di tutti i privilegi definiti sul tuo sistema. Privilegi composti sono collassati, ma cliccando su di essi puoi vederne le loro componenti</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>When adding or modifying a privilege, you can define it to have its own access rights, or simply to serve as a container for other privileges</string>
		<translation>Quando aggiungi o modifichi un privilegio, puoi definirne i diritti di accesso, o semplicemente deinirne i privilegi che lo compongono</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="32" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya comes preconfigured with a minimal set of privileges that are loaded when you run the installer. These will vary according to the configuration you chose. Examples are</string>
		<translation>Xaraya viene installato con una preconfiguraizone minima di privilegi. Questo variano a seconda della configurazione che scegli in fase di installazione. Per esempio:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;Administration&lt;/b&gt;: a privilege that gives a role complete access to all resources on the site. At installation this privilege is assigned to the role Administrators and is inherited by the user Admin.</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;Administration&lt;/b&gt;: questo &amp;egrave; un privilegio che definisce accesso completo a tutte le risorse del sito. In fase di installazoine, questo privilegio &amp;egrave; assegnato al ruolo Amministratori e viene ereditato dall'utente che hai definito come amministratore nella fase di installazione</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;CasualAccess&lt;/b&gt;: this is the privilege assigned to unregistered users on the site. It is initially defined to allow viewing access of the front page, as well as access to the login block.</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;CasualAccess&lt;/b&gt;: questo privilegio viene assegnato agli utenti non registrati. Inizialmente, permette l'accesso al frontespizio del sito e al blocco login</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;GeneralLock&lt;/b&gt;: a privilege that restricts access to certain basic roles and privileges the system requires, such as the default admin. This is to avoid inadvertent removal.</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;GeneralLock&lt;/b&gt;: questo privilegio vieta l'accesso a certi ruoli e privilegi base richiesti dal sistema come l'amministrazione. Esiste per evitare l'eliminazione per errore di certe componenti.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="37" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>All privileges in the system can be changed or removed. (For those protected by GeneralLock above this takes a bit more doing.) You can also combine privileges by using them as elements to create compound privileges, or make new privileges of your choosing. There is no limit to the number of privileges you can create or their levels of nesting.</string>
		<translation>Tutti i privilegi possono essere cambiati o eliminati. (Per quelli protetti dal privilegio GeneralLock occorre un p&amp;ograve; di lavoro). Puoi anche combinare privilegi usandoli come elementi di un privilegio composto, o crearne di nuovi senza alcuna limitazione.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Blocchi inclusi</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included blocks</string>
		<translation>Non ci sono blocchi inclusi</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="45" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Agganci (hooks) inclusi</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="48" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included hooks.</string>
		<translation>Non ci sono agganci inclusi</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="51" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found in</string>
		<translation>Ulteriori informazioni su questo modulo possono essere trovate in</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="54" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
