<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="hu_HU.utf-8">
<entry><string>Thank you for installing Xaraya!</string><translation>Köszönjük, hogy a Xarayát választotta!</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Welcome to your new Xaraya Site</string><translation>Üdvözli a Xaraya</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You have successfully installed &lt;strong&gt;Xaraya Version #(1)&lt;/strong&gt;! You now have the tools
to easily build custom design and functionality into your web site. This installation provides some out of the box functionality
to get you started.</string><translation>A &lt;strong&gt;Xaraya #(1)&lt;/strong&gt; telepítése sikeresen befejeződött. így rendelkezésre állnak az eszközök, hogy könnyen elkészíthessük egyedi megjelenésű és funkcionalitású honlapunkat. Már a telepítés után elérhetőek az elinduláshoz szükséges alapvető lehetőségek.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The advantage of Xaraya is in it's flexibility and powerful Blocklayout theme system. These work together
enabling you to meet the most demanding of project specifications. Whether your requirements are
small business or a community site, a company intranet or multi-server web installation, you can feel confident
knowing that Xaraya not only provides the flexibility you need but key features of performance, stability, security, and ease of maintenance.</string><translation>A Xaraya előnyét rugalmassága és erőteljes BlockLayout grafikai sablonrendszere jelenti. Ezek együtt biztosítják, hogy tetszőleges igényeket kielégítő rendszert építhessünk. Legyen az egy kisebb cég bemutató oldala, komolyabb vállalati intranet vagy több szerveres weblap rendszer, biztosak lehetünk benne, hogy a Xaraya nem csak hogy biztosítja a szükséges rugalmasságot, de olyan fontos tulajdonságokat is, mint teljesítmény, stabilitás, biztonság és egyszerű karbantartás.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Getting started</string><translation>Első lépések</translation></entry>
<entry><string>In Xaraya, User and Group Roles and Privileges set by the site Administrator dictate what a user can and cannot see or do on the site.
If you are new to Xaraya and are used to a separate Admin area you may prefer a separate look to your Administration area rather than the default Admin Menu.
Start by logging into your site as Administrator and turning on the Admin Dashboard</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>in your</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Themes Module Modify Config</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>option.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>in your Themes Module Modify Config option.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Explore</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Explore Xaraya by starting with the modules in your Admin Menu and reading the Overviews.
Some of the core modules such as Base, Themes, Blocks, and Roles are good places to start. For example,
the Base module is set as the default module in this installation, and provides the site frontpage. You can change this 'default' module in, coincidentally, the Base module.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can activate and install additional non-core modules in your Modules Administration to explore further.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can add a new &lt;em&gt;block&lt;/em&gt; of content anywhere on your page by defining a new block instance in the Blocks module and assigning to a default blockgroup.
You can explore Blocklayout for even further control of layout in your theme.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Getting Help</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>We invite you to become further involved in our community by joining our development or user discussions
at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>, via
mailing lists or IRC.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can contribute easily to making Xaraya an even better product by filing any unexpected functionality in our</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>bug tracker</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Thank you for your support.
For more information on Xaraya, please visit
&lt;a href="http://www.xaraya.com"&gt;
Xaraya's
&lt;/a&gt;
website.</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
