<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="hu_HU.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Thank you for installing and trying Xaraya!</string>
		<translation>Köszönjük, hogy a Xarayát választotta!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="4" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya is currently in Beta Production.</string>
		<translation>A Xaraya jelenleg Béta állapotú.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="10" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you notice any unexpected functionality, please use our bug tracker at
&lt;a href=&quot;http://bugs.xaraya.com&quot;&gt;
http://bugs.xaraya.com&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Hibás működés észlelése esetén, szívesen fogadjuk a probléma leírását a &lt;a href=&quot;http://bugs.xaraya.com&quot;&gt;http://bugs.xaraya.com&lt;/a&gt; címen.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Thank you for your support, and feel free to join our development or user discussions to become involved in our community.</string>
		<translation>Köszönjük a támogatást és várunk mindenkit a Xaraya fejlesztői és felhasználói közösségében!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>For more information on Xaraya, please visit
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xaraya.com&quot;&gt;
Xaraya's
&lt;/a&gt;
website.</string>
		<translation>További információk a &lt;a href=&quot;http://hu.xaraya.com&quot;&gt;Xaraya magyar&lt;/a&gt; és &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xaraya.com&quot;&gt;angol&lt;/a&gt; nyelvű oldalain találhatóak.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This message can be edited by creating an override template (#(1)/themename/modules/base/user-main.xt) for the base module.</string>
		<translation>Ez az üzenet az Alaprendszer modul „#(1)/themename/modules/base/user-main.xt” felülbírált sablonfájljában szerkeszthető.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>About the default theme (yes, this one).</string>
		<translation>Az alapértelmezett grafika (igen, ez).</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The default theme's name is Xaraya_Classic. It is supplied and installed with every distribution package of Xaraya.</string>
		<translation>Az alapértelmezett grafika neve „Xaraya_Classic”, amely minden Xaraya terjesztési csomagban megtalálható.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="47" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Starting from the release 0.9.11 the theme's layout is 100% table-free and is totally CSS driven. It means the theme is now more standards compliant than ever before. However, designing your site with the web-standards in mind requires certain degree of knowledge, experience, attention to detail and patience. So we would advise to keep this theme unmodified within your Xaraya installation directory, in case you need to use it as the (last resource) fallback.</string>
		<translation>A 0.9.11-es kiadástól az oldal elrendezése 100% táblázat mentes, teljesen CSS alapú. Ez azt jelenti, hogy az oldal minden eddigi változatnál pontosabban felel meg a szabványoknak. Azonban, egy weblapot a szabványoknak megfelelően tervezni bizonyos szintű tudást, tapasztalatot és a részletekre való odafigyelést igényel. Tehát azt javasoljuk, hogy a Xaraya_Classic grafikát mindenki tartsa meg a telepítési könyvtárban, bármikor visszakapcsolható, tartalék megoldásnak.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="52" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you wish to design your own Xaraya theme based on the current layout or alter the appearance of this theme, the graphics sources can be obtained from
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xaraya.com/~andyv/xclassic_sources&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Amennyiben a Xaraya_Classicra alapozva szeretne valaki egy új weblapot elkészíteni, a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xaraya.com/~andyv/xclassic_sources&quot;&gt;grafikai anyagok elérhetőek&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="58" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
