<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="sv_SE.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Översikt</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="8" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vad är detta?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="12" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Themes Module controls the display of your website. Certain display variables are set from this module to allow you to control the site name, footer information, etc.</string>
		<translation>Tema-modulen kontroller utseendet för din webbplats. Vissa visningsvariabler ställs in från den här modulen som låter dig kontrollerawebbplatsens namn, sidfots information osv.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="15" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hur använder man den?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="18" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have three choices.</string>
		<translation>Från menyn har du tre val.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="22" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>View Themes: Allows you to see what themes are currently installed on your system, and the current state that they are in.</string>
		<translation>Visa teman: Låter dig se vilka teman som är installerade på ditt system och vilken status de har.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Template Tags: Allows you to view, edit, and delete template tags on the system, as well as add new tags to functions.</string>
		<translation>Malltaggar: Låter dig se, redigera och ta bort malltaggar påsystemet, likväl som att lägga till taggar till funktioner.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Configuration: Allows you to set certain display configuration values.</string>
		<translation>Ändra konfiguration: Låter dig ställa in vissa visningkonfigurations värden.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Medföljande block</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Metablock: The meta block allows you to configure at one time the meta values for your site. This template can be overridden from your theme directory.</string>
		<translation>Metablock: Metablocket låter dig konfigurera metavärdena för din webbplats. Den här mallen kan åtsidosättas från din temakatlog.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="43" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Medföljande kopplingar</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="48" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Themes module has a user menu hook which allows the users of your Xaraya site to change the default theme to their choosing. This can be activated and deactivated from the modules module.</string>
		<translation>Tema-modulen har en användarmeny-koppling som låter användare på din Xaraya webbplats ändra standardtemat till ett som de önskar. Detta kan aktiveras och avaktiveras från modul-modulen.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="52" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
