<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
<entry><string>Installation Complete</string><translation>Installatie compleet</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Congratulations, you have successfully installed</string><translation>Gefeliciteerd, de installatie is succesvol afgerond</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Take this time to customize your installation to match your needs. Use the Modules administration to install any additional features, and use the Blocks administration to adjust the look of your sidebars.</string><translation>U kunt nu uw installatie aanpassen aan uw wensen. Gebruik de 'Modules' module om extra modules te installeren and de 'Blocks' module om blokken in de menu's te veranderen of toe te voegen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Security Hint:</string><translation>Beveiligings tip:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You are strongly advised to remove write access to html/var/config.system.php once the install has completed. This can be done on UNIX using the command</string><translation>Het wordt sterk aangeraden om de schrijftoegang tot html/var/config.system.php te verwijderen wanneer de installatie is afgerond. Dit kan worden gedaan met het UNIX commando</translation></entry>
<entry><string>from within the html/var directory.</string><translation>vanuit de html/var folder.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you are feeling even more security conscious you could remove read access from those who don't need it:</string><translation>Voor nog meer veiligheid kunt u ook nog de leesrechten verwijderen voor degenen die het niet nodig hebben:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>(substitute &quot;apache&quot; for the group your webserver runs as, probably one of apache, web, www or www-data)</string><translation>(vervang &quot;apache&quot; door de group waaronder uw webserver draait. Meestal &quot;apache&quot;, &quot;web&quot;, &quot;www&quot; of &quot;www-data&quot;.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Launch the site!</string><translation>Ga naar de site!</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Thank you for using Xaraya.</string><translation>Bedankt voor het kiezen van Xaraya.</translation></entry>
</translations>
