<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Ledger Module</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="1" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Ledger module is a web based accounting system running on the Xaraya applications framework. Ledger lets so-called virtual companies run their accounting from disparate and changing locations. For larger corporations Ledgers offers a cost-effective way of decentralizing the capture and posting of accounting transactions to the business units where they originate.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="16" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Ledger is an adaptation of CK-Ledger, an excellent open source accounting application that runs on phpgroupware. Information on CK-Ledger can be found</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Ledger can currently run as an accounts receivable package for service based companies</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>To get started</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="24" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>After installing the module, load a chart of accounts, tax, remarks and currency files from the data/ folder. You can do this using the sql files in the folder and for example phpmyadmin, or with the XML files using the Utilities functionality in the Admin part of Ledger. These files are not required; they just let you avoid having to enter your own base data manually.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>To begin, load the SampleData.sql into your database.This is not required; but it lets you avoid having to enter your own base data manually.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Next, insert or adjust the default values in Modify Config to suit your preferences. Note: with this version you *must* initially confirm the default settings in Modify Config by clicking on &quot;Update&quot; in each tab.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can now begin adding customers via the Accounts Receivables -&gt; Customer menu option.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Add the services you will be invoicing via the Service menu option</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="32" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can now begin posting sales orders, invoices and receipts.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Current limitations: Batch matching of invoices and receipts is not implemented; receipts must be matched one by one. Sales order to invoice conversion is not yet implemented.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="34" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Hooks to the Comments module are implemented for sales orders, invoices and receipts. Comments becomes available when any of these objects is being edited.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/ledger/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="48" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
