<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
<entry><string>Choose the publication type you want to display with top items.</string><translation>Kies het publicatietype dat u wilt gebruiken voor populaire items.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default / Current</string><translation>Standaard / Huidig</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Check this if you want the block to display content from all publication types all the time.</string><translation>Vink dit veld aan indien het blok de inhoud van alle publicatietypen moet weergeven.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>All Publication Types</string><translation>Alle publicatietypen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Check this if you want to include the publication type in the article links.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Link to Publication Type</string><translation>Link naar publicatie type</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Choose the category that you want to display with top items.</string><translation>Kies de categorie die voor populaire items gebruikt moet worden.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Check this if you want to include this the category in the article links.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Link to This Category</string><translation>Link naar deze categorie</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Check this if you want to display all articles in all subcategories of the current or selected category.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Include Child Category Content</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Check this if you want the block to display content from all categories all the time.</string><translation>Vind dit veld aan indien het blok de inhoud van alle categorieën moet weergeven.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>All Categories</string><translation>Alle categorieën</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Check this to have the block title dynamically generated from the current content.</string><translation>Vink dit veld aan om de bloktitel dynamisch te laten genereren op basis van de huidige inhoud.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Dynamic Block Title</string><translation>Titel Dynamisch blok</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Choose the sorting options for the top items.</string><translation>Kies de sorteeropties voor populaire items.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Hook Hitcount or Ratings to Articles to use these sort types</string><translation>Haak Hitcount of Ratings aan Artikelen om deze sorteer opties te gebruiken</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Check this box to show the value of the sort that you chose.</string><translation>Vink dit veld aan om de gekozen sorteeroptie weer te geven.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select this if you wish to show the summary of the individual item.</string><translation>Vink dit veld aan indien de samenvatting van het item weergegeven moet worden</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Hook Dynamic Data to articles or itemtypes for Dynamic Data option</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
