<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="de_DE.utf-8">
<entry><string>Modify XarTinyMCE Configuration</string><translation>Konfiguration ändern</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select</string><translation>Auswählen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Install Options</string><translation>Installationsoptionen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Basic Options</string><translation>Basisoptionen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Attributes &amp;amp; Styles</string><translation>Attribute &amp;amp; Styles</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Advanced Theme Options</string><translation>Fortgeschrittene Theme-Optionen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Advanced Config</string><translation>Fortgeschrittene Konfiguration</translation></entry>
<entry><string>1. Set tags in HTML Module</string><translation>1. Tags im HTML-Modul festlegen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Go to the HTML module</string><translation>Gehen Sie zum HTML-Modul</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Set HTML tags allowed</string><translation>Geben Sie die gewünschten HTML-Tags frei</translation></entry>
<entry><string>eg code, span, image, h1 and so on so they are rendered.</string><translation>z.B. code, span, image, h1 usw. - sie werden übergeben..</translation></entry>
<entry><string>2. Set default editor</string><translation>2. Den Standardeditor festlegen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Set xartinymce as default so it activates automatically</string><translation>XarTinyMCE als Standard festlegen, so dass es automatisch aktiviert wird</translation></entry>
<entry><string>TinyMCE as default editor?</string><translation>TinyMCE als Standardeditor?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Yes</string><translation>Ja</translation></entry>
<entry><string>No</string><translation>Nein</translation></entry>
<entry><string>3. Set Operation Mode</string><translation>3. Operationsmodus festlegen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select default replacement mode for TinyMCE</string><translation>Den standardmäßiges Austauschmodus für  TinyMCE festlegen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Choose Default Action Mode</string><translation>Wählen Sie den Standardaktionsmodus</translation></entry>
<entry><string>All Text areas</string><translation>Alle Textbereiche</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Special Labelled only</string><translation>Nur speziell gekennzeichnete Bereiche</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can choose either of the following ways to add a WYSIWYG editor:</string><translation>Sie können eine der folgenden Wege benutzen, um einen WYSIWYG-Editor hinzuzufügen:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;All Text Areas Mode&lt;/strong&gt;: every textarea will be WYSIWYG enabled by default.
Turn off WYSIWYG in a specific div or textarea by adding the reserved class</string><translation>&lt;strong&gt;'Alle Textbereiche'-Modus&lt;/strong&gt;: Jeder Textbereich lässt WYSIWYG standardmäßig zu. WYSIWYG lässt sich abschalten in einem speziellen div / Textbereich, wenn man die reservierte class</translation></entry>
<entry><string>to the textarea. You can also use a toggle or popup prompt for WYSIWYG. This option can affect performance as the javascript is loaded on every page.</string><translation>zu dem Textbereich hinzufügt. Sie können auch einen Schalter / Popup für for WYSIWYG verwenden. Diese Option kann die Performance beeinträchtigen, da Javascript auf jeder Seite geladen wird..</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Special Labelled Only&lt;/strong&gt;: Only textareas that are specially labelled with the
trigger class eg</string><translation>&lt;strong&gt;Nur speziell markierte&lt;/strong&gt;: Nur Textbereiche, die speziell z.B. mit der trigger class gekennzeichnet sind,</translation></entry>
<entry><string>are WYSIWYG activated.
You can do this in two main ways:</string><translation>sind WYSIWYG aktiviert. Sie können dies auf zwei Wegen erreichen:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add a &lt;strong&gt;xarTinyMCE GUI Dynamic Data Property field&lt;/strong&gt; to your Article pubtypes or
xarPages Page Type, or anywhere else you need a WYSIWYG input area.</string><translation>Fügen Sie ein &lt;strong&gt;&quot;xarTinyMCE GUI DynamicData Eigenschaftsfeld&quot;&lt;/strong&gt; zu Ihren Beitrags-Publikationstypen oder xarPages-Seitentyp hinzu oder irgendwo dort, wo Sie ein WYSIWYG-Eingabefeld benötigen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Manually add the class and attribute to any textarea (if activation is Auto this is all you need do else you'll have to add the template snippet below to the top of your template).</string><translation>Fügen Sie manuell die Klasse und das Attribut in jeden Textbereich ein (wenn als Aktivierung &quot;Auto&quot; gewählt wurde, ist dies alles, was Sie tun müssen. Anderenfalls müssen Sie den folgenden Template-Auszug oben in Ihr Template einfügen).</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can set row height and column width in the DD validation field. eg 20:80 for 20 rows high, 80 columns wide. Alternatively use the resizing options available in other Modify Config Tabs.</string><translation>Sie können die Zeilenhöhe und die Spaltenbreite in dem DD-Validierungsfeld festlegen, z.B. 20:80 für 20 Zeilenhöhe, 80 Spaltenbereite. Alternativ können Sie die Veränderungsoptionen nutzen, die in anderen &quot;Konfiguration ändern&quot;-Tabs verfügbar sind.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>4. Set Activation Method</string><translation>4. Aktivierungsmethode festlegen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select automatic activation or manual</string><translation>Automatische oder manuelle Aktivierung auswählen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Automatic activation or manual?</string><translation>Automatische oder manuelle Aktivierung?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Automatic</string><translation>Automatisch</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Manual Override</string><translation>Manuell überschreiben</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Automatic&lt;/strong&gt;: xarTinyMce is automatically activated when mode is
set to All TextAreas without the need to use tinymce DD properties or configure anything further. The disadvantage is that tinymce is loaded on every page.</string><translation>&lt;strong&gt;Automatisch&lt;/strong&gt;: xarTinyMCE wird automatisch aktiviert, wenn der Modus &quot;Alle Textbereiche&quot; festgelegt wurde. Es besteht dann keine Notwendigkeit, tinymce-DD-Eigenschaften zu verwenden oder irgendetwas anderes. Der Nachteil liegt darin, dass tinymce bei jeder Seite geladen wird.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Manual Override&lt;/strong&gt;: turns off automatic activation. xarTinyMCE DD properties are an exception and are still activated with this set as manual.
Alternatively, specify where wysiwyg should or should not be activated by adding the specific template snippet code as shown below, to your page or other specific templates.
All textareas contained or included in the template where you have the XarTinymce tags are converted to WYSIWYG according to the &quot;All Text Area&quot; or &quot;Special Labelled Only&quot; setting above.
Advantages are that tinymce is only loaded when required rather than every page or in every textarea.</string><translation>&lt;strong&gt;Manuell Aufheben&lt;/strong&gt;: schaltet die automatische Aktivierung ab. xarTinyMCE-DD-Eigenschaften sind ein Ausnahmefall und werden noch aktiviert mit dieser Einstellungand als manuell. Legen Sie alternativ fest, wo wysiwyg aktiviert oder eben nicht aktiviert werden sollte durch Hinzufügen unten angezeigte Codeschnipsel, entweder aud der Seite oder spezifischen Templates. Alle Textbereiche enthalten und schließen ein in den Templates, wo Sie die XarTinymce-Tags werden konvertiert zu WYSIWYG entsprechend der oben erwähnten Einstellungen &quot;Alle Textbereiche&quot; oder &quot;Nur speziell gekennzeichnete&quot;. Der Vorteil ist, dass Tinymce nur im Bedarfsfall geladen wird und nicht bei jeder Seite bzw. jedem Textbereich.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;HINT:&lt;/strong&gt; Copy &lt;code&gt;modules/tinymce/xartemplates/properties/showinput-tinymce.xd&lt;/code&gt;
to your own theme's &lt;code&gt;themes/yourtheme/modules/base/properties/showinput-textarea.xt&lt;/code&gt; as a DD textarea override
and set to Specially Labelled and Manual loading mode. This way you can have all your pubtype or xarpages or other DD property textarea fields
automatically converted to wysiwyg with or without button prompt, and tinymce is loaded on a page only when needed.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Basic Editor options</string><translation>Editorbasisoptionen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select which browsers to use WYSIWYG - msie,gecko,opera,safari</string><translation>Wählen Sie, welche Browser WYSIWYG verwenden sollen - msie,gecko,opera,safari</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use for browsers:</string><translation>Verwenden für Browser:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>No spaces eg msie,gecko,opera,safari. Defaults to all.</string><translation>Keine Leerzeichen, z.B. msie,gecko,opera,safari. Stand für alle.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select default Theme Edit Panel for TinyMCE</string><translation>Wählen Sie das Standardpanel des Themeeditors für TinyMCE aus</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default Theme Editor Panel</string><translation>Standardpanel Theme-Editor</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Extra options Tab appears for Advanced Theme</string><translation>Tab für Extraoptionen dient den fortgeschrittenen Themes</translation></entry>
<entry><string>See</string><translation>Achten Sie</translation></entry>
<entry><string>theme instructions</string><translation>auf die Theme-Anleitungen,</translation></entry>
<entry><string>to code your own.</string><translation>um Ihren eigenen Code zu erzeugen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>List of instances, separated by commas, to replace if specific area mode selected</string><translation>Liste von zu ersetzenden Instanzen, getrennt durch Kommata, wenn ein spezifischer Bereichsmodus ausgewählt wurde</translation></entry>
<entry><string>List areas to replace (not supported yet)</string><translation>Bereiche auflisten zum Ersetzen (noch nicht unterstützt)</translation></entry>
<entry><string>WYSIWYG is on by default, unless you check to ask user if they wish to use WYSIWYG for each text area</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Prompt to use WYSIWYG (popup prompt or on by default)?</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use an on/off toggle button to prompt for WYSIWYG</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Display an On/Off Toggle button for WYSIWYG?</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>(xartinymce DD property only)</string><translation>(nur xartinymce DD-Eigenschaft)</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use tiled images instead of individual for faster loading.</string><translation>Vereinfachte Bilder statt individueller verwenden wegen schnelleren Ladens.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use icon map?</string><translation>Icons verwenden?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>(Faster loading, may not work in all setups)</string><translation>(Lädt schneller, arbeitet eventuell nicht in allen Konfigurationen)</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use compressed js to increase preformance?</string><translation>Komprimiertes js verwenden zur Verbesserung der Performance?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use compressor?</string><translation>Kompression einsetzen?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Defaults to width of individual textareas if left blank</string><translation>Wenn leer gelassen, gelten die standardmäßige Werte für die Breite der individuellen Textbereiche</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Override width:</string><translation>Weite aufheben:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Affects all textareas (enter in px eg 450). Turn off resizing.</string><translation>Gilt für alle Textbereiche (Eingabe in px, z.B. 450). Unterbindet die Größenveränderung.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Defaults to height of individual textareas if left blank</string><translation>Wenn leer gelassen, gelten die standardmäßige Werte für die Höhe der individuellen Textbereiche</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Override height:</string><translation>Höhe aufheben:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Defaults to unlimited undo levels if left blank</string><translation>Wenn leer gelassen, gelten standardmäßig unbegrenzte UNDO-Level</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Max # of undo levels :</string><translation>Max # von UNDO-Leveln:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Unlimited if blank</string><translation>Unbegrenzt wenn leer</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Set cleanup functionality that enables you to specify what elements and attributes are allowed.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use content cleanup?</string><translation>Inhalt säubern verwenden?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>(ON by default).</string><translation>(AN als Standard).</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Convert all new lines to &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; tags instead of &amp;lt;p&amp;gt; tags</string><translation>Alle neue Zeilen zu &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; -Tags anstatt zu &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;-Tags konvertieren</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Convert new lines to &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt;</string><translation>Neue Zeilen zu &amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; umwandeln</translation></entry>
<entry><string>(OFF by default).</string><translation>(AUS als Standard).</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Convert all newline chars to &amp;lt;p /&amp;gt; tags</string><translation>Alle Neue-Zeile-Zeichen zu &amp;lt;p /&amp;gt;-Tags konvertieren</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Convert all new line chars to &amp;lt;p /&amp;gt;</string><translation>Alle Neue-Zeile-Zeichen zu &amp;lt;p /&amp;gt; konvertieren</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Strip all newlines</string><translation>Alle neue Zeilen entfernen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Apply formatting to source</string><translation>Wenden Sie die Formatierung auf die Quelle an</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Apply source formatting</string><translation>Wenden Sie die Quellenformatierung an</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Language options</string><translation>Sprachoptionen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select default language for TinyMCE</string><translation>Wählen Sie die Standardsprache für TinyMCE aus</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default language</string><translation>Standardsprache</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Supplied in UTF-8 format only. See</string><translation>Unterstützt nur im UTF-8-Format. Schauen Sie bei ein</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Creating a Language Pack</string><translation>Sprachpaket anlegen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>if you wish to edit or contribute a language pack. Further language packs for this version can
be downloaded at</string><translation>nach, wenn ein Sprachpaket bearbeiten oder ein solches beisteuern wollen. Weitere Sprachpakete für diese Version finden sich bei</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select direction of text input - defaults left to right</string><translation>Textrichtung für die Eingabe auswählen - standardmäßig ist das links nach rechts</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Text input direction</string><translation>Texteingaberichtung</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Right to left</string><translation>Rechts nach links</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Left to right</string><translation>Links nach rechts</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default is Left to right.</string><translation>Standard ist links nach rechts.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Convert to a XML escaping entities eg</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Convert to XML escaped character entities</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select encoding method</string><translation>Verschlüsselungsmethode auswählen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Entity Encoding:</string><translation>Entity-Definition:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Raw</string><translation>Ohne</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Numeric &amp;amp;#160;</string><translation>Numerisch &amp;amp;#160;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Named &amp;amp;nbsp;</string><translation>Benannt &amp;amp;nbsp;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Numeric</string><translation>Numerisch</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Named entities</string><translation>Benannte Entities</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default is Raw (none).</string><translation>Standard ist Raw (keine).</translation></entry>
<entry><string>If 'named' a</string><translation>Wenn 'benannt&quot; ausgewählt ist, wird ein</translation></entry>
<entry><string>default string</string><translation>Standardstring</translation></entry>
<entry><string>of named entities is used.</string><translation>von benannten entities verwendet.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Set CSS and Style Options</string><translation>CSS- und S´tyle-Optionen festlegen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Converts attributes like width, height, border, to inline styles eg style= ....</string><translation>Konvertiert Eigenschaften wie Breite, Höhe, Rahmen zu Inline-Styles z.B. style=...</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Convert attributes to inline style?</string><translation>Eigenschaften zu Inline-Styles konvertieren?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Additional html tags, forced or alternate attributes and so on, separated by commas</string><translation>Zusätzliche HTML-Tags, erzwungen oder Ausweicheigenschaften usw., getrennt durch Kommata</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Additional tags or attributes:</string><translation>Zusätzliche Tags oder Attribute</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Additional regex for allowed tags and attributes.</string><translation>Zusätzliche reguläre Ausdrücke für erlaubte Tags und Attribute.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Check the Defaults</string><translation>Prüfen Sie die Standards,</translation></entry>
<entry><string>before adding new allowed tags and attributes here. Any added elements here are are added to the default with the &lt;strong&gt;extended_valid_elements&lt;/strong&gt;
config option. Separate each tag with a comma. *[*] allows all tags and attributes. If you have HTML module installed, its settings will override and
prevent tags being rendered (but not filter out individual tags, or specific attributes).</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>List of html tags that are not allowed, separated by commas. These will be stripped from the textarea.</string><translation>Liste von nicht erlaubten HTML-Tags, getrennt durch Kommata. Diese werden aus dem Textbereich entfernt.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Tags that are NOT allowed:</string><translation>Tags, die NICHT erlaubt sind:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>CSS file name for content and class dropdown list, relative to index.php</string><translation>CSS-Dateiname für Inhalt- und Klasse-Auswahlliste, relativ zur index.php</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Content and Style list CSS</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Classes defined in this file appear in the Style dropdown list and affect content.</string><translation>In dieser Datei definierte Klassen erscheinen in der Style-Auswahlliste und betreffen den Inhalt.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>CSS file name for editor and toolbar/user interface, relative to index.php</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Editor UI CSS File</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Affects the editor layout, toolbars and general look of the editor itself.</string><translation>Betrifft das Editorlayout, Werkzeugleiste und das allgemeine Aussehen des Editors selbst.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Advanced Theme Editor Options</string><translation>Fortgeschrittene Themeeditoroptionen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Position of the editor toolbar at top or bottom of text input area</string><translation>Position der Editorwerkzeugleiste am Anfang oder Ende des Eingabefeldes</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Toolbar position:</string><translation>Position der Werkzeugleiste:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Top</string><translation>Oben</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Bottom</string><translation>Unten</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Position of the status bar</string><translation>Position der Statusbar</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Status bar display position:</string><translation>Anzeigeposition der Statusbar:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enable or disable the status bar path</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Display css rule path in status bar?</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enable vertical resizing of editor?</string><translation>Vertikale Größenveränderung des Editors ermöglichen?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Allow vertical resizing of editor?</string><translation>Vertikale Größenveränderung des Editors zulassen?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enable horizontal resizing of editor?</string><translation>Horizontale Größenveränderung des Editors ermöglichen?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Allow horizontal resizing of editor?</string><translation>Horizontale Größenveränderung des Editors zulassen?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>List of other style elements to add - must be defined in your style sheet or page</string><translation>Liste von anderen hinzuzufügenden Style-Elementen - sie müssen in Ihrem Stylesheet oder in Ihrer Seite definiert sein</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Extended style list</string><translation>Umfassende Style-Liste</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Comma separated list of block formats to be used in format drop down list.</string><translation>Kommagetrennte Liste von Blockformaten, die in der Formatauflistung (Dropdownliste) verwandt werden.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>List of block formats:</string><translation>Liste von Block-Formaten:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>These default to p, address, pre, h1, h2, h3, h4, h5 and h6 if left blank. You can add div,blockquote,dt,dd,code,samp.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Plugin Options</string><translation>Pluginoptionen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>for more detail on each plugin.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add names of any extra plugins you wish to load here.</string><translation>Fügen Sie den Namen jedes zusätzlichen Plugins an, das hier geladen werden soll.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Names of plugins to load (separated by commas):</string><translation>Namen der zu ladenden Plugins (getrennt durch Kommata)</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Available plugins (bundled):&lt;/strong&gt; save, emotions, iespell (IE only), insertdatetime, preview, zoom,
advimage, advlink, flash, advhr, searchreplace, print, table, xarpagebreak, contextmenu, lorem, paste,
fullscreen, directionality, fullpage, liststyle, layer, style, spellchecker, media, visualchars, nonbreaking, xhtmlxtras, devkit</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Format for Date</string><translation>Datumsformat</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Format for date</string><translation>Datumsformat</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default is YYYY-MM-DD</string><translation>Standardwert ist YYYY-MM-DD</translation></entry>
<entry><string>%y as year range 00 to 99, %Y as year YYYY, %d day range 01 to 31, %m month range 01 to 12, %D same as %m/%d/%y</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Format for Time</string><translation>Zeitformat</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Format for time :</string><translation>Zeitformat</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default is HH:MM:SS</string><translation>Standardwert ist HH:MM:SS</translation></entry>
<entry><string>%H hour using a 24-hour clock, %M minute as 00-59, %S second as 00-59, %% - a literal `%' character</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use the filebrowser for advanced image, link or flash plugins?</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use integrated &lt;strong&gt;Filebrowser&lt;/strong&gt; for file browsing and uploading for eg images, links, flash plugins ?</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>To use FileBrowser (or downloaded Xaraya IBrowser or IManager plugin):</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add &lt;strong&gt;ibrowser or imanager&lt;/strong&gt; (or any plugin that uses filebrowser eg advimage or advlink) to the plugins above</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add &lt;strong&gt;ibrowser or imanager &lt;/strong&gt; to the button list in Advanced Theme Layout option below.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Update the</string><translation>Aktualisieren Sie</translation></entry>
<entry><string>configuration file at modules/tinymce/xartemplates/includes/tinymceconfig.inc.php</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>and copy to your &lt;code&gt;var/tinymce/tinymceconfig.inc.php&lt;/code&gt; directory</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Advanced Theme Button Layout</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you wish to change the DEFAULTS then you can add or remove buttons, or define
which buttons appear.</string><translation>Wenn Sie die STANDARDS ändern wollen, können Sie Button entfernen und hinzufügen oder aber definieren, welche Buttons erscheinen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Valid button names are&lt;/strong&gt; (separate names by comma - no spaces):</string><translation>&lt;strong&gt;Gültige Buttonnamen sind&lt;/strong&gt; (Namen mit Komma trennen - nicht mit Leerzeichen):):</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Valid plugin button options&lt;/strong&gt;</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add extra button or plugins for this theme here</string><translation>Fügen Sie Extra-Buttons oder Plugins für dieses Theme hier hinzu</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add EXTRA Buttons:</string><translation>EXTRA-Button hinzufügen:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add these extra buttons to your editor toolbar.</string><translation>Fügen Sie diese zusätzlichen Buttons zu Ihrer Werkzeugleiste hinzu.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Additional buttons for this theme for Line 1 - see manual</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Row 1</string><translation>Zeile 1</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Additional buttons for this theme for Line 2 - see manual</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Row 2</string><translation>Zeile 2</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Additional buttons for this theme for Line 3 - see manual</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Row 3</string><translation>Zeile 3</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Buttons to remove from Advanced theme</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Remove these buttons:</string><translation>Diese Buttons entfernen:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Build Your Own Layout</string><translation>Gestalten Sie sich Ihr eigenes Layout</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can define your own Custom Editor Layout from here using existing buttons.
Any entry in a row will force use of this custom layout. A &lt;strong&gt;space&lt;/strong&gt; alone will remove a row so be careful!</string><translation>Sie können sich Ihr eigenes Editorlayout unter Verwendung der existierenden Buttons gestalten. Jeder Eintrag in einer Zeile erzwingt die Verwendung dieses Layouts. Ein &lt;strong&gt;Leerzeichen &lt;/strong&gt; alleine entfernt eine Zeile - seien Sie also vorsichtig!</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Restrict buttons for Line 1 to these buttons only</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Restrict buttons for Line 2 to these buttons only</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Restrict buttons for Line 3 to these buttons only</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Multiple Configuration Instances</string><translation>Mehrfach-Konfigurationsinstanzen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Would you like to use multiple configuration settings?</string><translation>Wollen Sie Mehrfach-Konfigurationseinstellungen verwenden?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;strong&gt;Use multiple configurations?&lt;/strong&gt; (Must be checked for activation of custom config options below).</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enter code for multiple configuration instances of tinymce.
In each configuration you must have at least</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Do not</string><translation>Verwenden Sie nicht</translation></entry>
<entry><string>use the default</string><translation>den Standard-</translation></entry>
<entry><string>as the trigger name.</string><translation>als Auslösenamen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can set multiple instances here.To use a specific configuration add the trigger class name to
your div or textarea where you want the wysiwyg instance eg</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Please &lt;strong&gt;check the final tinymce config code&lt;/strong&gt; in the code display at the end of this screen before use!</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enter additional individual custom config options here</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Custom Config options:</string><translation>Spezifische Konfigurationsoptionen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Custom Configuration Code</string><translation>Spezifischer Konfigurationscode</translation></entry>
<entry><string>This option allows you to add additional custom configuration options that are added to the DEFAULT tinymce configuration string.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Please refer to the TinyMCE</string><translation>Bitte verweisen Sie auf die TinyMCE</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Usage Documentation</string><translation>-Gebrauchsanweisung</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Each option should be on a separate line, ending in a comma, in the format</string><translation>Jede Option sollte sich in einer eigenen Zeile befinden, endend mit einem Komma, in dem Format</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enter additional config options here</string><translation>Zusätzliche Konfigurationsoptionen hier eingeben</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Current active default configuration</string><translation>Aktuell aktive Standardkonfiguration</translation></entry>
</translations>
