<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
<entry><string>deleted</string><translation>διαγράφηκε</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The operation #(1) is not supported</string><translation>Η λειτουργία #(1) δεν υποστηρίζεται</translation></entry>
<entry><string>SELECT with total of columns different from the number retrieved.</string><translation>Εντολή SELECT με σύνολο στηλών διαφορετικό από τον αριθμό που επιστράφηκε</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The table #(1) you are trying to add needs to be a string or an array.</string><translation>Ο πίνακας #(1) που προσπαθείτε να προσθέσετε πρέπει να είναι string ή array</translation></entry>
<entry><string>This function only take 1 or 2 paramters</string><translation>Αυτή η συνάρτηση δέχεται 1 ή 2 το πολύ ορίσματα</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The field #(1) you are trying to add needs to be a string or an array.</string><translation>Το πεδίο #(1) που προσπαθείτε να προσθέσετε πρέπει να είναι string ή array</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Your query has no fields.</string><translation>Το ερώτημα δεν έχει πεδία</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Realm</string><translation>Realm</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Module</string><translation>Μονάδα</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Component</string><translation>Εξάρτημα</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Level</string><translation>Επίπεδο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Confirm the deletion of all instances of Privilege</string><translation>Επιβεβαιώστε την διαγραφή όλων των υλοποιήσεων του Προνομίου</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modify Privilege</string><translation>Τροποποίηση Προνομίου</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Current instances</string><translation>Τρέχουσες υλοποιήσεις</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modify the &lt;a #(1)&gt;instances that apply&lt;/a&gt; for this privilege</string><translation>Τροποποίηση των &lt;a #(1)&gt;υλοποιήσεων που είναι σχετικές&lt;/a&gt; με αυτό το προνόμιο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add Privilege To</string><translation>Προσθήκη Προνομίου Στο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Privilege:</string><translation>Προνόμιο:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Component Memberships</string><translation>Μέλη Εξαρτημάτων</translation></entry>
<entry><string>New Privilege</string><translation>Νέο Προνόμιο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Member of</string><translation>Μέλος του</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Specify the &lt;a #(1)&gt;instances that apply&lt;/a&gt; for this privilege</string><translation>Προσδιορίστε τις &lt;a #(1)&gt;υλοποιήσεις που είναι σχετικές&lt;/a&gt; με αυτό το προνόμιο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Confirm the removal of Privilege</string><translation>Επιβεβαιώστη την αφαίρεση του Προνομίου</translation></entry>
<entry><string>from</string><translation>από</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Cancel the removal</string><translation>Ακύρωση της αφαίρεσης</translation></entry>
<entry><string>View</string><translation>Εμφάνιση</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Privileges module lets you manage &lt;b&gt;access rights&lt;/b&gt; on your site. Privileges give roles access to certain resources of your choosing. They are the basic components of the security system.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Here are some of the things you can do with privileges</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya's privileges are extremely flexible. You can define privileges at the level of site, modules, component classes within modules, or single instances of those classes.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Clicking on the View Privileges link gives you an overview of all the privileges on your system. Compound privileges are collapsed, but you can click on them to open them up and view their components.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>When adding or modifying a privilege, you can define it to have its own access rights, or simply to serve as a container for other privileges</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya comes preconfigured with a minimal set of privileges that are loaded when you run the installer. These will vary according to the configuration you chose. Examples are</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;b&gt;Administration&lt;/b&gt;: a privilege that gives a role complete access to all resources on the site. At installation this privilege is assigned to the role Administrators and is inherited by the user Admin.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;b&gt;CasualAccess&lt;/b&gt;: this is the privilege assigned to unregistered users on the site. It is initially defined to allow viewing access of the front page, as well as access to the login block.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>&lt;b&gt;GeneralLock&lt;/b&gt;: a privilege that restricts access to certain basic roles and privileges the system requires, such as the default admin. This is to avoid inadvertent removal.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>All privileges in the system can be changed or removed. (For those protected by GeneralLock above this takes a bit more doing.) You can also combine privileges by using them as elements to create compound privileges, or make new privileges of your choosing. There is no limit to the number of privileges you can create or their levels of nesting.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no included blocks</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Extended information about this module can be found in</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
