<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Mode of operation</string>
		<translation>Mude-a ooff oopereshun</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="12" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The multilanguage system (MLS) works in three different modes.</string>
		<translation>Zee moolteelungooege-a system (MLS) vurks in three-a deefffferent mudes. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Please note that you cannot use UNBOXED mode of the MultiLanguage system unless you have php 4.3.0
                with the mbstring extension compiled in.</string>
		<translation>Pleese-a nute-a thet yuoo cunnut use-a UNBOXED mude-a ooff zee MoolteeLungooege-a system unless yuoo hefe-a php 4.3.0 veet zee mbstreeng ixtenseeun cumpeeled in. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="15" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Single language mode (SINGLE)</string>
		<translation>Seengle-a lungooege-a mude-a (SINGLE)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="22" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>MLS uses only one character set, typically single byte but potentially multi byte if mb_string is 
                built in. All information is stored coherently with the chosen character set (at installation time), 
                and also user data is meaningful in the chosen character set.</string>
		<translation>MLS uses oonly oone-a cherecter set, typeecelly seengle-a byte-a boot putenteeelly mooltee byte-a iff mb_streeng is booeelt in. Ell inffurmeshun is stured cuherently veet zee chusee cherecter set (et instelleshun teeme-a), und elsu user deta is meuneengffool in zee chusee cherecter set. Um de hur de hur de hur.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Per page mode (BOXED)</string>
		<translation>Per pege-a mude-a (BOXED)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>MLS can use more than one character set in the site (the same consideration for the single or multi byte matter as 
                above can be applied here), but only one character set per page is used (this is an obvious concept maybe, 
                but important to understand). Due to this fact content cannot be shared across through different 
                language areas (for example an Arabic comment won't be shown in the English area even if 
                they are referring to the same object, e.g. an article available in both English and Arabic). 
                Another point is that every operation involves only a single language. This mode can produce 
                unexpected results if mb_string is not installed.</string>
		<translation>MLS cun use-a mure-a thun oone-a cherecter set in zee seete-a (zee seme-a cunseedereshun fur zee seengle-a oor mooltee byte-a metter es ebufe-a cun be-a eppleeed here-a), boot oonly oone-a cherecter set per pege-a is used (thees is un oobfeeuoos cuncept meybe-a, boot impurtunt tu understund). Dooe-a tu thees fect cuntent cunnut be-a shered ecruss thruoogh deefffferent lungooege-a erees (fur ixemple-a un Erebeec cumment vun't be-a shoon in zee Ingleesh erea ifee iff zeey ere-a refferreeng tu zee seme-a oobject, i.g. un erteecle-a efeeeleble-a in but Ingleesh und Erebeec). Unuzeer pueent is thet ifery oopereshun infulfes oonly a seengle-a lungooege-a. Thees mude-a cun prudooce-a unexpected resoolts iff mb_streeng is nut instelled. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>It is installed on this server, so you can give this mode a try</string>
		<translation>It is instelled oon thees serfer, su yuoo cun geefe-a thees mude-a a try</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="41" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>WARNING: mb_string is NOT installed on this server, proceed with caution</string>
		<translation>VERNING: mb_streeng is NOT instelled oon thees serfer, pruceed veet cooshun</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="43" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Full multilanguage (UNBOXED) (experimental!)</string>
		<translation>Fooll moolteelungooege-a (UNBOXED) (ixpereementel!)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="46" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>MLS uses an universal character set to represent everything (read: UTF-8). This guarantees that no 
                conversion is needed for the content representation. Every page is always shown according to 
                the user chosen language, but the page can contain texts in other languages 
                (for example a French article and comments inside an English page).</string>
		<translation>MLS uses un uneefersel cherecter set tu represent iferytheeng (reed: UTF-8). Thees gooeruntees thet nu cunferseeun is needed fur zee cuntent representeshun. Ifery pege-a is elveys shoon eccurdeeng tu zee user chusee lungooege-a, boot zee pege-a cun cunteeen texts in oozeer lungooeges (fur ixemple-a a French erteecle-a und cumments inseede-a un Ingleesh pege-a).</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="53" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Language/Locale Configuration</string>
		<translation>Lungooege-a/Lucele-a Cunffeegooreshun</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="59" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The following locales are available to this site:</string>
		<translation>Zee fullooeeng luceles ere-a efeeeleble-a tu thees seete-a:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="61" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Locale</string>
		<translation>Lucele</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="66" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Active</string>
		<translation>Ecteefe</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="69" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Default locale to load</string>
		<translation>Deffoolt lucele-a tu lued</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="90" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Default Locale</string>
		<translation>Deffoolt Lucele</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="90" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Translations backend</string>
		<translation>Trunsleshuns beckend</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="107" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The translated information for xaraya and her modules can be stored in different back-ends. The following back-ends are supported:</string>
		<translation>Zee trunsleted inffurmeshun fur xereya und her mudooles cun be-a stured in deefffferent beck-inds. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Zee fullooeeng beck-inds ere-a sooppurted:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="108" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Translations Backend</string>
		<translation>Trunsleshuns Beckend</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="113" />
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="113" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>XML (good for interoperability)</string>
		<translation>XML (guud fur interuperebeelity)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="118" />
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="121" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>PHP (good for programmed access)</string>
		<translation>PHP (guud fur prugremmed eccess)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="119" />
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/includes/modifyconfig-locales.xd" line="122" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
