<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="hu_HU.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Messages Module Overview</string>
		<translation>Áttekintés</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If this is your first visit to this part of your Xaraya site,
please take a minute to read through the following introduction,
in order to explore the different possibilities offered by the
Contact module.</string>
		<translation>Ezen az oldalon az Üzenetek modul rövid áttekintését olvashatjuk el.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="7"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>"The Messages module gives your users a way to send messages to another users inbox."</string>
		<translation>Az Üzenetek modul lehetőséget biztosít a felhasználóknak, hogy más felhasználóknak üzeneteket küldjenek a weblapon.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>"You must be logged into the site before you can send messages. Select Messages from the user menu and select a user from the drop down list to send your message too. Compose your message and select the send button."</string>
		<translation>A modult csak a honlapra bejelentkezett felhasználók tudják használni. A felhasználói menüből válasszuk az Üzenetek modult, majd válasszuk ki a felhasználót akinek üzenetet szeretnénk küldeni. Írjuk meg és küldjük el az üzenetet.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>"From the Admin menu you can specify the support of short urls for the messages module."</string>
		<translation>Az Üzenetek adminisztrálásánál ki illetve bekapcsolhatjuk a modul rövid URL támogatását.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>"newmessages"</string>
		<translation>newmessages</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>newmessages -&gt; Display's a block that lists any new unread messages for the user with a link to the view messages page.'</string>
		<translation>newmessages -&gt; Megjeleníti az olvasatlan üzenetek számát és egy hivatkozást az üzenetek modulra.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="41"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Your private messages</string>
		<translation>Személyes üzenetek</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/user-display.xd" line="4"/>
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
