<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
<entry><string>WikiAdministration</string><translation>Διαχείριση Wiki</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Overview</string><translation>Περίληψη</translation></entry>
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Τι είναι;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Wiki module is a simple imlementation of some aspects of wikis.</string><translation>Η μονάδα Wiki είναι μια απλή υλοποίηση ορισμένων λειτουργίων των wikis</translation></entry>
<entry><string>It is currently responsible for providing the ability to transform &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:How_to_edit_a_page#Wiki_markup&quot;&gt;wiki markup&lt;/a&gt; in a module itemtype when hooked to the module or itemtype.</string><translation>Είναι υπεύθυνη για να δίνει την δυνατότητα μετατροπής Wiki markup του τύπου &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia:How_to_edit_a_page#Wiki_markup&quot;&gt;wiki markup&lt;/a&gt; σε ένα itemtype μονάδας όταν έχει γίνει hook στην μονάδα ή στο itemtype.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>At the current time it provides transformation of wiki formatting markup tags,
not wiki markup for wiki linking and wiki words.</string><translation>Αυτή την στιγμή παρέχει μετατροές για wiki formatting markup tags, όχι για wiki markup για συνδέσμους και λέξεις</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Πως χρησιμοποιείται;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Hook the wiki module to any content module and/or it's itemtypes that supports hooks. For example the Articles module and any of it's publication types.</string><translation>Αγκιστρώστε (hook) την μονάδα wiki σε οποιαδήποτε μονάδα περιεχομένου και/ή στους τύπους αντικειμένων της που υποστηρίζουν άγκιστρα (hooks). Για παράδειγμα την μονάδα Άρθρα και οποιαδήποτε από τους τύπους έκδοσής της.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Blocks που συμπεριλαμβάνονται</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no blocks included at this time</string><translation>Δεν περιλαμβάνονται blocks</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Άγκιστρα που συμπεριλαμβάνονται</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Wiki module provides a transform hook that transforms Wiki markup.
To activate the hook go to</string><translation>Η μονάδα Wiki παρέχει ένα άγκιστρο μετατροπής που μετατρέπει Wiki markup. Για να το ενεργοποίηστε πηγαίντε στο</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modules - Configure Hooks - Wiki Module</string><translation>Μονάδες - Ρύθμιση Hooks - Μονάδα Wiki</translation></entry>
<entry><string>From there check the radio buttons next to the modules and itemtypes where you wish to activate the wiki markup transformations.</string><translation>Απο εκεί επιλέξτε τα radio buttons δίπλα στις μονάδας και τύπους αντικειμένων για τα οποία επιθυμείται να ενεργοποιήσετε μετατροπές wiki markup</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation>Περισσότερες πληροφορίες</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the Example module can be found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Example Extension page at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Example Module - Xaraya Extension 36</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation>Πατήστε στο tab Ιστορία Εκδόσεων κάτω για να πάρετε περισσότερες πληροφορίες για ιστορικό εκδόσεων</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on Example found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on Example</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Example Module Overview</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation>Έκδοση</translation></entry>
</translations>
