<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The AuthSSO module allows Xaraya to automatically log users authenticated by the web server into Xaraya.  The original intent was to transparently log in users whose credentials could be passed by their browser to the web server for authentication.  Additionally, this module can be used to leverage other authentication mechanisms via its ability to delegate authentication to the web server (say, by having the web server authenticate with mod_auth_pam and then using pam to plug into an external authentication system).</string>
		<translation>Zee OothSSO mudoole-a elloos Xereya tu ootumeteecelly lug users oozeenteeceted by zee veb serfer intu Xereya. Zee ooreeginel intent ves tu trunsperently lug in users vhuse-a credenteeels cuoold be-a pessed by zeeur brooser tu zee veb serfer fur oozeenteeceshun. Eddeeshunelly, thees mudoole-a cun be-a used tu leferege-a oozeer oozeenteeceshun mechuneesms feea its ebeelity tu delegete-a oozeenteeceshun tu zee veb serfer (sey, by hefeeng zee veb serfer oozeenteecete-a veet mud_oot_pem und zeen useeng pem tu ploog intu un ixternel oozeenteeceshun system).</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Warning: this module is useless if you do not have your web server set up to authenticate users.  Refer to your web server's documentation on how to set this up.</string>
		<translation>Verneeng: thees mudoole-a is useless iff yuoo du nut hefe-a yuoor veb serfer set up tu oozeenteecete-a users. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Reffer tu yuoor veb serfer's ducoomenteshun oon hoo tu set thees up.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Warning: this module is only as secure as your web server authentication mechanism.  It completely trusts the web server to handle user credential processing.</string>
		<translation>Verneeng: thees mudoole-a is oonly es secoore-a es yuoor veb serfer oozeenteeceshun mechuneesm. It cumpletely troosts zee veb serfer tu hundle-a user credenteeel prucesseeng.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Authentication by AuthSSO is automatically enabled/available once the AuthSSO module has been initialized.  To disable AuthSSO authentication, you must remove the module (or disable the webserver authentication, which is a prerequisite of AuthSSO functionality).</string>
		<translation>Oozeenteeceshun by OothSSO is ootumeteecelly inebled/efeeeleble-a oonce-a zee OothSSO mudoole-a hes beee ineetielized. Bork bork bork! Tu deeseble-a OothSSO oozeenteeceshun, yuoo moost remufe-a zee mudoole-a (oor deeseble-a zee vebserfer oozeenteeceshun, vheech is a prereqooeesite-a ooff OothSSO fooncshuneleety).</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have one choice.  &quot;Modify Config&quot;.</string>
		<translation>Frum zee menoo, yuoo hefe-a oone-a chueece-a. &quot;Mudeeffy Cunffeeg&quot;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Config -- You can also allow a user that has been authenticated by the web server to be automatically added to the Xaraya database and allowed to login.</string>
		<translation>Mudeeffy Cunffeeg -- Yuoo cun elsu elloo a user thet hes beee oozeenteeceted by zee veb serfer tu be-a ootumeteecelly edded tu zee Xereya detebese-a und ellooed tu lugeen.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="43" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>No blocks yet, but one is coming...</string>
		<translation>Nu blucks yet, boot oone-a is cumeeng...</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="47" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="51" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The AuthSSO module has no hooks included at this time.</string>
		<translation>Zee OothSSO mudoole-a hes nu huuks inclooded et thees teeme-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>TODO List</string>
		<translation>TODO Leest</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="59" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The 0.02 version of the AuthSSO module is a skeleton proof of concept.  There are many &quot;ToDo&quot;s.</string>
		<translation>Zee 0.02 ferseeun ooff zee OothSSO mudoole-a is a skeletun pruuff ooff cuncept. Um de hur de hur de hur. Zeere-a ere-a muny &quot;TuDu&quot;s. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="63" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Rework to make natively pluggable with external auth systems other than the web server (i.e. allow xaraya to trust the authentication of other external systems, or to validate a ticket issued by a third party SSO product).</string>
		<translation>Roourk tu meke-a neteefely plooggeble-a veet ixternel oot systems oozeer thun zee veb serfer (i.i. elloo xereya tu troost zee oozeenteeceshun ooff oozeer ixternel systems, oor tu feleedete-a a teecket issooed by a thurd perty SSO prudooct).</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Make integration with other external user information options easily configurable and extendable.</string>
		<translation>Meke-a integreshun veet oozeer ixternel user inffurmeshun oopshuns ieseely cunffeegooreble-a und ixtendeble-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="66" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Allow site administrators to designate a local authsystem administrator account.</string>
		<translation>Elloo seete-a edmeenistreturs tu deseegnete-a a lucel oothsystem edmeenistretur eccuoont. Um de hur de hur de hur.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="67" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Allow site administrators to configure which modules or pages do not auto sign in the web server authenticated user.</string>
		<translation>Elloo seete-a edmeenistreturs tu cunffeegoore-a vheech mudooles oor peges du nut ootu seegn in zee veb serfer oozeenteeceted user. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="68" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Extended inffurmeshun ebuoot thees mudoole-a cun be-a fuoond here-a. [mudooles mudoole-a]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authsso/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="73" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
