<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Update Privileges Configuration</string>
		<translation>Bewaar de privilege instellingen</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xaradmin/modifyconfig.php" line="26" />
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="73" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Components of</string>
		<translation>De componenten van</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-displayprivilege.xd" line="140" />
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-modifyprivilege.xd" line="272" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Add a Privilege to</string>
		<translation>Voeg een privilege toe aan</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-modifyprivilege.xd" line="277" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Privilege:</string>
		<translation>Privilege:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-modifyprivilege.xd" line="282" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Component Memberships</string>
		<translation>Component onderdelen</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-modifyprivilege.xd" line="302" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Module to which this provilege will apply</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-newprivilege.xd" line="120" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Component to which this provilege applies</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-newprivilege.xd" line="140" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This privilege is assigned to the following groups/users:</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-viewroles.xd" line="85" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya's privileges are extremely flexible. You can define privileges at the level of site, modules, component classes within modules, or single instances of those classes.</string>
		<translation>De privileges van Xaraya zijn uiterst flexibel. U kunt privileges definiëren op het niveau van de site, de modules, componentklassen binnen module, of enkelvoudige instanties van deze klassen.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="26" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Clicking on the View Privileges link gives you an overview of all the privileges on your system. Compound privileges are collapsed, but you can click on them to open them up and view their components.</string>
		<translation>Door op 'toon privileges' te klikken wordt een overzicht getoond van de beschikbare privileges. Samengestelde privileges zijn compact weergegeven, maar u kunt deze uitklappen en hun componenten bekijken.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="44" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Administration: a privilege that gives a role complete access to all resources on the site. At installation this privilege is assigned to the role Administrators and is inherited by the user Admin.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="57" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>CasualAccess: this is the privilege assigned to unregistered users on the site. It is initially defined to allow viewing access of the front page, as well as access to the login block.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="60" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>GeneralLock: a privilege that restricts access to certain basic roles and privileges the system requires, such as the default admin. This is to avoid inadvertent removal.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="63" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>All privileges in the system can be changed or removed. (For those protected by GeneralLock above this takes a bit more doing.) You can also combine privileges by using them as elements to create compound privileges, or make new privileges of your choosing. There is no limit to the number of privileges you can create or their levels of nesting.</string>
		<translation>Alle privileges in het systeem kunnen worden gewijzigd of verwijderd (Voor de privileges die worden beschermd door 'GeneralLock' moet er wat meer moeite worden gedaan). U kunt ook privileges combineren door ze als elementen te gebruiken in samengestelde privileges, of nieuwe privileges naar keuze aanmaken. Er is geen limiet aan het aantal privileges of het aantal niveaus dat genest kan worden.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="68" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found in</string>
		<translation>Uitgebreide informatie over deze module kan worden gevonden in</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="90" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>View Privilege:</string>
		<translation>Bekijk Privilege:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-displayprivilege.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
