<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The AuthphpBB2 module allows Xaraya to automatically log users authenticated by the phpBB2 into Xaraya.</string>
		<translation>Zee OothphpBB2 mudoole-a elloos Xereya tu ootumeteecelly lug users oozeenteeceted by zee phpBB2 intu Xereya.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Authentication by AuthphpBB2 is automatically enabled/available once the AuthphpBB2 module has been initialized.  To disable AuthphpBB2 authentication, you must remove the module. But if your phpBB2 settins differ from the defautl ones (they are, sure) you need to set them up in &quot;Admin panel/authphpbb2/Modify Config&quot;.</string>
		<translation>Oozeenteeceshun by OothphpBB2 is ootumeteecelly inebled/efeeeleble-a oonce-a zee OothphpBB2 mudoole-a hes beee ineetielized. Bork bork bork! Tu deeseble-a OothphpBB2 oozeenteeceshun, yuoo moost remufe-a zee mudoole-a. Boot iff yuoor phpBB2 setteens deeffffer frum zee deffootl oones (zeey ere-a, soore-a) yuoo need tu set zeem up in &quot;Edmeen punel/oothphpbb2/Mudeeffy Cunffeeg&quot;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Notices:</string>
		<translation>Nuteeces:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>When user logs in using this module new record appears in Xaraya's roles table. And user can change this table using Roles module. But all that changes wouldn't be synchronized back to phpBB2.</string>
		<translation>Vhee user lugs in useeng thees mudoole-a noo recurd eppeers in Xereye's rules teble-a. Und user cun chunge-a thees teble-a useeng Rules mudoole-a. Boot ell thet chunges vuooldn't be-a synchruneezed beck tu phpBB2.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya uses username (login) to refer to phpBB2 users. So if user changes there names in phpBB2 they will get problems in Xaraya account.</string>
		<translation>Xereya uses userneme-a (lugeen) tu reffer tu phpBB2 users. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Su iff user chunges zeere-a nemes in phpBB2 zeey veell get prublems in Xereya eccuoont. Um de hur de hur de hur.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have one choice.  &quot;Modify Config&quot;.</string>
		<translation>Frum zee menoo, yuoo hefe-a oone-a chueece-a. &quot;Mudeeffy Cunffeeg&quot;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Config -- Here you should set your phpBB2 settings to allow Xaraya to connect to phpBB2 db and get user's info from there. You can also allow a user that has been authenticated by the web server to be automatically added to the Xaraya database and allowed to login.</string>
		<translation>Mudeeffy Cunffeeg -- Here-a yuoo shuoold set yuoor phpBB2 setteengs tu elloo Xereya tu cunnect tu phpBB2 db und get user's inffu frum zeere-a. Yuoo cun elsu elloo a user thet hes beee oozeenteeceted by zee veb serfer tu be-a ootumeteecelly edded tu zee Xereya detebese-a und ellooed tu lugeen. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="37" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>No blocks yet. It's possible to add some like &quot;Last messages&quot;, &quot;Registered users&quot; etc.</string>
		<translation>Nu blucks yet. Um de hur de hur de hur. It's pusseeble-a tu edd sume-a leeke-a &quot;Lest messeges&quot;, &quot;Regeestered users&quot; itc.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="46" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="50" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The AuthphpBB2 module has no hooks included at this time.</string>
		<translation>Zee OothphpBB2 mudoole-a hes nu huuks inclooded et thees teeme-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="54" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>TODO List</string>
		<translation>TODO Leest</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="58" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The 0.01 version of the AuthphpBB2 module is just a copy/paste-made module. If there will be realized some usefull functionality in any other Auth module, it will be added here too. Now I just don't know clearly how Xaraya works with all that stuff.</string>
		<translation>Zee 0.01 ferseeun ooff zee OothphpBB2 mudoole-a is joost a cupy/peste-a-mede-a mudoole-a. Iff zeere-a veell be-a reeleezed sume-a useffooll fooncshuneleety in uny oozeer Oot mudoole-a, it veell be-a edded here-a tuu. Noo I joost dun't knoo cleerly hoo Xereya vurks veet ell thet stooffff.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="62" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Extended inffurmeshun ebuoot thees mudoole-a cun be-a fuoond here-a. [mudooles mudoole-a]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authphpbb2/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="66" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
