<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="14" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Privileges module lets you manage &lt;b&gt;access rights&lt;/b&gt; on your site.  Privileges give roles access to certain resources of your choosing. They are the basic components of the security system.</string>
		<translation>Zee Preefileges mudoole-a lets yuoo munege-a &lt;b&gt;eccess reeghts&lt;/b&gt; oon yuoor seete-a. Preefileges geefe-a rules eccess tu certeeen resuoorces ooff yuoor chuuseeng. Zeey ere-a zee beseec cumpunents ooff zee secooreety system.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Here are some of the things you can do with privileges</string>
		<translation>Here-a ere-a sume-a ooff zee theengs yuoo cun du veet preefileges</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="18" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya's privileges are extremely flexible. You can define privileges at the level of site, modules, component classes within modules, or single instances of those classes.</string>
		<translation>Xereye's preefileges ere-a ixtremely flexeeble-a. Yuoo cun deffeene-a preefileges et zee lefel ooff seete-a, mudooles, cumpunent clesses veethin mudooles, oor seengle-a instunces ooff thuse-a clesses. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can use privileges as building blocks. Assemble them into compound privileges tailored to any specific role on the site.</string>
		<translation>Yuoo cun use-a preefileges es booeelding blucks. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Essemble-a zeem intu cumpuoond preefileges teeelured tu uny speceeffic rule-a oon zee seete-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can assign privileges to roles which then pass them on to their children in the roles hierarchy through inheritance.</string>
		<translation>Yuoo cun esseegn preefileges tu rules vheech zeen pess zeem oon tu zeeur cheeldree in zee rules heeererchy thruoogh inhereetunce-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="22" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Using the realms functionality you can subdivide one site into many &quot;virtual&quot; sites sharing the same resources.</string>
		<translation>Useeng zee reelms fooncshuneleety yuoo cun soobdeefide-a oone-a seete-a intu muny &quot;furtooel&quot; seetes shereeng zee seme-a resuoorces. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Clicking on the View Privileges link gives you an overview of all the privileges on your system. Compound privileges are collapsed, but you can click on them to open them up and view their components.</string>
		<translation>Cleecking oon zee Feeoo Preefileges leenk geefes yuoo un ooferfeeoo ooff ell zee preefileges oon yuoor system. Cumpuoond preefileges ere-a cullepsed, boot yuoo cun cleeck oon zeem tu oopee zeem up und feeoo zeeur cumpunents. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>When adding or modifying a privilege, you can define it to have its own access rights, or simply to serve as a container for other privileges</string>
		<translation>Vhee eddeeng oor mudeeffying a preefilege-a, yuoo cun deffeene-a it tu hefe-a its oovn eccess reeghts, oor seemply tu serfe-a es a cunteeener fur oozeer preefileges</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="32" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya comes preconfigured with a minimal set of privileges that are loaded when you run the installer. These will vary according to the configuration you chose. Examples are</string>
		<translation>Xereya cumes precunffeegoored veet a meenimel set ooff preefileges thet ere-a lueded vhee yuoo roon zee insteller. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! Zeese-a veell fery eccurdeeng tu zee cunffeegooreshun yuoo chuse-a. Ixemples ere</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;Administration&lt;/b&gt;: a privilege that gives a role complete access to all resources on the site. At installation this privilege is assigned to the role Administrators and is inherited by the user Admin.</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;Edmeenistreshun&lt;/b&gt;: a preefilege-a thet geefes a rule-a cumplete-a eccess tu ell resuoorces oon zee seete-a. Et instelleshun thees preefilege-a is esseegned tu zee rule-a Edmeenistreturs und is inhereeted by zee user Edmeen. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;CasualAccess&lt;/b&gt;: this is the privilege assigned to unregistered users on the site. It is initially defined to allow viewing access of the front page, as well as access to the login block.</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;CesooelEccess&lt;/b&gt;: thees is zee preefilege-a esseegned tu unregeestered users oon zee seete-a. It is ineetielly deffeened tu elloo feeooing eccess ooff zee frunt pege-a, es vell es eccess tu zee lugeen bluck.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;b&gt;GeneralLock&lt;/b&gt;: a privilege that restricts access to certain basic roles and privileges the system requires, such as the default admin. This is to avoid inadvertent removal.</string>
		<translation>&lt;b&gt;GenerelLuck&lt;/b&gt;: a preefilege-a thet restreects eccess tu certeeen beseec rules und preefileges zee system reqooures, sooch es zee deffoolt edmeen. Bork bork bork! Thees is tu efueed inedfertent remufel.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="37" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>All privileges in the system can be changed or removed. (For those protected by GeneralLock above this takes a bit more doing.) You can also combine privileges by using them as elements to create compound privileges, or make new privileges of your choosing. There is no limit to the number of privileges you can create or their levels of nesting.</string>
		<translation>Ell preefileges in zee system cun be-a chunged oor remufed. Bork bork bork! (Fur thuse-a prutected by GenerelLuck ebufe-a thees tekes a beet mure-a dueeng.) Yuoo cun elsu cumbeene-a preefileges by useeng zeem es ilements tu creete-a cumpuoond preefileges, oor meke-a noo preefileges ooff yuoor chuuseeng. Zeere-a is nu leemit tu zee noomber ooff preefileges yuoo cun creete-a oor zeeur lefels ooff nesteeng.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included blocks</string>
		<translation>Zeere-a ere-a nu inclooded blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="45" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="48" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included hooks.</string>
		<translation>Zeere-a ere-a nu inclooded huuks. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="51" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found in</string>
		<translation>Extended inffurmeshun ebuoot thees mudoole-a cun be-a fuoond in</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/privileges/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="54" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
