<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
<entry><string>Julian</string><translation>Julian</translation></entry>
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>What is het?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Julian is the Basic Calendar for Xaraya.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>It is currently responsible for accomplishing these tasks:</string><translation>Het is momenteel mogelijk om de volgende taken uit te voeren:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Display a calendar for day, week, month or year.</string><translation>Toon een kalender voor dag, week, maand of jaar.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Display events for a given date.</string><translation>Toon gebeurtenissen op een bepaalde datum.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Send out an alert with the upcoming events</string><translation>Verstuur meldingen met komende gebeurtenissen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Hoe te gebruiken?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use it like a calendar.</string><translation>Gebruik het als een kalender.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Julian has some requirements at this moment.</string><translation>Julian heeft op dit moment enkele benodigdheden.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The dependancies should have been resolved at installation, otherwise you are not seeing this page.</string><translation>De afhankelijkheden zouden nu opgelost moeten zijn, anders zou u deze pagina niet te zien krijgen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Bijgevoegde blokken</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Month Calendar. This block shows a graphical representation of the current month.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Today's Events and Upcoming Events. This block shows a short list of the events of today and for the upcoming X days. You can set the amount of days in the future you want the block to show.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Security</string><translation>Veiligheid</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Julian has a full set of security levels. The checks are carried out on:</string><translation>Julian beschikt over een complete set van beveilligingsregels. De regels gebruiken:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Event ID.</string><translation>Evenement ID</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Calendar ID (not in use at present).</string><translation>Kalender ID (momenteel niet in gebruik)</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Category ID. This check works together with the category privileges. You will need to give users read or edit level access to the Julian categories as well.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Owner or Organizer ID. This is the user that has entered the event. In future we will implement the use of 'MYSELF' as a check.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Bijgevoegde Hooks</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Julian offers a hook that will enable you to hook any content type to the calendar.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The hook shows an input form with all the information needed. You can attach this hook to your own publication type for instance.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>In your pubtype, you can then add the data needed by Julian to show the event in the calendar.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The hook has been tested with various modules like articles and example. It will work with any module that provides a clear userapi-getitemlinks function.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Known Bugs</string><translation>Bekende bugs</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Program can't view dates in the year 2038 or beyond on 32bit *nix machines.</string><translation>Programma kan geen data bekijken in het jaar 2038 of hoger op 32bit *nix machines.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The alert subscriptions cannot be migrated from earlier version to 0.2.1. Users need to subscribe again.</string><translation>De waarschuwings berichten kunnen niet gemigreerd worden vanaf een versie vroeger dan 0.2.1. Gebruikers moeten zich opnieuw inschrijven.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the Julian module can be found at</string><translation>Meer informatie over de Julian module kan worden gevonden op</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Julian Extension page at</string><translation>de Julian extensie pagina</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Julian Module - Xaraya Extension 319</string><translation>Julian module - Xaraya extensie 319</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on Julian can be found at</string><translation>Gerelateerde documentatie over Julian kan gevonden worden op</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on Julian</string><translation>Gerelateerde documentatie over Julian</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation>Xaraya documentatie</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Julian Module - Overview</string><translation>Julian Module - Overzicht</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation>Versie</translation></entry>
</translations>
