<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="es_MX.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>A glimpse into Xaraya's Theme System</string>
		<translation>Un vistazo al Sistema de Dise&amp;#241;os de Xaraya</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main-glimpse.xt" line="1" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>A feature of Xaraya is it's powerful &lt;a href=&quot;http://xaraya.com/documentation/rfcs/rfc0010.html&quot;&gt;Blocklayout Theme System&lt;/a&gt;
providing you with the flexibility you need for complete control of your theme design.</string>
		<translation>Una caracter&amp;#237;stica de Xaraya es su poderoso &lt;a href=&quot;http://xaraya.com/documentation/rfcs/rfc0010.html&quot;&gt;Sistema de Dise&amp;#241;os Blocklayout&lt;/a&gt;, que te brinda la flexibilidad que necesitas para un completo control de tu dise&amp;#241;o.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main-glimpse.xt" line="7" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This particular page is an example of content written in
an &lt;em&gt;override&lt;/em&gt; template and located in (#(1)/themename/modules/base/user-main.xt).
The template overrides the original that is located in the &lt;em&gt;base&lt;/em&gt; module.
This means its content is determined by the active theme in a Xaraya installation and not by the &lt;em&gt;internal&lt;/em&gt; template
which is part of the standard code and templates of Xaraya. This template also contains some simple blocklayout as an example.</string>
		<translation>Esta p&amp;#225;gina en particular es un ejemplo de contenido escrito en una plantilla de &lt;em&gt;superposici&amp;#243;n&lt;/em&gt; y localizada en (#(1)/themename/modules/base/user-main.xt). La plantilla se superpone al original que est&amp;#225; localizado en el m&amp;#243;dulo &lt;em&gt;base&lt;/em&gt;. Esto significa que su contenido est&amp;#225; determinado por el dise&amp;#241;o activo en la instalaci&amp;#243;n de Xaraya y no por la plantilla &lt;em&gt;interna&lt;/em&gt; que es parte del c&amp;#243;digo y plantillas est&amp;#225;ndares de Xaraya. Esta plantilla tambi&amp;#233;n contiene un poco de blocklayout como ejemplo.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main-glimpse.xt" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Of course, this is a tiny peek into Xaraya's templates and just the tip
of the iceberg. When you decide to use Xaraya, you'll get to know the templating
system in far more detail, but a good start is to have a look at the contents of
the file mentioned above.</string>
		<translation>Por supuesto, esta es una peque&amp;#241;a ojeada a las plantillas de Xaraya y s&amp;#243;lo la punta del iceberg. Cuando decidas utilizar Xaraya, aprender&amp;#225;s el sistema de emplantillado en mucho mayor detalle, pero un buen inicio es el leer los contenidos del archivo mencionado arriba.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main-glimpse.xt" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
