<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya is currently in the beta development phase</string>
		<translation>Xereya is coorrently in zee beta defelupment phese</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/XBlue_Pro/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="7" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you notice any unexpected functionality, please use our bug tracker at</string>
		<translation>Iff yuoo nuteece-a uny unexpected fooncshuneleety, pleese-a use-a oooor boog trecker et</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/XBlue_Pro/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Thank you for your support, and feel free to join our development or user discussions to become involved in our community.</string>
		<translation>Thunk yuoo fur yuoor sooppurt, und feel free-a tu jueen oooor defelupment oor user deescoossiuns tu becume-a infulfed in oooor cummooneety. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/XBlue_Pro/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>For more information on Xaraya, please visit</string>
		<translation>Fur mure-a inffurmeshun oon Xereya, pleese-a feesit</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/XBlue_Pro/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="26" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>P.S. Messages on this page are made out of static templates. However, they can be edited in the overridden template file for the base module; the template is located on this path:</string>
		<translation>P.S. Messeges oon thees pege-a ere-a mede-a oooot ooff steteec templetes. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Hooefer, zeey cun be-a ideeted in zee ooferreeddee templete-a feele-a fur zee bese-a mudoole-a; zee templete-a is luceted oon thees pet:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/XBlue_Pro/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
