<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="hu_HU.utf-8">
<entry><string>MetaWeblog API Administration</string><translation>MetaWeblog API adminisztrálása</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Overview</string><translation>Áttekintés</translation></entry>
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Mi ez?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The MetaWeblog API is a XML-RPC API used for blogging.
It is basically an extended version of the original blogger API,
where the format of the messages which can be passed between a client
and a server is more structured and more rich. Additional support
for categorizing posts and integrating other media (like pictures)
makes this API more attractive for blogging.</string><translation>A MetaWeblog API egy XML-RPC API melyet a blogok használnak. Ez tulajdonképpen az eredeti blogger API továbbfejlesztett változata, amely a kiszolgáló és a kliens közötti üzenetek formátumát rendezettebbé tette és kibővítette. Az új lehetőségek között szerepel a cikkek kategorizálása és a további adatformátumok (például képek) kezelése is.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can find the specification of the MetaWeblog API at</string><translation>A MetaWeblog API pontos leírása:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How does it work?</string><translation>Hogyan kell használni?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation>További információk</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the Metaweblogapi module can be found at</string><translation>További információk a modulról:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Metaweblogapi Extension page at</string><translation>A Metaweblog API modul bővítmény oldala</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Metaweblogapi Module - Xaraya Extension 747</string><translation>Metaweblog API modul - Xaraya bővítmény: 747</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation>A „Version History” fülre kattintva található információ a legfrissebb kiadásról.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on Metaweblogapi found at</string><translation>A modulhoz kapcsolódó oktatóanyagok és dokumentáció:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on Metaweblogapi</string><translation>A modulhoz kapcsolódó dokumentáció.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation>Xaraya dokumentáció.</translation></entry>
</translations>
