<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Authinvision Module Overview</string>
		<translation>Ootheenfisiun Mudoole-a Ooferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="9" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Authinvision module allows you to authenticate a user with your Invision Board database.  The Authinvision module checks the username and password from the login screen against the Invision database and returns true for a match.</string>
		<translation>Zee Ootheenfisiun mudoole-a elloos yuoo tu oozeenteecete-a a user veet yuoor Infeesiun Buerd detebese-a. Zee Ootheenfisiun mudoole-a checks zee userneme-a und pessvurd frum zee lugeen screee egeeenst zee Infeesiun detebese-a und retoorns trooe-a fur a metch.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="16" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Authinvision &lt;strong&gt;does not&lt;/strong&gt; log users into both systems at once, nor does it allow users who register on xaraya to have their user information duplicated in the Invision database.  &lt;strong&gt;It is highly suggested that you turn off xaraya registration and use your Invision board's registration/password retrieval process.&lt;/strong&gt;</string>
		<translation>Ootheenfisiun &lt;strong&gt;dues nut&lt;/strong&gt; lug users intu but systems et oonce-a, nur dues it elloo users vhu regeester oon xereya tu hefe-a zeeur user inffurmeshun doopleeceted in zee Infeesiun detebese-a. &lt;strong&gt;It is heeghly sooggested thet yuoo toorn ooffff xereya regeestreshun und use-a yuoor Infeesiun buerd's regeestreshun/pessvurd retreeefel prucess. Um gesh dee bork, bork!&lt;/strong&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="22" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Authentication by Authinvision is automatically set once the the Authinvision module has been initialized.   You must configure Authinvision before a user will be able to login to Xaraya.  To remove Authinvision authentication, you must remove the module.</string>
		<translation>Oozeenteeceshun by Ootheenfisiun is ootumeteecelly set oonce-a zee zee Ootheenfisiun mudoole-a hes beee ineetielized. Bork bork bork! Yuoo moost cunffeegoore-a Ootheenfisiun beffure-a a user veell be-a eble-a tu lugeen tu Xereya. Tu remufe-a Ootheenfisiun oozeenteeceshun, yuoo moost remufe-a zee mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have one choice.  &quot;Modify Config&quot;.</string>
		<translation>Frum zee menoo, yuoo hefe-a oone-a chueece-a. &quot;Mudeeffy Cunffeeg&quot;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Config -- From here, you can configure the authinvision server that will be used for authentication.   A user that has account information in Invision to be automatically added to the Xaraya database and allowed to login.</string>
		<translation>Mudeeffy Cunffeeg -- Frum here-a, yuoo cun cunffeegoore-a zee ootheenfisiun serfer thet veell be-a used fur oozeenteeceshun. A user thet hes eccuoont inffurmeshun in Infeesiun tu be-a ootumeteecelly edded tu zee Xereya detebese-a und ellooed tu lugeen.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="37" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>usercp: a block that mimics the user links from Invision.</string>
		<translation>usercp: a bluck thet meemics zee user leenks frum Infeesiun. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>whos_online.php: a who's online block that replaces the one in the roles module.</string>
		<translation>vhus_oonleene-a.php: a vhu's oonleene-a bluck thet repleces zee oone-a in zee rules mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authinvision/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="41" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
