<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>official icon</string>
		<translation>Officieel icoon</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="12" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Overzicht</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="16" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Wat is het?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The mail module controls the ways that your Xaraya system sends mail to users or groups of users. This module is a utility module and takes information from other modules installed on your Xaraya system and formats the mail for them. This module at its heart is using the</string>
		<translation>De mailmodule beheert de mogelijkheden voor het versturen van mail naar gebruikers en groepen van gebruikers. Deze module is een zgn. utility module en gebruikt informatie van andere modules om de mailberichten vorm te geven. Deze module is voor een groot deel gebaseerd op</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="26" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>phpmailer</string>
		<translation>phpmailer</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>classes for processing. These classes extend Xaraya to allow you to use SMTP, SendMail or the normal PHP Mail functions.</string>
		<translation>klassen voor de mailverwerking. Deze klassen breiden Xaraya uit met mogelijkheden voor SMTP, SendMail of de gebruikelijke PHP mail functies</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="34" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoe te gebruiken?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have three choices.</string>
		<translation>Vanuit het menu heeft u drie keuzes.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="44" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Test Configuration: From this menu option you can test your mail system configuration.</string>
		<translation>Test configuratie: vanuit deze menu optie kunt u de configuratie van het mail systeem testen.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="50" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Notification Template: From this menu option you can edit the templates of mail messages sent for notifications.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Configuration: From this menu option, you can update the necessary configuration options, such as the email address that you want to send from, reply to address, type of mail system to use, etc.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="60" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Scheduling Mail</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="66" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Other modules can request that a certain mail be sent no earlier than a specific time.</string>
		<translation>Andere modules kunnen een verzoek indienen om een bepaald mailbericht te versturen, niet eerder dan een bepaalde ingestelde tijd.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="71" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This will have no effect unless you install the 'scheduler' module first.</string>
		<translation>Dit zal geen effect hebben tenzij u ook de 'scheduler' module installeert.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="77" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>In order to support that, you can configure the mail module to use the 'scheduler' and check if any mails need to be sent e.g. every x hours. Otherwise, those mails will be sent immediately.</string>
		<translation>Om dat te kunnen ondersteunen, kunt u de mail module configureren om de 'scheduler' te gebruiken, die controleert dan of er mail verstuurt moet worden. In andere gevallen zal de mail direct worden verstuurd.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="83" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Bijgevoegde blokken</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="94" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Mail Module has no blocks included at this time.</string>
		<translation>De mailmodule heeft op dit moment geen bijgevoegde blokken</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="99" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Bijgevoegde hooks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="104" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The mail hook allows you to send an email to the site admin when something (content, users, etc) is created or deleted. This can be configured in the modules module.</string>
		<translation>De mailmodule ondersteunt de mogelijkheid een mailbericht te versturen wanneer een item in een andere module wordt aangemaakt of verwijderd. Dit kan in de 'modules' module worden ingesteld.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="109" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Uitgebreide informatie over deze module kan worden gevonden op</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/mail/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="117" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
