<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="es_ES.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>A glimpse into Xaraya</string>
		<translation>Una introducción a Xaraya</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/glimpse.xt" line="1" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The contents of this page are written in what we call an
&lt;em&gt;overridden&lt;/em&gt; template (in this case one from the base module). This means
that its contents are determined by the active theme in a Xaraya installation
and not by the &lt;em&gt;internal&lt;/em&gt; template, which is part of the standard code
and templates of Xaraya.</string>
		<translation>En contenido de esta página está escrito en lo que se llama un plantilla &lt;em&gt;sobreescrita&lt;/em&gt; (en este caso, una del módulo Base). Esto significa que su contenido es determinado por el diseño activo en la instalación de Xaraya y no por la plantilla &lt;em&gt;interna&lt;/em&gt;, que es parte del código y plantillas estandar de Xaraya.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/glimpse.xt" line="9" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This overridden template you are looking at is located in
(#(1)/themename/modules/base/user-main.xt). The template is part of the
&lt;em&gt;base&lt;/em&gt; module which is by default configured to be the active module on
the frontpage of a Xaraya installation.</string>
		<translation>Esta plantilla que está viendo se encuentra en (#(1)/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt). Es parte del módulo Base, que es el módulo configurado por defecto para aparecer en la página de inicio en la instalación de Xaraya.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/glimpse.xt" line="16" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Of course, the above tiny peek into Xaraya's templates is just the tip
of the iceberg. When you decide to use Xaraya, you'll get to know the templating
system in far more detail, but a good start is to have a look at the contents of
the file mentioned above.</string>
		<translation>Por supuesto, esto es solo la punta del iceberg de las plantillas en Xaraya. Cuando se decida a usarlo, encontrará que el sistema de plantillas tiene muchos detalles, pero es buena idea echar un vistazo al contenido de las plantillas mencionadas antes.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/glimpse.xt" line="24" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
