<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="hu_HU.utf-8">
<entry><string>You must enable cookies on your browser to run Xaraya. Check the browser configuration options to make sure cookies are enabled, click on the "Back" button of the browser and try again.</string><translation>A Xaraya használatához a böngészőben a sütiket engedélyezni kell. A beállítás ellenőrzése után nyomjuk meg a „Vissza” gombot és ismét próbáljuk meg a bejelentkezést.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Your account has been locked for #(1) minutes.</string><translation>Ez a felhasználói bejelentkezés #(1) percre lezárásra került.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You must provide a username.</string><translation>A felhasználónév megadása kötelező.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>You must provide a password.</string><translation>A jelszó megadása kötelező.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Problem logging in: Invalid username or password.</string><translation>Bejelentkezési hiba: Érvénytelen felhasználónév vagy jelszó.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Your account has been terminated by your request or at the administrator's discretion.</string><translation>A bejelentkezés saját kérésre vagy az adminisztrátor döntése alapján lezárásra került.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Your account has been marked as inactive. Contact the administrator if you have further questions.</string><translation>A bejelentkezés inaktív. Az aktiválást az adminisztrátor végezheti el.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Problem logging in: Invalid username or password. Your account has been locked for #(1) minutes.</string><translation>Bejelentkezési hiba: Érvénytelen felhasználónév vagy jelszó. Ez a felhasználói bejelentkezés #(1) percre lezárásra került.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Problem logging in: Invalid username or password. You have tried to log in #(1) times.</string><translation>Bejelentkezési hiba: Érvénytelen felhasználónév vagy jelszó. #(1) bejelentkezési kísérlet történt.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Home Page</string><translation>Honlap</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Your account has not yet been activated by the site administrator</string><translation>A bejelentkezést az adminisztrátor még nem érvényesítette.</translation></entry>
</translations>
