<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="de_DE.utf-8">
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Wozu dient es?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The BBCode module allows you to use BBCode style mark-up in your content instead of, or with, HTML mark-up.</string><translation>Mit dem BBCode-Modul kann man BBCode zur Textformatierung nutzen, anstelle von oder in Verbindung mit HTML.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Adding custom bb-code is available. This is a three step process. First, you will need to add the tag to the system via the &quot;add&quot; function in your admin. Secondly, you will need to add the corresponding API function to html/modules/bbcode/xaruserapi folder. Examples are included. Finally, you will need to add a template for this function in the html/modules/bbcode/xartemplates or to your theme directly. This can be resource intensive. If you do not want to use the advanced bb-code, turn the option off in the modify configuration section. The advance bbcode can also be used to create custom functions to your content, by which you have the ability to place blocks, etc, into your content. This functionality is advanced, but an example has been provided via the [you] tag which transform to the reader's name.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Dazugehörige Blöcke</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The BBCode Module has no blocks included at this time.</string><translation>...sind derzeit nicht vorhanden.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Dazugehörige Hooks</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The BBCode has transform hooks on the output, and form control hooks on the input to allow insertion of BBCode in content.</string><translation>Der BBCode verwendet Transform-Hooks auf der Ausgabeseite und Form-Kontroll-Hooks für die Eingabe, um die Einfügung des BBCode in den Inhalt vorzunehmen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation>Weitere Information</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the BBCode module can be found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>BBCode Extension page at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>BBCode Module - Xaraya Extension 778</string><translation>BBCode-Modul - Xaraya Erweiterung778</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on BBCode found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on BBCode</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation>Xaraya-Dokumentation.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>BBCode Module - Overview</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation>Version</translation></entry>
</translations>
