<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="14" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The CacheSecurity module provides an admin user interface to control the settings of the Security Caching system of Xaraya.</string>
		<translation>Zee CecheSecooreety mudoole-a prufeedes un edmeen user interffece-a tu cuntrul zee setteengs ooff zee Secooreety Cecheeng system ooff Xereya.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The security cache system is designed to reduce the amount of work a server system has to do under heavy load conditions. It saves parts of the security checks calls in a way to minimize the necessary work and database calls to return the security check.</string>
		<translation>Zee secooreety ceche-a system is deseegned tu redooce-a zee emuoont ooff vurk a serfer system hes tu du under heefy lued cundeeshuns. Um gesh dee bork, bork! It sefes perts ooff zee secooreety checks cells in a vey tu meenimize-a zee necessery vurk und detebese-a cells tu retoorn zee secooreety check.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Please do not confuse security caching with Xaraya's variable, template or output caching systems. Each are different. In time, they will likely use the same caching infrastructure, but will still provide different caching for different purposes.  General data caching is also planned for xarCache.</string>
		<translation>Pleese-a du nut cunffoose-a secooreety cecheeng veet Xereye's fereeeble-a, templete-a oor ooootpoot cecheeng systems. Iech ere-a deefffferent. Um de hur de hur de hur. In teeme-a, zeey veell leekely use-a zee seme-a cecheeng inffrestrooctoore-a, boot veell steell prufeede-a deefffferent cecheeng fur deefffferent poorpuses. Generel deta cecheeng is elsu plunned fur xerCeche-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Cache Security module has several tools for managing the Cache Security system.  The tools are organized under the following menu links:</string>
		<translation>Zee Ceche-a Secooreety mudoole-a hes seferel tuuls fur munegeeng zee Ceche-a Secooreety system. Zee tuuls ere-a oorguneezed under zee fullooeeng menoo leenks:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Synchronize All - synchronizes all of the security caches at once.</string>
		<translation>Synchruneeze-a Ell - synchruneezes ell ooff zee secooreety ceches et oonce-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Synchronize Roles Structure - synchronizes just the security roles structure cache.</string>
		<translation>Synchruneeze-a Rules Strooctoore-a - synchruneezes joost zee secooreety rules strooctoore-a ceche-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Synchornize Privileges Structure - synchronizes just the security privileges structure cache.</string>
		<translation>Synchurneeze-a Preefileges Strooctoore-a - synchruneezes joost zee secooreety preefileges strooctoore-a ceche-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="37" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Synchronize Masks - synchronizes just the security masks cache.</string>
		<translation>Synchruneeze-a Mesks - synchruneezes joost zee secooreety mesks ceche-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Synchornize Privileges - synchronizes just the security privileges cache.</string>
		<translation>Synchurneeze-a Preefileges - synchruneezes joost zee secooreety preefileges ceche-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Turns On/Off - Turn the security caching on and off.</string>
		<translation>Toorns Oon/Ooffff - Toorn zee secooreety cecheeng oon und ooffff.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/cachesecurity/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
