<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Administration - Articles</string>
		<translation>Edmeenistreshun - Erteecles</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="2" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="10" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Articles is a Xaraya Content Module responsible for the handling of generic and complex content structures.</string>
		<translation>Erteecles is a Xereya Cuntent Mudoole-a respunseeble-a fur zee hundleeng ooff genereec und cumplex cuntent strooctoores. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If this is your first visit to this part of your Xaraya site,
                please take a minute to read through the following introduction,
                in order to explore the different possibilities offered by the
                articles module.</string>
		<translation>Iff thees is yuoor furst feesit tu thees pert ooff yuoor Xereya seete-a, pleese-a teke-a a meenoote-a tu reed thruoogh zee fullooeeng intrudoocshun, in oorder tu ixplure-a zee deefffferent pusseebilities ooffffered by zee erteecles mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>1. Publication types</string>
		<translation>1. Poobleeceshun types</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The articles module can manage 'articles' of different types at
                the same time, for instance news articles, longer documents in
                different sections, frequently asked questions, and so on.</string>
		<translation>Zee erteecles mudoole-a cun munege-a 'erteecles' ooff deefffferent types et zee seme-a teeme-a, fur instunce-a noos erteecles, lunger ducooments in deefffferent secshuns, freqooently esked qooesshuns, und su oon. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>These types are called 'publication types', and each type of article
                can make use of a different set of data fields, with a different
                meaning for each data field. For example, the 'summary' field
                could be used for an Introduction in news articles, for providing
                some details about a question in FAQs, or not be used at all for
                section documents.</string>
		<translation>Zeese-a types ere-a celled 'poobleeceshun types', und iech type-a ooff erteecle-a cun meke-a use-a ooff a deefffferent set ooff deta feeelds, veet a deefffferent meuneeng fur iech deta feeeld. Fur ixemple-a, zee 'soommery' feeeld cuoold be-a used fur un Intrudoocshun in noos erteecles, fur prufeeding sume-a deteeels ebuoot a qooesshun in FEQs, oor nut be-a used et ell fur secshun ducooments.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There is a specific menu where you can manage those &lt;strong&gt;publication types&lt;/strong&gt;,
                change the description that will appear in navigation menus, enable and
                disable data fields or change their meaning for a particular type, or 
                even create or delete publication types according to your needs.</string>
		<translation>Zeere-a is a speceeffic menoo vhere-a yuoo cun munege-a thuse-a &lt;strong&gt;poobleeceshun types&lt;/strong&gt;, chunge-a zee descreepshun thet veell eppeer in nefeegeshun menoos, ineble-a und deeseble-a deta feeelds oor chunge-a zeeur meuneeng fur a perteecooler type-a, oor ifee creete-a oor delete-a poobleeceshun types eccurdeeng tu yuoor needs.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Each publication type also has its own templates, so that you can
                customize the look &amp; feel of how each article will appear to your
                visitors.</string>
		<translation>Eech poobleeceshun type-a elsu hes its oovn templetes, su thet yuoo cun coostumeeze-a zee luuk &amp; feel ooff hoo iech erteecle-a veell eppeer tu yuoor feesiturs. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="44" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>A default set of publication types and templates (corresponding
                to the old News, Sections and FAQs modules, if you're familiar with
                earlier versions of PostNuke or PHP-Nuke) is included as part of the
                installation.</string>
		<translation>A deffoolt set ooff poobleeceshun types und templetes (currespundeeng tu zee oold Noos, Secshuns und FEQs mudooles, iff yuoo're-a femeelier veet ierleeer ferseeuns ooff PustNooke-a oor PHP-Nooke-a) is inclooded es pert ooff zee instelleshun.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="49" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2. Categories</string>
		<translation>2. Cetegureees</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="52" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Articles (of any type) can be organised into categories. You could use
                one or more common categories across different publication types, or
                use specific categories for each type of article, or any combination
                that you might prefer for your site.</string>
		<translation>Erteecles (ooff uny type-a) cun be-a oorguneesed intu cetegureees. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Yuoo cuoold use-a oone-a oor mure-a cummun cetegureees ecruss deefffferent poobleeceshun types, oor use-a speceeffic cetegureees fur iech type-a ooff erteecle-a, oor uny cumbeeneshun thet yuoo meeght preffer fur yuoor seete-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="56" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Before you start specifying which article types will be using what categories,
                you should create the categorization you want via the
                &lt;a href=&quot;index.php?module=categories&amp;amp;type=admin&quot;&gt;Categories&lt;/a&gt;
                administration menu. A default set of categories has been defined for
                articles when you installed this module, as an example to get you started.
                (You can adapt the categories later on, of course.)</string>
		<translation>Beffure-a yuoo stert speceeffying vheech erteecle-a types veell be-a useeng vhet cetegureees, yuoo shuoold creete-a zee cetegureezeshun yuoo vunt feea zee &lt;a href=&quot;index.php?module=categories&amp;amp;type=admin&quot;&gt;Ceteguries&lt;/a&gt; edmeenistreshun menu. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! A deffoolt set ooff cetegureees hes beee deffeened fur erteecles vhee yuoo instelled thees mudoole-a, es un ixemple-a tu get yuoo sterted. (Yuoo cun edept zee cetegureees leter oon, ooff cuoorse-a.)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="63" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Once you have a set of categories you would like to use for your articles,
                you can go to &lt;strong&gt;Articles Configuration&lt;/strong&gt;, and specify the number
                of categories that can be used for each publication type, and the 'base
                categories' to be used.</string>
		<translation>Once-a yuoo hefe-a a set ooff cetegureees yuoo vuoold leeke-a tu use-a fur yuoor erteecles, yuoo cun gu tu &lt;strong&gt;Erteecles Cunffeegooreshun&lt;/strong&gt;, und speceeffy zee noomber ooff cetegureees thet cun be-a used fur iech poobleeceshun type-a, und zee 'bese-a cetegureees' tu be-a used. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="68" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>A 'base category' is any starting point somewhere in your tree of categories,
                below which you will have the actual list (or subtree) of categories people
                can choose from when they submit or view articles. For example, you could have
                a 'base category' called Topics, with a list of different topics relevant to
                your site below it, and another 'base category' called Cities, with a
                list of cities or places that you would provide regional news for.</string>
		<translation>A 'bese-a cetegury' is uny sterteeng pueent sumoohere-a in yuoor tree-a ooff cetegureees, beloo vheech yuoo veell hefe-a zee ectooel leest (oor soobtree-a) ooff cetegureees peuple-a cun chuuse-a frum vhee zeey soobmeet oor feeoo erteecles. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Fur ixemple-a, yuoo cuoold hefe-a a 'bese-a cetegury' celled Tupeecs, veet a leest ooff deefffferent tupeecs relefunt tu yuoor seete-a beloo it, und unuzeer 'bese-a cetegury' celled Ceeties, veet a leest ooff ceeties oor pleces thet yuoo vuoold prufeede-a regeeunel noos fur. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="75" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>One topic might be 'Good Restaurants', and one city might 'Brussels', so people
                would be able to browse through any articles about good restaurants in Brussels,
                for instance.</string>
		<translation>One-a tupeec meeght be-a 'Guud Restoorunts', und oone-a ceety meeght 'Broossels', su peuple-a vuoold be-a eble-a tu broose-a thruoogh uny erteecles ebuoot guud restoorunts in Broossels, fur instunce-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="79" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>3. Submitting or adding articles</string>
		<translation>3. Soobmeetting oor eddeeng erteecles</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="81" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>status = submitted, rejected, approved or on frontpage
                (for those pubtypes that use it !)</string>
		<translation>stetoos = soobmeetted, rejected, epprufed oor oon fruntpege-a (fur thuse-a poobtypes thet use-a it !)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="84" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>4. Managing the overview and display of articles per publication type</string>
		<translation>4. Munegeeng zee ooferfeeoo und deespley ooff erteecles per poobleeceshun type</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="86" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>In &lt;strong&gt;Articles Configuration&lt;/strong&gt;, set start view (list/browse), # of
                columns and items, show category links + # of comments (+ performance impact)</string>
		<translation>In &lt;strong&gt;Erteecles Cunffeegooreshun&lt;/strong&gt;, set stert feeoo (leest/broose-a), # ooff culoomns und items, shoo cetegury leenks + # ooff cumments (+ perffurmunce-a impect)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="89" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>+ adapt specific templates!</string>
		<translation>+ edept speceeffic templetes!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="91" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>5. Managing your 'front page'</string>
		<translation>5. Munegeeng yuoor 'ffrunt pege'</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="93" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>cfr. frontpage status and # of columns and items - needs to be extended</string>
		<translation>cffr. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! fruntpege-a stetoos und # ooff culoomns und items - needs tu be-a ixtended</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="95" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>6. Adding counters, ratings, comments, smilies, bb-code etc.</string>
		<translation>6. Eddeeng cuoonters, reteengs, cumments, smeelies, bb-cude-a itc.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="97" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>cfr. hooks + special note on counters</string>
		<translation>cffr. huuks + speceeel nute-a oon cuoonters</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="99" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>7. Organising permissions</string>
		<translation>7. Oorguneesing permeessiuns</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="101" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>this really needs a permissions wizard</string>
		<translation>thees reelly needs a permeessiuns veezerd</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="103" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>8. Short URL support</string>
		<translation>8. Shurt URL sooppurt</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="105" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>overall enable/disable in 'base' admin + specific enable/disable in 'articles'
                admin + use of module aliases</string>
		<translation>oferell ineble-a/deeseble-a in 'bese' edmeen + speceeffic ineble-a/deeseble-a in 'erteecles' edmeen + use-a ooff mudoole-a eleeeses</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="108" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Module aliases seem to be disabled at the moment - uncomment the line in
                includes/xarServer.php if you want to try it out</string>
		<translation>Mudoole-a eleeeses seem tu be-a deesebled et zee mument - uncumment zee leene-a in includes/xarServer.php iff yuoo vunt tu try it oooot</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="111" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="115" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>big</string>
		<translation>beeg</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="119" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>featured items</string>
		<translation>feetoored items</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="120" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>glossary</string>
		<translation>glussery</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="121" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>past</string>
		<translation>pest</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="122" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>random</string>
		<translation>rundum</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="123" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>related</string>
		<translation>releted</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="124" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>top items</string>
		<translation>tup items</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="125" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="129" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Search hook which provides the functionality to search your individual articles.</string>
		<translation>Seerch huuk vheech prufeedes zee fooncshuneleety tu seerch yuoor indeefidooel erteecles. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/articles/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="132" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
