<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="de_DE.utf-8">
<entry><string>Application Form for ice.attest</string><translation>ice.attest Antragsformular</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icesite/modules/eorigin/user-attest-cover.xt" line="57" />
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>#xarModVars::get('eorigin', 'error_message')#</string><translation></translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icesite/modules/eorigin/user-attest-cover.xt" line="66" />
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>In the name and on behalf of our client and applicant mentioned below, identified by password and PIN, we ask you to see and complete the following PDF-documents with the Attestation and Stamp of the Basel Chamber of Commerce, Switzerland.</string><translation>Im Namen und im Auftrag unseres(er) nachfolgend genannten sowie durch persönlichen PIN und Passwort identifizierten Kunden(in) und Antragstellers(in) bitten wir Sie, die unten angehängten Dokumente einzusehen und mit Ihrem Attest zu versehen.</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icesite/modules/eorigin/user-attest-cover.xt" line="78" />
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>Terms and Conditions / Disclaimer:</string><translation>Benutzungsbedingungen / Disclaimer</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icesite/modules/eorigin/user-attest-cover.xt" line="88" />
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>The verification and attestation of this document refer solely to the attached PDF-documents. The original papers and/or documents are not seen or consulted. The client and applicant above-mentioned is fully and exclusively responsible for the content, correctness, authenticity and integrity of the underlying original documents. Any liability for damages in any form or kind is excluded by icetodo Ltd. liab. Co, Basel/Switzerland and Basel Chamber of Commerce, Switzerland. Any liability wich may result of the use or abuse of the present Attestation to the client and applicant and/or to any third person is excluded completely and worldwide. Damages shall mean any incidental, direct, indirect, special, consequential, or punitive damages or loss of any nature whatsoever. icetodo Ltd. liab. Co, Basel, Switzerland and Basel Chamber of Commerce, Switzerland, exclude any warranty for any form of authenticity or explanatory power of the present online-attestation in form of this PDF-document.</string><translation>Zur Überprüfung und Beglaubigung liegen auschliesslich die diesem Dokument angehängten Dokumente vor. Die Originaldokumente werden nicht eingesehen. Der (die) obengenannte Kunde(in) ist ausschliesslich und vollumfänglich für den Inhalt, die Richtigkeit und die Echtheit der zugrundeliegende Originale verantwortlich. Jegliche Haftung für Schäden irgendeiner Form oder Art, welche dem (der) Kunde(in) oder irgendwelchen Dritten durch die Verwendung der vorliegenden Beglaubigung entstehen, wird von der Handelskammer Beider Basel, e-origin und icetodo Ltd. vollumfänglich und weltweit ausgeschlossen. Jegliche Gewährleistung irgendeiner Beweiskraft oder Aussagekraft der ausgestellten online-Beglaubigung wird von der Handelskammer Beider Basel, e-origin und icetodo Ltd. vollumfänglich und weltweit ausgeschlossen.</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icesite/modules/eorigin/user-attest-cover.xt" line="94" />
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>icetodo Ltd. liab. Co, Basel/Switzerland and Basel Chamber of Commerce, Switzerland may amend, modify, change, revise or alter in any manner icetodo Ltd. liab. Co, Basel, Switzerland and Basel Chamber of Commerce, Switzerland deems necessary and its absolute and sole discretion the Terms and Conditions of the Website without notice to you and without your consent.</string><translation></translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icesite/modules/eorigin/user-attest-cover.xt" line="98" />
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>Choice of Law and Venue.</string><translation></translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icesite/modules/eorigin/user-attest-cover.xt" line="103" />
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>The laws of Switzerland and the State of Basel shall govern the applicability, interpretation and validity of this contract. You hereby agree that the State Courts located in the State of Kanton Basel-Stadt, in Switzerland shall be the exclusive venue for any dispute, action, claim or contest arising out of or related in any manner to the Terms and Conditions.</string><translation></translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icesite/modules/eorigin/user-attest-cover.xt" line="105" />
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>The client and applicant confirms that he/she has understood this terms and conditions / disclaimer and accepted it completely.</string><translation>Der (die) Antragsteller(in) erklärt, die Benutzungsbedingungen / Disclaimer verstanden zu haben und diese zu akzeptieren.</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icesite/modules/eorigin/user-attest-cover.xt" line="109" />
		</references>
</entry>
</translations>
