<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Administration - Uploads</string>
		<translation>Edmeenistreshun - Uplueds</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Uploads is a Xaraya Utility Module.</string>
		<translation>Uplueds is a Xereya Uteelity Mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>It is currently responsible for accomplishing these tasks:</string>
		<translation>It is coorrently respunseeble-a fur eccumpleeshing zeese-a tesks:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="18" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Allows for the importing of files into the Xaraya system either locally or externally.</string>
		<translation>Elloos fur zee impurteeng ooff feeles intu zee Xereya system ieezeer lucelly oor ixternelly. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Allows the managing of access to files via privileges.</string>
		<translation>Elloos zee munegeeng ooff eccess tu feeles feea preefileges.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>External Imports and Uploads</string>
		<translation>Externel Impurts und Uplueds</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="32" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Files that are uploaded or imported from external locations can be saved in the database (DB) 
                    or stored in the filesystem (FS). Use the options (FS/DB) under each form to select the 
                    storage location for your file.</string>
		<translation>Feeles thet ere-a uplueded oor impurted frum ixternel luceshuns cun be-a sefed in zee detebese-a (DB) oor stured in zee feelesystem (FS). Use-a zee oopshuns (FS/DB) under iech furm tu select zee sturege-a luceshun fur yuoor feele-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The import engine will try to make a best guess for the name of the file you are trying to import. 
                    In the event that it cannot figure out what the file name is it will use the following methods:</string>
		<translation>Zee impurt ingeene-a veell try tu meke-a a best gooess fur zee neme-a ooff zee feele-a yuoo ere-a tryeeng tu impurt. Um de hur de hur de hur. In zee ifent thet it cunnut feegoore-a oooot vhet zee feele-a neme-a is it veell use-a zee fullooeeng methuds:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="45" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;strong&gt;HTTP and HTTPS&lt;/strong&gt;</string>
		<translation>&lt;strong&gt;HTTP und HTTPS&lt;/strong&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="48" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>In the event that the filename for an HTTP import can not be determined, the file will be 
                                named based on the host name of the server the file was imported from. For example, importing
                                http://www.xaraya.com/ would return a file with the name of www_xaraya_com.html</string>
		<translation>In zee ifent thet zee feeleneme-a fur un HTTP impurt cun nut be-a determeened, zee feele-a veell be-a nemed besed oon zee hust neme-a ooff zee serfer zee feele-a ves impurted frum. Fur ixemple-a, impurteeng http://vvv.xereya.cum/ vuoold retoorn a feele-a veet zee neme-a ooff vvv_xereya_cum.html</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="54" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Due to the underlying nature of the FTP protocol, it is impossible to successfully access a file 
                                on a system without providing a viable file name. In this case, no file name 'guessing' will be 
                                attempted and the import will fail.</string>
		<translation>Dooe-a tu zee underlyeeng netoore-a ooff zee FTP prutucul, it is impusseeble-a tu sooccessffoolly eccess a feele-a oon a system veethuoot prufeeding a feeeble-a feele-a neme-a. In thees cese-a, nu feele-a neme-a 'gooesseeng' veell be-a ettempted und zee impurt veell feeel.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="64" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Local Imports Sandbox</string>
		<translation>Lucel Impurts Sundbux</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="71" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Files can be inserted into your local import sandbox and used immediately by users with sufficient access to 
                    add files and attach them to hooked objects (articles, comments, etc). Files you place in your local import
                    sandbox can be seen in the 'Import Local Files' form immediately upon adding them.</string>
		<translation>Feeles cun be-a inserted intu yuoor lucel impurt sundbux und used immedeeetely by users veet sooffffeecient eccess tu edd feeles und ettech zeem tu huuked oobjects (erteecles, cumments, itc). Feeles yuoo plece-a in yuoor lucel impurt sundbux cun be-a seee in zee 'Impurt Lucel Feeles' furm immedeeetely upun eddeeng zeem.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="78" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="85" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included blocks.</string>
		<translation>Zeere-a ere-a nu inclooded blucks. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="89" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/uploads/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="93" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
