<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="de_DE.utf-8">
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Wozu dient es?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Ratings is a Xaraya Utility Module.</string><translation>Das Bewertungs-Modul ist ein Utility-Modul von Xaraya.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>It is currently responsible for accomplishing these tasks:</string><translation>Es nimmt momentan folgende Aufgaben wahr:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The ratings module is a utility module that allows you to add a rating type to any content module that supports hooks.</string><translation>Das Bewertungs-Modul ist ein Utility-Modul, mit dem man jedem Content-Modul einen Bewertungstyp anfügen kann, sofern dies Modul Hooks unterstützt.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Wie setzt man es ein?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>From the Modules Administration configure the ratings hook with any content module that you would like to allow a rating to happen. You can configure the appearance of the ratings from the configure portion in the ratings administration.</string><translation>Im Administrationsbereich des Module-Moduls lässt sich der Bewertungs-Hook bei jedem Content-Modul einstellen, das Bewertungen haben soll. Das Erscheinungsbild des Bewertungs-Moduls lässt sich im Konfigurationsbereich des Moduls einstellen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Dazugehörige Blöcke</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no included blocks at this time.</string><translation>...sind momentan nicht vorhanden.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Dazugehörige Hooks</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The ratings hook is a display hook to allow content modules to rate content.</string><translation>Der Bewertungs-Hook ist ein Anzeige-Hook, das bei Content-Modulen die Bewertung des Inhalts ermöglicht.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the Ratings module can be found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Ratings Extension page at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Ratings Module - Xaraya Extension 41</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on Ratings found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on Ratings</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Ratings Module Overview</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
