<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;p&gt;Using this administration system is very simple. First, you may want to configure the adminmenu appearance and sorting order of the items in it. 
            Of course, it largely depends on what kind of website you are running and on the number of admin-capable modules you deploy. 
            Experiment with the options provided, and hopefully you will find the best solution for your administrative environment. 
            For instance, position the menu left or right, choose convenient display order and/or temporarily hide modules which you are not going to re-configure frequently. &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Secondly, you may configure this overview panel to show a more useful information than this text. 
            Some options are (will be) available from &quot;Configure Overview&quot; panel. &lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Having done that, you can start using other modules administration facilities. Load other modules by clicking corresponding links in the adminmenu.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;And last, to hide the administration menu, you must logout as admin; to minimise, use collapsible menu option in &quot;blocks&quot; module&lt;/p&gt;</string>
		<translation>&lt;p&gt;Het gebruik van dit beheer systeem is erg eenvoudig. Als eerste wilt u wellicht het uiterlijk van het beheermenu en de items erin aanpassen. Uiteraard is dit afhankelijk van het soort website dat u gaat maken en hoeveel te beheren modules u toepast. Expirimenteer met de geboden opties en al doende komt u tot de meest passende beheeromgeving voor u. Zo kunt u er bijvoorbeeld voor kiezen om het menu aan de rechter- of linkerkant te plaatsen, bepaal de volgorde van te tonen items en/of maak  bepaalde modules tijdelijk onzichtbaar (die u niet regelmatig gebruikt). &lt;/p&gt;   
&lt;p&gt;Daarna wilt u wellicht dit dat dit overzicht een voor u bruikbaardere tekst gaat bevatten. Sommige opties zijn beschikbaar via het &quot;Configureer overzicht&quot; paneel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Als u dit gedaan heeft, kunt u beginnen met het gebruiken van andere beheermogelijkheden. Laad andere modules door erop te klikken in het beheermenu.&lt;/p&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;Ten slotte, om het beheermenu te laten verdwijnen dient u uit te loggen; om te minimaliseren, gebruik inklapbare menu optie in de &quot;blokken&quot; module.&lt;/p&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-view.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
