<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="it_IT.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Thank you for installing and trying Xaraya!</string>
		<translation>Grazie per avere installato e per provare Xaraya!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="4" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya is currently in Beta Production.</string>
		<translation>Xaraia &amp;egrave; attualmente distribuito in versione Beta</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="10" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you notice any unexpected functionality, please use our bug tracker at
&lt;a href=&quot;http://bugs.xaraya.com&quot;&gt;
http://bugs.xaraya.com&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Se noti qualsiasi problema, usa il nostro sistema di controllo bugs all'indirizzo &lt;a href=&quot;http://bugs.xaraya.com&quot;&gt; http://bugs.xaraya.com&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Thank you for your support, and feel free to join our development or user discussions to become involved in our community.</string>
		<translation>Grazie del tuo supporto. Consulta i nostri gruppi di discussione o i nostri forum per collaborare a migliorare Xaraya.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>For more information on Xaraya, please visit
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xaraya.com&quot;&gt;
Xaraya's
&lt;/a&gt;
website.</string>
		<translation>Per maggiori informazioni su Xaraya, visita &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xaraya.com&quot;&gt; Xaraya's &lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This message can be edited by creating an override template (#(1)/themename/modules/base/user-main.xt) for the base module.</string>
		<translation>Questo messaggio pu&amp;ograve; essere modificato modificando il template (modello) (#(1)/themename/modules/base/user-main.xt) del modulo base.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>About the default theme (yes, this one).</string>
		<translation>Il tema preinstallato (questo).</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The default theme's name is Xaraya_Classic. It is supplied and installed with every distribution package of Xaraya.</string>
		<translation>Il tema preinstallato e' Xaraya_Classic.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="47" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Starting from the release 0.9.11 the theme's layout is 100% table-free and is totally CSS driven. It means the theme is now more standards compliant than ever before. However, designing your site with the web-standards in mind requires certain degree of knowledge, experience, attention to detail and patience. So we would advise to keep this theme unmodified within your Xaraya installation directory, in case you need to use it as the (last resource) fallback.</string>
		<translation>Dalla versione 0.9.11 il layout di questo tema e' senza tabelle e completamente visualizzato attraverso CSS. In questo modo, il tema e' piu' conforme agli standards che mai. Progettare un sito scondo gli standards del web richiede conoscenze, esperienza e attenzione ai dettagli. Ti consigliamo di tenere questo tema senza modifiche entro la tua directory di installazione Xaraya, nel caso tu abbia bisogno di usarlo come ultima risorsa.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="52" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you wish to design your own Xaraya theme based on the current layout or alter the appearance of this theme, the graphics sources can be obtained from
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xaraya.com/~andyv/xclassic_sources&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Se vuoi usare questo tema per progettare il tuo tema, le risorse grafiche si possono ottenere &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xaraya.com/~andyv/xclassic_sources&quot;&gt;qui&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main.xt" line="58" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
