<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="de_DE.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>for use within your Xaraya web site. This module allows configuration options via the GUI in the Xaraya Administration area for xarTinyMCE.&amp;nbsp; It has a number
of nice features over similar editors, with&amp;nbsp; multiple browser support, (currently Mozilla, MSIE and FireFox) and support for XHTML 1.0 strict markup. There are powerful
features for not only allowing or disallowing xhtml tags (like the Xaraya HTML module), but also what attributes, and&amp;nbsp; attribute values to allow. You can enhance
xarTinyMCE further with plugins!</string>
		<translation>zur Verwendung auf unserer Xaraya-Website. Dieses Modul bietet Konfigurationsmöglichkeiten mittels der grafischen Benutzeroberfläche im Adminbereich von xarTinyMCE. Es enthält im Vergleich zu ähnlichen Editoren eine Reihe von Features wie mannigfaltigen Browsersupport (aktuell Motilla, MSIE und FireFox) und Unterstützung zur Ausgabe von striktem XHTML 1.0. Die umfangreichen Features regeln nicht nur die Verwendung von xhtml-Tags (wie das HTML-Modul von Xaraya) sondern auch, welche Attribute und Attributwerte erlaubt werden. Sie können xarTinyMCE mit weiteren Plugins erweitern!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="18" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Image Browser (ibrowser) - browse your image libraries and select a file to insert to
your textarea. Upload a file if you have allowed uploads in the configuration. See the configuration area for more detail</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="114" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Dictionary - lookup word in Merriam-Webster Online dictionary.</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="131" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>xarTinyMCE WYSIWYG Editor - Overview</string>
		<translation>xarTinyMCE WYSIWYG Editor - Überblick</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="185" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>before adding new allowed tags and attributes here. Any added elements here are are added to the default with the &lt;strong&gt;extended_valid_elements&lt;/strong&gt;
config option. Separate each tag with a comma. *[*] allows all tags and attributes. If you have HTML module installed, its settings will override and
filter all tags (but not individual attributes).</string>
		<translation>bevor Sie hier neue erlaubte Tags und Attribute hinzufügen. Jedes hier hinzugefügte Element wird zu der Standard &lt;strong&gt;extended_valid_elements&lt;/strong&gt;-Konfigurationsoption hinzugefügt. Trennen Sie jeden Tag durch ein Komma. *[*] erlaubt alle Tags und Attribute. Wenn Sie das HTML-Module installiert haben, setzen dessen Einstellungen alle Tags (aber nicht die Attribute) außer Kraft und filtern diese.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="510" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;strong&gt;Available plugins (bundled):&lt;/strong&gt; save, ibrowser, emotions, iespell (IE only), insertdatetime, preview, zoom,
advimage, advlink, flash, advhr, searchreplace, print, table, xarpagebreak, contextmenu, lorem, dictionary, paste,
fullscreen, directionality, fullpage, liststyle, layer, style, spellchecker</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="652" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Use filebrowser in advanced image, link or flash plugins?</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="684" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>To use FileBrowser, IBrowser or IManager:</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="689" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Add &lt;strong&gt;ibrowser or imanager&lt;/strong&gt; (or plugin that uses filebrowser eg advimage or advlink)&lt;/strong&gt; to the plugins above</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="692" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;strong&gt;HINT:&lt;/strong&gt; Copy &lt;code&gt;modules/tinymce/xartemplates/properties/showinput-tinymce.xd&lt;/code&gt;
to your own theme's &lt;code&gt;themes/yourtheme/modules/base/properties/showinput-textarea.xt&lt;/code&gt; as a DD textarea override
and set to Specially Labelled and Manual loading mode. This way you can have all your pubtype or xarpages or other DD property textarea fields
automatically converted to wysiwyg with or without button prompt, and tinymce is loaded on a page only when needed.&lt;/code&gt;</string>
		<translation>&lt;strong&gt;HINWEIS:&lt;/strong&gt; Kopieren Sie &lt;code&gt;modules/tinymce/xartemplates/properties/showinput-tinymce.xd&lt;/code&gt; in Ihren eigenen Theme-Ordner &lt;code&gt;themes/yourtheme/modules/base/properties/showinput-textarea.xt&lt;/code&gt; als DD-Textbereich-Überschreibung und legen Sie den Modus auf &quot;Speziell gekennzeichnet&quot; und Manuell geladen fest. Auf diese Weise erreichen Sie, dass alle Ihre Publikationstypen, xarpages oder andere DD-Eigenschafts-Textfelder automatisch nach wysiwyg konvertiert werden mit oder ohne Button. Tinymce dann wird bei einer Seite nur geladen, wenn es benötigt wird.&lt;/code&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="201" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Ask user if they wish to use WYSIWYG for each text area?</string>
		<translation>Nutzer fragen, ob sie WYSIWYG für jeden Textbereich einsetzen wollen?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="266" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Prompt to use WYSIWYG?</string>
		<translation>Sofort WYSIWYG verwenden?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="267" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Use a button to prompt for WYSIWYG or default to popup</string>
		<translation>Verwenden Sie einen Button, um WYSIWYG einzusetzen oder standardmäßig ein Popup-Fenster</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="277" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Toggle button instead of popup prompt?</string>
		<translation>Button statt Popup-Fenster verwenden?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="278" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;strong&gt;Available plugins (bundled):&lt;/strong&gt; save, emotions, iespell (IE only), insertdatetime, preview, zoom,
advimage, advlink, flash, advhr, searchreplace, print, table, xarpagebreak, contextmenu, lorem, paste,
fullscreen, directionality, fullpage, liststyle, layer, style, spellchecker, media</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="652" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Add &lt;strong&gt;ibrowser or imanager&lt;/strong&gt; (or any plugin that uses filebrowser eg advimage or advlink)&lt;/strong&gt; to the plugins above</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/tinymce/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="693" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
