<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="ja_JP.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Administration - xarCacheManager</string>
		<translation>キャッシュマネージャー管理</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="2" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>これは何？</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="14" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The xarCacheManager module provides an administrator interface to control the settings of the xarCache system of Xaraya. It also provides hooks that allow the cache system to know when changes have happened to modules so that it can respond accordingly (event based cache expiration/invalidation).</string>
		<translation>キャッシュマネージャーモジュールはXarayaのキャッシュシステムの設定を行う管理者インターフェースを提供します。 またモジュールに変化（イベントベースでのキャッシュ期限切れ/無効化）発生時にキャッシュシステムが正常に反応できるようにフックを提供します</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The output cache system is designed to reduce the amount of work a server system has to do under heavy load conditions. It saves the output used by Xaraya so that it does not need to go through the entire process to reproduce the same output over and over again. At this point, only page level output caching for anonymous users and block level output caching for all users are available. In time, the output cache system will also support module level output caching for all users, as well as more efficient serving of cached pages for anonymous users. Page level output caching for certain user groups is also planed to be available to sites that can take advantage of this.</string>
		<translation>出力キャッシュシステムはサーバーの負荷を軽減します。同じ結果を出力するために全てのプロセスを実行させないようにします。この時点では、匿名ユーザのためのページ単位でのキャッシュ、全てのユーザのためのブロック単位でのキャッシュが可能です。さらに、出力キャッシュシステムは匿名ユーザー用のページキャッシュより効果的なモジュール単位でのキャッシュを全てのユーザーに提供します。特定のユーザーグループごとにページ単位でのキャッシュ化も検討されています。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Please do not confuse output caching with Xaraya's variable or template caching systems. Each are different. In time, they will likely use the same caching infrastructure, but will still provide different caching for different purposes. General data caching is also planned for xarCache. For more on the different points of caching in Xaraya, please refer to:</string>
		<translation>Xarayaの出力キャッシュとXaraya変数またはテンプレートキャッシュシステムと混同しないでください、同じキャッシュ構造を使用してはいますが、別々の理由で別々のキャッシュを行います。一般データキャッシュはxarCacheで検討中です。Xarayaのキャッシュシステムについての情報は次を参照してください：</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>どうやって使うの？</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The xarCacheManager module has several tools for managing the xarCache system and your cached output files. The tools are organized under the following menu links:</string>
		<translation>キャッシュマネージャーモジュールは幾つかのキャッシュシステムと、キャッシュファイルのマネージメントツールを提供しています。それらのツールは：</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Query Caching - Queries in the certain functions could be quite expensive for large sites. You can use this tool to set query caching to save the results of some expensive queries for reuse. Please note that cached query results will only be invalidated based on expiration time.</string>
		<translation>クエリーキャッシュ：いくつかの関数に含まれるクエリーは大規模なサイトでは非常にコストが高くつきます。ページキャッシュやモジュール出力キャッシュを使用しないでも、それぞれのデータベースクエリーをキャッシュすることをお考えください。注：クエリーの結果をキャッシュすると有効期限が切れた時のみ無効になります。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Flush Cache - allows you to flush (delete) the output cache of specific Cache Keys. Page output Cache Keys are define by module, type, and function. Block output Cache Keys are define by module, block instance id, and block group.</string>
		<translation>キャッシュ開放：特定のキャッシュキーによるキャッシュファイルの開放（削除）を行います。ページ出力キャッシュキーはモジュール、タイプ、関数ごとに設定されます。ブロック出力キャッシュはモジュール、ブロック（インスタンス）、ブロックグループごとに設定されます。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Page Caching - allows you to enable page caching for certain user groups, set up session-less page caching, and configure auto-cache settings. Session-less page caching allows cached pages to be served before loading xarCore to users who do not have a session (new/first-time visitors). Auto-cache allows you to configure your site to dynamically enable session-less page caching for pages that hit certain page view thresholds.</string>
		<translation>ページキャッシュ：特定のユーザーグループごとのページキャッシュ、セッション外ページキャッシュの設定、自動キャッシュ設定などを可能にします。セッション外ページキャッシュはビジター、匿名ユーザーなどのセッションシステム外ユーザーへコアを読み込む前にキャッシュページを出力することが可能になります。自動キャッシュは上記セッション外ページキャッシュなどを自動的に設定することが可能になります。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Block Caching - provides a single view and management point of the output caching settings of all block instances.</string>
		<translation>ブロックキャッシュ：ブロック単位でのキャッシュの設定や管理を行います。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="41" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Config - allows you to set the values for the output cache system. Mouse over the setting titles for more information.</string>
		<translation>設定の修正：数値の設定などのキャッシュシステムの設定などを行います。詳しい情報はタイトル上にマウスを移動してください。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>付随するブロック</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="47" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The xarCacheManager Module has no blocks included at this time.</string>
		<translation>なし</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="50" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>付随するフック</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="54" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The xarCacheManager module provides create, update, delete and modify config API hooks and a modify GUI hook (currently only used for adding caching configuration administration to block instance modify pages). To activate these hooks, go to Admin panel -&gt; Modules -&gt; Configure Hooks and click on the xarcachemanager link. Select the modules you would like to enable the xarCacheManager hook functionality for (articles, categories, autolinks, blocks, html are likely candidates) and click the Save Changes button. Once hooked to xarCacheManager, when you create, update, or delete items of the module, or modify the configuration of a module, the call to the xarCacheManager hooks will flush the appropriate cache to insure that your changes will be instantly available on your site (not masked by cached output files).</string>
		<translation>キャッシュマネージャーは作成、更新、削除、修正などのAPIフックと修正のGUIフック（現在はブロックインスタンス編集ページでのキャッシュ設定のみ）を提供します。これらのフックを有効にするには
管理パネル＞モジュール＞フック設定＞キャッシュマネージャーへと移動して、各種記事、カテゴリー、自動リンク、ブロック、HTMLなどのモジュールを有効に設定した設定を保存してください。フックが完了すると、それぞれのモジュールアイテムが作成、更新、削除された時、またはモジュール自体の設定が更新された時にキャッシュマネージャーは自動的に対応したキャッシュファイルを開放します。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="57" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Additional Information</string>
		<translation>追加情報</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="61" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Please note that page level output caching is not appropriate for sites that require the serving of dynamic content to anonymous users. Example: if each page contains data that changes every second and must be presented to the anonymous viewer in the latest state, you do not want to use page level output caching. However, if it is acceptable to present the data with changes no older than 1 minute, you can enable page level output caching and set the Cache Expiration Time to 60 seconds. If your site serves the same page 100 times per minute this will measurably reduce the load on your systems to do so.</string>
		<translation>不特定多数のユーザーに動的なコンテンツを配信するサイトではページ単位でのキャッシュは使用しないでください。例：それぞれのページで毎秒変化するようなデータを配信するサイトでは、常に最新の状態で表示されなければなりませんので、ページ単位でのキャッシュは（未登録/匿名ユーザーとしてキャッシュされてしまうために）適当ではありません。ですが、1分毎などに更新するなどの場合は、ページキャッシュの有効時間を６０秒にセットすることで使用することが出来ます。もし１分間に100回のアクセスがあるようなサイトではサーバー負荷を軽減することが出来ます。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="64" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Page level output caching may also affect the expected behavior of certain aspects of Xaraya as cached pages are served without loading the modules. Example: the stats and opentracker modules will not accurately reflect the total number of page views your site receives because they are not invoked when serving cached pages. If your site is under heavy load that needs to be reduced, you may want to consider doing your site statistic tracking via the web server log files or a javascript based solution like that implemented by Hitbox or WebTrends Live, anyway. Either of these methods will accurately work with page level caching enabled.</string>
		<translation>ページキャッシュはモジュールの呼び出しをせずにキャッシュされたページを出力するために、予期した動作を行わない場合があります。例：統計モジュールとオープントラッカーモジュールはページキャッシュされたページではモジュールが呼び出されないために正確なデータを取得することができなくなります。もし高負荷での軽減を行わなければならないサイトであれば、ウェブサーバーのログファイル、JavascriptベースのHitboxやWebTrends Liveなどの方法で統計を取ることをお勧めします。いずれの場合でもページキャッシュを有効にしながらデータの正確性は増します。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="67" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Block level output caching does not have the same dynamic content limitations. It is purpose-built to allow Xaraya to fully load the core and active module(s) with each page request. Block output caching can be configure on a per block instance basis, so you can have some block instances be fully dynamic (never cached), while other instances are cached for varying lifetimes. The cache of each block instance can be configure to be or not be shared between users (or groups of users) and pages. This allows for very flexible output caching behaviors for sites with mixed static and dynamic pages, but the tradeoff is a much higher fixed cost (page generation time). Where page level output caching can reduce a site's page generation time by 65 to 80% (YMMV depending on site configuration), block level output caching general only reduced page generation time by 20 to 30%.</string>
		<translation>ブロックキャッシュでは動的なコンテンツに対しての制限はありません。Xarayaがそれぞれのリクエストに対しコアと有効なモジュールをくまなく読み込めるように設計されています。ブロックキャッシュはブロック（インスタンス）毎にキャッシュしますので、幾つかのブロックを動的に、幾つかのブロックを静的（キャッシュから）に出力させることが出来ます。このインスタンスごとのキャッシュをユーザー単位（またはグループ単位）、ページ単位でのキャッシュ共有設定ができますので、とても動的、静的コンテンツが混在したサイトでも柔軟な設定ができますが、ページ生成時間には非常に高負荷になります。ページキャッシュではページ生成時間を６５％から８０％くらいまで減少させることが出来ます（サイト設定によります）が、ブロックキャッシュでは大体２０％から３０％くらいまでの減少率となります。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="70" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Page level and block level output caching can be used in tandem to reduce loads and improve page generation times on sites that serve both anonymous and non-anonymous audience members, or on sites with varying page and block level output caching requirements.</string>
		<translation>ページキャッシュとブロックキャッシュを併用して、匿名、登録ユーザーが混在するサイト、または動的なページとブロックキャッシュが組み合ったサイトなどで負荷軽減とページ生成時間の短縮をすることが出来ます。</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="73" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>TODO List</string>
		<translation>TODOリスト</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="77" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>General caching related:</string>
		<translation>全般</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="83" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Support multisite configurations.</string>
		<translation>マルチサイト設定でのサポート</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="85" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Provide data caching API.</string>
		<translation>データキャッシュAPIの提供</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="86" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Provide an output cache file browser, like the template cache file browser in SiteTools.</string>
		<translation>サイトツールのテンプレートキャッシュファイルブラウザーのようなキャッシュファイルブラウザーの提供</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="87" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Refactor, refactor, refactor.</string>
		<translation>リファクタリング・・・</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="88" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Page level output caching related:</string>
		<translation>ページキャッシュ関連</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="94" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Support itemtype as a 'name' between cacheKey and page when available.</string>
		<translation>キャッシュキーとページ間で名前をアイテムタイプとして利用できるようにする</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="96" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Provide Scheduler, getfile/link integration for pre-population of output cache.</string>
		<translation>スケジューラー、ファイル取得/リンクなどの実装</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="97" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Analyze Slashdot and Google News use of 304 &amp;amp; ETag HTTP headers and rework our use of these headers based on findings.</string>
		<translation>スラッシュドットとグーグルニュースの304とETag HTTPヘッダーの解析、これらのヘッダーを使用しての作り直し</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="98" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Block/module level output caching related:</string>
		<translation>ブロック/モジュールキャッシュ関連：</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="104" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Add module output caching functions, reutilizing xarBlock*Cached functions when appropriate.</string>
		<translation>モジュールキャッシュ関数の追加、ブロックキャッシュ関数の追加</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="106" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Add xarMod*Cached() calls in xarModFunc().</string>
		<translation>xarMod*Cached()関数をxarModFunc()に追加</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="107" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Provide Admin GUI hooks to modules beyond Blocks for the configuration of per module output cache settings.</string>
		<translation>ブロックキャッシュと同様のモジュールキャッシュ設定を行う管理者GUIフックの提供</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="108" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>その他の情報は[モジュール　モジュール]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarcachemanager/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="113" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
