<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
<entry><string>Update configuration</string><translation>Ενημέρωση ρυθμίσεων</translation></entry>
<entry><string>ADOdb Cache Path:</string><translation>Διαδρομή Cache ADOdb:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>RSS Cache Path:</string><translation>Διαδρομή Cache RSS:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Template Cache Path:</string><translation>Διαδρομή Cache Υποδειγμάτων:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Backup Path:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use timestamp in backup filename:</string><translation>Χρησιμοποίησει μαρκάρισμα χρόνου στο όνομα αρχείου backup:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use database prefix in backup table create sql:</string><translation>Χρησιμοποίηση του προθέματος βάσης δεδομένων στην εντολή sql δημιουργίας πινάκων:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Line termination type:</string><translation>Τύπος τερματισμού γραμμής:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Cache Options</string><translation>Επιλογές Cache</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The default cache paths are entered below.
Change them only if you have changed default cache directory paths.
Note these should be full paths and there is no trailing slash in the path names.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Check the following carefully, and correct them if necessary.</string><translation>Ελέγξτε τα παρακάτω προσεκτικά και αλλάξτε τα αν απαιτείται.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default ADOdb Cache path is</string><translation>Προεπιλογή διαδρομής cache για την ADOdb</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default RSS Cache path is</string><translation>Προεπιλογή διαδρομής cache για τα RSS</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default Template Cache path is</string><translation>Προεπιλογή διαδρομής cache για τα υποδείγματα</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Relative path from your root document directory to the backup directory on your server, where backup files will be created. It must be writeable chmod 777. No trailing slash.</string><translation>Σχετικές διαδρομές από το αρχικό (root) φάκελο μέχρι τον φάκελο backup όπου θα τοποθετούνται τα σχετικά αρχεία. Δεν θα πρέπει να είναι εγγράψιμο με chmod 777. Δεν θα πρέπει να υπάρχει τελικό slash.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>If checked a time stamp will be added to the backup file name.</string><translation>Αν επιλεγεί μια χρονική σήμανση θα προστεθεί στο όνομα αρχείου backup.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>If checked the database name will prefix all table names in the backup file sql table create statements.</string><translation>Αν επιλεγεί το όνομα της βάσης δεδομένων θα προστεθεί πριν από όλα τα ονόματα πινάκων στις εντολές sql στο αρχείο backup</translation></entry>
<entry><string>*nix (default)</string><translation>*nix (προεπιλογή)</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Windows</string><translation>Windows</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Macintosh</string><translation>Macintosh</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Line terminator - dependent on your database server environment. The *nix option should be fine for most systems. Older systems may require specific selection.</string><translation>Τερματισμός γραμμής - εξαρτάται από το περιβάλλον του server της βάσης δεδομένων. Η επιλογή *nix πρέπει να είναι ικανοποιητική για τα περισσότερα συστήματα. Παλαιότερα συστήματα μπορεί να απαιτήσουν ειδική επιλογή.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Number of columns used to list database tables</string><translation>Αριθμός στηλών που χρειάζονται για τον κατάλογο πινάκων βάσεως δεδομένων</translation></entry>
<entry><string>No. of columns in database table display:</string><translation>Αριθμός στηλών στην εμφάνιση του πίνακα βάσης δεδομένων:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Default Backup Type used with Scheduler:</string><translation>Προεπιλογή Τύπου Backup που χρησιμοποιείται με τον Scheduler.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>This is the default backup type, used by default with the Scheduler module.</string><translation>Αυτή είναι η προεπιλογή backup, που χρησιμοποιείται από την μονάδα Scheduler.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>*Full backup - complete inserts (default)</string><translation>*Πλήρες backup - πλήρεις εισαγωγές (προεπιλογή)</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Structure only</string><translation>Μόνο δομή</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Scheduling Options</string><translation>Επιλογές Χρονοπρογραμματισμού</translation></entry>
<entry><string>not scheduled</string><translation>δεν έχει προγραμματιστεί</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Specify how often this job should be executed</string><translation>Προσδιορίστε πόσο συχνά θα πρέπει να εκτελείται αυτή η εργασία</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Please note that if you stop the scheduler or if it isn't triggered, these jobs will not be executed.</string><translation>Σημειώστε ότι αν σταπατήσετε τον scheduler ή αν δεν ενεργοποιηθεί, αυτές οι εργασίες δεν θα εκτελούνται.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Should the scheduler FTP the created back-up file to another server?</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You will need to have an FTP server to place the file.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The FTP server</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enter the full name of the server.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The username</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The unique user name for the FTP server.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Password</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enter the password for this user.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>The path on the FTP server</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enter the full name of the path. Defaults to /</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Use Secure FTP?</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You will need to have both the FTP and OpenSSL extension installed.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Modify Configuration</string><translation>Τροποποίηση Ρυθμίσεων</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Must be writeable chmod 777</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Please install and activate the Scheduler module to enable scheduling.</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
