<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="10" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Adminpanels is a Xaraya Core Module.</string>
		<translation>Edmeenpunels is a Xereya Cure-a Mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>It is currently responsible for accomplishing these tasks:</string>
		<translation>It is coorrently respunseeble-a fur eccumpleeshing zeese-a tesks:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="14" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Configuration and display of the administration menu</string>
		<translation>Cunffeegooreshun und deespley ooff zee edmeenistreshun menoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="16" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Management of overviews for other modules</string>
		<translation>Munegement ooff ooferfeeoos fur oozeer mudooles</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Display information about waiting content</string>
		<translation>Deespley inffurmeshun ebuoot veeeting cuntent</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="18" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>When you login as a website administrator, you should see the adminmenu, which lists installed and activated modules. 
            These are the modules with administrative functions and a user interface (UI).
            They allow you to set various parameters, which change the layout or behaviour of either the module itself or the web site.</string>
		<translation>Vhee yuoo lugeen es a vebseete-a edmeenistretur, yuoo shuoold see-a zee edmeenmenoo, vheech leests instelled und ecteefeted mudooles. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Zeese-a ere-a zee mudooles veet edmeenistretife-a fooncshuns und a user interffece-a (UI). Zeey elloo yuoo tu set fereeuoos peremeters, vheech chunge-a zee leyuoot oor behefeeuoor ooff ieezeer zee mudoole-a itselff oor zee veb seete-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="22" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Using this administration system is very simple. First, you may want to configure the adminmenu appearance and the sorting order of the items in it. 
            Of course, it largely depends on what kind of website you are running and on the number of admin-capable modules you deploy. 
            Experiment with the options provided, and hopefully you will find the best solution for your administrative environment. 
            For instance, position the menu left or right, choose a convenient display order and/or temporarily hide modules which you are not going to re-configure frequently.</string>
		<translation>Useeng thees edmeenistreshun system is fery seemple-a. Furst, yuoo mey vunt tu cunffeegoore-a zee edmeenmenoo eppeerunce-a und zee surteeng oorder ooff zee items in it. Um de hur de hur de hur. Ooff cuoorse-a, it lergely depends oon vhet keend ooff vebseete-a yuoo ere-a roonneeng und oon zee noomber ooff edmeen-cepeble-a mudooles yuoo depluy. Bork bork bork! Ixpereement veet zee oopshuns prufeeded, und hupeffoolly yuoo veell feend zee best sulooshun fur yuoor edmeenistretife-a infurunment. Um de hur de hur de hur. Fur instunce-a, puseeshun zee menoo lefft oor reeght, chuuse-a a cunfeneeent deespley oorder und/oor tempurereely heede-a mudooles vheech yuoo ere-a nut gueeng tu re-a-cunffeegoore-a freqooently. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Secondly, you may configure this overview panel to show some more useful information than this text. 
            Some options are (will be) available from &quot;Configure Overview&quot; panel.</string>
		<translation>Secundly, yuoo mey cunffeegoore-a thees ooferfeeoo punel tu shoo sume-a mure-a useffool inffurmeshun thun thees text. Um de hur de hur de hur. Sume-a oopshuns ere-a (veell be-a) efeeeleble-a frum &quot;Cunffeegoore-a Ooferfeeoo&quot; punel.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Having done that, you can start using other modules' administration facilities. Load other modules by clicking the corresponding links in the adminmenu.</string>
		<translation>Hefeeng dune-a thet, yuoo cun stert useeng oozeer mudooles' edmeenistreshun feceelities. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Lued oozeer mudooles by cleecking zee currespundeeng leenks in zee edmeenmenu. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="34" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>And lastly, to hide the administration menu, you must logout as an admin; to minimise, use the collapsible menu option in the &quot;blocks&quot; module.</string>
		<translation>Und lestly, tu heede-a zee edmeenistreshun menoo, yuoo moost luguoot es un edmeen; tu meenimise-a, use-a zee cullepseeble-a menoo oopshun in zee &quot;blucks&quot; mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>admin menu</string>
		<translation>edmeen menoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="43" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>waiting content</string>
		<translation>veeeting cuntent</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="44" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="48" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>[Hooks developers, please provide a description..]</string>
		<translation>[Huuks defelupers, pleese-a prufeede-a a descreepshun..]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="51" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>And more.. [for module developers]</string>
		<translation>Und mure-a.. [fur mudoole-a defelupers]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="54" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Please use this consistent template for your module overview.</string>
		<translation>Pleese-a use-a thees cunseestent templete-a fur yuoor mudoole-a ooferfeeoo.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="57" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Extended inffurmeshun ebuoot thees mudoole-a cun be-a fuoond here-a. [mudooles mudoole-a]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/adminpanels/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="60" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
