<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Τι είναι;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Window module is a port of the popular PostWrap module (for PostNuke) to Xaraya. It lets you display standalone external web pages from within your Xaraya site.</string>
		<translation>Η μονάδα Παράθυρο είναι μια μεταφορά της δημοφιλούς μονάδας (του Postnuke) με το όνομα PostWrap στο Xaraya. Επιτρέπει την εμφάνιση εξωτερικών σελίδων από το site σας.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="16" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Window uses the center block to display the external page(s).</string>
		<translation>Η μονάδα Παράθυρο χρησιμοποιεί το κεντρικό block για να εμφανίσει τις εξωτερικές σελίδες</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="18" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Pages correspond to URLs. You can display pages off your local server, or from the Internet.</string>
		<translation>Οι σελίδες αντιστοιχούν σε URL. Μπορείτε να εμφανίσετε σελίδες από τον τοπικό σας server ή από το Internet.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="19" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can define a number of different options for your external page(s), among them the height and width of the display, whether only registered users may see them, and so on.</string>
		<translation>Μπορείτε να ορίσετε έναν αριθμό διαφορετικών επιλογών για τις εξωτερικές σελίδες, μεταξύ των οποίων το ύψος και το πλάτος της εμφάνισης, αν μόνο εγγεγραμμένοι χρήστες μπορούν να τις δουν κλπ</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can display as many pages as you like, each with its own settings.</string>
		<translation>Μπορεί να εμφανίσετε όσες σελίδες επιθυμείτε, η καθεμία με τις δικές της ρυθμίσεις</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Πως χρησιμοποιείται;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are two administration pages, one for general and one for URL specific settings.</string>
		<translation>Υπάρχουν δύο σελίδες διαχείρισης, μία για την γενική και μια ειδικές ρυθμίσεις URL</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>General settings are valid for all URLs.</string>
		<translation>Οι γενικές ρυθμίσεις είναι αποδεκτές για όλα τα URLs.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The general settings available are:</string>
		<translation>Οι γενικές ρυθμίσεις που είναι διαθέσιμες είναι:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Display only pages off the local server, or also from other servers on the Internet.</string>
		<translation>Εμφανίζονται μόνο οι σελίδες από τον τοπικό server ή από άλλους server στο Internet.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="32" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Buffer the output before displaying it.</string>
		<translation>Buffering της εξόδου πριν την εμφάνισή της.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Allow direct input from the browser address bar.</string>
		<translation>Επιτρέπεται η απευθείας είσοδος στην μπάρα διευθύνσεων</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="34" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Allow only pages from a list of URLs you define.</string>
		<translation>Επιτρέπονται μόνο σελίδες από έναν κατάλογο URL που ορίζετε</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Let only registered users, or all users, see the pages.</string>
		<translation>Επιτρέπεται μόνο οι εγγεγραμμένοι χρήστες ή όλοι οι χρήστες να δούν τις σελίδες;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Display the page directly, or display a link that lets you open the page in a separate window.</string>
		<translation>Εμφάνιση της εικόνας απευθείας ή εμφάνιση ενός συνδέσμου που επιτρέπει το άνοιγμα μιας σελίδας σε ξεχωριστό παράθυρο.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="37" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Use a standard title for the page(s) or use a different title for each page.</string>
		<translation>Χρησιμοποίηση ενός τυποποιημένου τίτλου για τις σελίδες ή χρήση ενός διαφορετικού τίτλου για κάθε σελίδα.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Automatically adjust the size of the display to fill your available space, or not.</string>
		<translation>Αυτόματη διαρρύθμιση του μεγέθους του παραθύρου για να γεμίζει το διαθέσιμο χώρο</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Define the height and width of the display.</string>
		<translation>Καθορισμός ύψους και πλάτους του παραθύρου</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="41" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can also define specific settings for different pages.</string>
		<translation>Μπορείτε επίσης να ορίσετε ρυθμίσεις για διαφορετικές σελίδες.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="45" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>URL specific settings, such as the dimensions of the display, will override the general settings.</string>
		<translation>Ειδικές ρυθμίσεις για URL, όπως π.χ. οι διαστάσεις του παραθύρου</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="45" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>To display an external page, create an entry for it in the user menu. (See the Blocks module for information on how to do this.)
In the URL field of the menu entry write the following:</string>
		<translation>Για να εμφανιστεί μια εξωτερική σελίδα, δημιουργήστε μια εγγραφή από το menu χρήστη (δείτε την μονάδα Blocks για περισσότερες πληροφορίες για το πως γίνεται αυτό.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="49" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&amp;lt;your page&amp;gt; can be an actual URL, such as &lt;b&gt;http://www.xaraya.com&lt;/b&gt;, or an alias you define via your URL specific settings.</string>
		<translation>&amp;lt;η σελίδα&amp;gt; μπορεί να είναι οποιοδήποτε URL, όπως &lt;b&gt;http:/www.xaraya.com&lt;/b&gt; ή ένα alias που ορίζεται από τις ειδικές ρυθμίσεις URL</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="53" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can also add other parameters, as in the following example. See the docs/install.txt for more details.</string>
		<translation>Μπορείτε επίσης να προσθέσετε άλλες παραμέτρους, όπως στο παρακάτω παράδειγμα. Δείτε το docs/install.txt για περισσότερες πληροφορίες.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="54" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Blocks που συμπεριλαμβάνονται</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="61" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>None.</string>
		<translation>Κανένα.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="64" />
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="71" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Hooks που συμπεριλαμβάνονται</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="68" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Επιπρόσθετες πληροφορίες για την μονάδα μπορούν να βρεδούν εδ.ω [μονάδα modules]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/window/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="74" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
