<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="hu_HU.utf-8">
<entry><string>Overview</string><translation>Áttekintés</translation></entry>
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Mi ez?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Paypal Set-Up will set-up the necessary variables for use with the PayPal merchant tools such as the cart, pay now buttons, subscriptions. This module just sets up the defaults. To use the individual buttons and functionality, Dynamic Data must be hooked to your displays.</string><translation>A PayPal beállítások modul a PayPal fizetési lehetőségek alapvető beállításához használható, mint péládul a kosár, fizetés gombok, előfizetések. A modul csak alapértelmezett értékeket állít be, a gombok és lehetőségek használatához a Dinamikus Adatokat kell a megjelenített elemekhez kapcsolni.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Hogyan kell használni?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>From the menu, you have one choice.</string><translation>A menüben a következő lehetőségek érhetőek el:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>"Modify Configuration". From this menu option, you can update the necessary configuration options, such as your paypal account, and prefered currency.</string><translation>Beállítások: Ezen az oldalon végezhetjük a szükséges beállításokat, például a PayPal számlánk adatai és a használni kívánt pénznemet.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Kapcsolódó blokkok</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no blocks included at this time.</string><translation>Nincsenek kapcsolódó blokkok.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Kapcsolódó hurkok</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no hooks included at this time.</string><translation>Nincsenek kapcsolódó hurkok.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string><translation>További információk a modulról:</translation></entry>
</translations>
