<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Search capability</string>
		<translation>Seerch cepebeelity</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="11" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Enable searching</string>
		<translation>Eneble-a seercheeng</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>By hooking search into bkview we enable the search results screen provide by the search
                module (GUI hook) and by hooking bkview into search module, we expose the bkview search
                function to the search module (API) hook</string>
		<translation>By huukeeng seerch intu bkfeeoo ve-a ineble-a zee seerch resoolts screee prufeede-a by zee seerch mudoole-a (GOOI huuk) und by huukeeng bkfeeoo intu seerch mudoole-a, ve-a ixpuse-a zee bkfeeoo seerch fooncshun tu zee seerch mudoole-a (EPI) huuk</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>By clicking the checkbox these hooks will be enabled for you, so you dont have to do this
                manually</string>
		<translation>By cleecking zee checkbux zeese-a huuks veell be-a inebled fur yuoo, su yuoo dunt hefe-a tu du thees munooelly</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Request method</string>
		<translation>Reqooest methud</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="34" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Use an XMLHTTP request method</string>
		<translation>Use-a un XMLHTTP reqooest methud</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>BK-view can use an XML http request for all links in the module. This means that only the
                module area is fetched from the server and dynamically replaced, and not the whole theme with it. If you have a site
                configuration which is suitable this can speed up the access to bkview considerably. This option works
                only with browsers which have support for the XMLHTTPRequest object (Opera has not, for example).</string>
		<translation>BK-feeoo cun use-a un XML http reqooest fur ell leenks in zee mudoole-a. Thees meuns thet oonly zee mudoole-a erea is fetched frum zee serfer und dynemeecelly repleced, und nut zee vhule-a zeeme-a veet it. Um de hur de hur de hur. Iff yuoo hefe-a a seete-a cunffeegooreshun vheech is sooeeteble-a thees cun speed up zee eccess tu bkfeeoo cunseederebly. Bork bork bork! Thees oopshun vurks oonly veet broosers vheech hefe-a sooppurt fur zee XMLHTTPReqooest oobject (Oopera hes nut, fur ixemple-a).</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="47" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Setting this wont break the site if your clients browser does not support the xmlhttprequest object, it
                should gracefully fall back to a normal page request, so it's safe to set this to ON if you like.</string>
		<translation>Setteeng thees vunt breek zee seete-a iff yuoor cleeents brooser dues nut sooppurt zee xmlhttpreqooest oobject, it shuoold greceffoolly fell beck tu a nurmel pege-a reqooest, su it's seffe-a tu set thees tu OoN iff yuoo leeke-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="53" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>These are the &lt;em&gt;known&lt;/em&gt; issues:</string>
		<translation>Zeese-a ere-a zee &lt;em&gt;knoon&lt;/em&gt; issooes:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="56" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You will have to have the module.xt page template (included in recent distributions) on the server, otherwise the 
                    speed increase is considerably less, because the whole page will be fetched regardless.</string>
		<translation>Yuoo veell hefe-a tu hefe-a zee mudoole-a.xt pege-a templete-a (inclooded in recent deestribooshuns) oon zee serfer, oozeerveese-a zee speed increese-a is cunseederebly less, becoose-a zee vhule-a pege-a veell be-a fetched regerdless. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="60" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you have page caching enabled, and bkview pages are normally cached, this option will defeat this. This needs
                    to be fixed eventually. For now, if you have page caching, this option will still work, but the page wont be cached
                    in the output cache. In your configuration, you'll have to test what is the optimal configuration.</string>
		<translation>Iff yuoo hefe-a pege-a cecheeng inebled, und bkfeeoo peges ere-a nurmelly ceched, thees oopshun veell deffeet thees. Thees needs tu be-a feexed ifentooelly. Bork bork bork! Fur noo, iff yuoo hefe-a pege-a cecheeng, thees oopshun veell steell vurk, boot zee pege-a vunt be-a ceched in zee ooootpoot ceche-a. In yuoor cunffeegooreshun, yuoo'll hefe-a tu test vhet is zee oopteemel cunffeegooreshun.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Not really an issue, because it is by design, but worth mentioning is that this technique basically NEVER 
                    refreshes the page. This has two major consequences:</string>
		<translation>Nut reelly un issooe-a, becoose-a it is by deseegn, boot vurt menshuneeng is thet thees techneeqooe-a beseecelly NEFER reffreshes zee pege-a. Thees hes tvu mejur cunseqooences:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="70" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The back button (history functionality) will not be updated while navigating bkview</string>
		<translation>Zee beck boottun (heestury fooncshuneleety) veell nut be-a updeted vheele-a nefeegeting bkfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="75" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Dynamic blocks which base their content on the &lt;em&gt;current page&lt;/em&gt; will keep their content as if still on the 
                                main page of the bkview module.</string>
		<translation>Dynemeec blucks vheech bese-a zeeur cuntent oon zee &lt;em&gt;coorrent pege-a&lt;/em&gt; veell keep zeeur cuntent es iff steell oon zee meeen pege-a ooff zee bkfeeoo mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/bkview/xartemplates/admin-modifyconfig.xd" line="81" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
