<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Administrator Account Creation</string>
		<translation>Edmeenistretur Eccuoont Creeshun</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-create_administrator.xd" line="9" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Please enter the settings for your Administrator account. This information is necessary in order to properly secure your Xaraya installation. These settings can be changed at any point in the future by visiting the roles module.</string>
		<translation>Pleese-a inter zee setteengs fur yuoor Edmeenistretur eccuoont. Um de hur de hur de hur. Thees inffurmeshun is necessery in oorder tu pruperly secoore-a yuoor Xereya instelleshun. Zeese-a setteengs cun be-a chunged et uny pueent in zee footoore-a by feesiting zee rules mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-create_administrator.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Administrator Information</string>
		<translation>Edmeenistretur Inffurmeshun</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-create_administrator.xd" line="22" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Display name</string>
		<translation>Deespley neme</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-create_administrator.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Password Again</string>
		<translation>Pessvurd Egeeen</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-create_administrator.xd" line="56" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Email</string>
		<translation>Emeeel</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-create_administrator.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Your Administrator password is the key to your Xaraya installation. Choose something that you will remember and do not share it or write it down. As a rule of thumb, it should not contain any words, and should contain a mix of upper and lower case letters, numbers and punctuation.</string>
		<translation>Yuoor Edmeenistretur pessvurd is zee key tu yuoor Xereya instelleshun. Chuuse-a sumetheeng thet yuoo veell remember und du nut shere-a it oor vreete-a it doon. Bork bork bork! Es a roole-a ooff thoomb, it shuoold nut cunteeen uny vurds, und shuoold cunteeen a meex ooff upper und looer cese-a letters, noombers und poonctooeshun.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-create_administrator.xd" line="75" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
