<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Database Settings Collection</string>
		<translation>Detebese-a Setteengs Cullecshun</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="9" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Please enter your database settings. You can connect to databases on non-standard ports using 'hostname:port' in the Host field. (e.g. 'localhost:12345')</string>
		<translation>Pleese-a inter yuoor detebese-a setteengs. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Yuoo cun cunnect tu detebeses oon nun-stunderd purts useeng 'hustneme-a:purt' in zee Hust feeeld. (i.g. 'lucelhust:12345')</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you do not have root access to your database (due to virtual hosting, etc.), you will need to have a pre-existing one configured before you proceed.</string>
		<translation>Iff yuoo du nut hefe-a ruut eccess tu yuoor detebese-a (dooe-a tu furtooel husteeng, itc.), yuoo veell need tu hefe-a a pre-a-ixeesting oone-a cunffeegoored beffure-a yuoo pruceed. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>UPGRADE NOTE: If you plan on upgrading to Xaraya from a previous version or another Weblog/CMS, install as normal, then run the provided upgrade script.</string>
		<translation>UPGREDE NOTE: Iff yuoo plun oon upgredeeng tu Xereya frum a prefeeuoos ferseeun oor unuzeer Veblug/CMS, instell es nurmel, zeen roon zee prufeeded upgrede-a screept. Um de hur de hur de hur.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="26" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Database Information</string>
		<translation>Detebese-a Inffurmeshun</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Host</string>
		<translation>Hust</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Database Name</string>
		<translation>Detebese-a Neme</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Table Prefix</string>
		<translation>Teble-a Preffeex</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="74" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>(for Table Sharing)</string>
		<translation>(fur Teble-a Shereeng)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="80" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Database Type</string>
		<translation>Detebese-a Type</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="88" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Create the database</string>
		<translation>Creete-a zee detebese</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="105" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This option specifies whether you need the install to create the empty database for you first or whether it can just populate an already existing database. If you cannot create databases through phpMyAdmin because of virtual hosting or MySQL security settings, the installer will not be able to create the database for you. It will be able to populate an already existing one though.</string>
		<translation>Thees oopshun speceeffies vhezeer yuoo need zee instell tu creete-a zee impty detebese-a fur yuoo furst oor vhezeer it cun joost pupoolete-a un elreedy ixeesting detebese-a. Iff yuoo cunnut creete-a detebeses thruoogh phpMyEdmeen becoose-a ooff furtooel husteeng oor MySQL secooreety setteengs, zee insteller veell nut be-a eble-a tu creete-a zee detebese-a fur yuu. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! It veell be-a eble-a tu pupoolete-a un elreedy ixeesting oone-a thuoogh.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/installer/xartemplates/admin-phase4.xd" line="111" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
