<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="sv_SE.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>From this screen, you will be adding a release note for your extension. Please enter all applicable information. Release notes are held for validation. If your extension has never had a release before, it may take extra time to determine the certification status. For more information on the certification of extensions, and their benefits, please read this information (insert link).</string>
		<translation>Från denna skärmen kommer du att lägga till en release-anteckning för ditt tillägg. Vänligen fyll i all passande information. Release-anteckningar finns till för validering. Om ditt tillägg inte har släppts tidigare kan det ta tid att bestämma dess certifieringsstatus. För mer information om tilläggs certifiering och dess fördelar, vänligen läs denna information (lägg till länk).</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/release/xartemplates/user-addnote_start.xd" line="9" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Your Release Notification has been sent for review. It should appear on the site very shortly.
In the meantime you can</string>
		<translation>Din release-notis har sänts in för granskning. Den bör dyka upp på sajten inom kort. Under tiden kan du</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/release/xartemplates/user-addnote_thanks.xd" line="9" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can view all Registered Extensions in the &lt;a href=&quot;#$extlisturl#&quot;&gt;Extension List View Page&lt;/a&gt;.You can also &lt;a href=&quot;#$extregisterurl#&quot;&gt;register your own extensions&lt;/a&gt; with the link from that page.</string>
		<translation>Du kan granska alla registrerade tillägg i &lt;a href=&quot;#$extlisturl#&quot;&gt;tilläggslistans sida&lt;/a&gt;.Du kan också &lt;a href=&quot;#$extregisterurl#&quot;&gt;registrera ditt egna tillägg&lt;/a&gt; med länken från den sidan.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/release/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extensions that have already been release can be viewed on the &lt;a href=&quot;#$extreleaseurl#&quot;&gt;Recent Extension Release page&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Tillägg som redan har släppts ut kan ses på &lt;a href=&quot;#$extreleaseurl#&quot;&gt;sidan för nyligen släppta tillägg&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/release/xartemplates/user-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Add Extension</string>
		<translation>Lägg till tillägg</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/release/xartemplates/user-view.xd" line="16" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Please Log In to Add an Extension</string>
		<translation>Vänligen logga in för att lägga till ett tillägg</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/release/xartemplates/user-view.xd" line="18" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>[Add Extension]</string>
		<translation>[Lägg till tillägg]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/release/xartemplates/user-view.xd" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Author (uid sort)</string>
		<translation>Utgivare (sorterat på användarID)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/release/xartemplates/user-view.xd" line="82" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Currently displaying filtered by:
&lt;b&gt;
#(1)
&lt;/b&gt;</string>
		<translation></translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/release/xartemplates/user-view.xd" line="95" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>No Extension Found that matches your search</string>
		<translation>Inga tillägg enligt din sökning kunde hittas</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/release/xaruser/search.php" line="115" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
