<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="sv_SE.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>A glimpse into Xaraya</string>
		<translation>En glimt in i Xaraya</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/glimpse.xt" line="1" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The contents of this page are written in what we call an
&lt;em&gt;overridden&lt;/em&gt; template (in this case one from the base module). This means
that its contents are determined by the active theme in a Xaraya installation
and not by the &lt;em&gt;internal&lt;/em&gt; template, which is part of the standard code
and templates of Xaraya.</string>
		<translation>Innehållet på den här sidan är skrivit i en vad vi kallar för &lt;em&gt;åtsidosättande&lt;/em&gt; mall(i detta fall en från basmodulen). Det betyder att dess innehåll bestäms av det aktiva temat för en Xaraya installation och inte av en &lt;em&gt;intern&lt;/em&gt; mall, som är en del av standard koden och mallarna för Xaraya.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/glimpse.xt" line="9" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This overridden template you are looking at is located in
(#(1)/themename/modules/base/user-main.xt). The template is part of the
&lt;em&gt;base&lt;/em&gt; module which is by default configured to be the active module on
the frontpage of a Xaraya installation.</string>
		<translation>Den åtsidosättande mallen som du tittar på är sparad i (#(1)/themename/modules/base/user-main.xt). Mallen är en del av &lt;em&gt;basmodulen&lt;/em&gt; som är som standard konfigurerad att vara den aktiva modulen på framsidan för en Xaraya installation.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/glimpse.xt" line="16" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Of course, the above tiny peek into Xaraya's templates is just the tip
of the iceberg. When you decide to use Xaraya, you'll get to know the templating
system in far more detail, but a good start is to have a look at the contents of
the file mentioned above.</string>
		<translation>Ovanstående  glimt in i Xarayas mallar är bara toppen på ett isberg. Nä'r du bestämt dig för att använda Xaraya, kommer du lära känna mallsystemet bättre, men en bra början är att titta på innehållet i ovan nämda fil.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/glimpse.xt" line="24" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
