<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/pubsub/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/pubsub/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Pubsub module allows users to subscribe to events on your system such as new articles being posted in a particular category or replies on a forum thread.
This module uses the Scheduler module to process events and the Mail module to actually send the notifications.</string>
		<translation>Zee Poobsoob mudoole-a elloos users tu soobscreebe-a tu ifents oon yuoor system sooch es noo erteecles beeeng pusted in a perteecooler cetegury oor repleees oon a furoom threed. Bork bork bork! Thees mudoole-a uses zee Schedooler mudoole-a tu prucess ifents und zee Meeel mudoole-a tu ectooelly send zee nuteefficeshuns.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/pubsub/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="18" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/pubsub/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="22" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&lt;p&gt;The pubsub module should be hooked to the categories module first, so that your users can subscribe to events concerning a particular category.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then you should enable the pubsub hooks for any other module (e.g. articles) where you want to send out create/update/delete notifications to your users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And finally you should specify which templates to use for each module and how often events should be processed in &quot;Modify Configuration&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</string>
		<translation>&lt;p&gt;Zee poobsoob mudoole-a shuoold be-a huuked tu zee cetegureees mudoole-a furst, su thet yuoor users cun soobscreebe-a tu ifents cuncerneeng a perteecooler cetegury.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Zeen yuoo shuoold ineble-a zee poobsoob huuks fur uny oozeer mudoole-a (i.g. erteecles) vhere-a yuoo vunt tu send oooot creete-a/updete-a/delete-a nuteefficeshuns tu yuoor users.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Und feenelly yuoo shuoold speceeffy vheech templetes tu use-a fur iech mudoole-a und hoo oofftee ifents shuoold be-a prucessed in &quot;Mudeeffy Cunffeegooreshun&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/pubsub/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/pubsub/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="32" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Pubsub module has no blocks included at this time.</string>
		<translation>Zee Poobsoob mudoole-a hes nu blucks inclooded et thees teeme-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/pubsub/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/pubsub/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Pubsub module supports item display hooks to let your users subscribe to events in particular categories. It also supports item create, item update and item delete hooks to inform your users when a module item is created, updated or deleted. This can be configured in the modules module.</string>
		<translation>Zee Poobsoob mudoole-a sooppurts item deespley huuks tu let yuoor users soobscreebe-a tu ifents in perteecooler cetegureees. Um gesh dee bork, bork! It elsu sooppurts item creete-a, item updete-a und item delete-a huuks tu inffurm yuoor users vhee a mudoole-a item is creeted, updeted oor deleted. Thees cun be-a cunffeegoored in zee mudooles mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/pubsub/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="44" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Extended inffurmeshun ebuoot thees mudoole-a cun be-a fuoond here-a. [mudooles mudoole-a]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/pubsub/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="48" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
