<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Messages Module Overview</string>
		<translation>Messeges Mudoole-a Ooferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If this is your first visit to this part of your Xaraya site,
please take a minute to read through the following introduction,
in order to explore the different possibilities offered by the
Contact module.</string>
		<translation>Iff thees is yuoor furst feesit tu thees pert ooff yuoor Xereya seete-a, pleese-a teke-a a meenoote-a tu reed thruoogh zee fullooeeng intrudoocshun, in oorder tu ixplure-a zee deefffferent pusseebilities ooffffered by zee Cuntect mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="7" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&quot;The Messages module gives your users a way to send messages to another users inbox.&quot;</string>
		<translation>&quot;Zee Messeges mudoole-a geefes yuoor users a vey tu send messeges tu unuzeer users inbux.&quot;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&quot;You must be logged into the site before you can send messages. Select Messages from the user menu and select a user from the drop down list to send your message too. Compose your message and select the send button.&quot;</string>
		<translation>&quot;Yuoo moost be-a lugged intu zee seete-a beffure-a yuoo cun send messeges. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Select Messeges frum zee user menoo und select a user frum zee drup doon leest tu send yuoor messege-a tuu. Cumpuse-a yuoor messege-a und select zee send boottun. Bork bork bork!&quot;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&quot;From the Admin menu you can specify the support of short urls for the messages module.&quot;</string>
		<translation>&quot;Frum zee Edmeen menoo yuoo cun speceeffy zee sooppurt ooff shurt urls fur zee messeges mudoole-a.&quot;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>&quot;newmessages&quot;</string>
		<translation>&quot;noomesseges&quot;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Messages Module has one block included at this time.</string>
		<translation>Zee Messeges Mudoole-a hes oone-a bluck inclooded et thees teeme-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>newmessages -&gt; Display's a block that lists any new unread messages for the user with a link to the view messages page.'</string>
		<translation>noomesseges -&gt; Deespley's a bluck thet leests uny noo unreed messeges fur zee user veet a leenk tu zee feeoo messeges pege-a.'</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/messages/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="41" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
