<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
<entry><string>1.1 Grant rights for an unregistered user</string><translation>1.1 Geef rechten aan een ongeregistreerde gebruiker</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Unregistered users have their own set of rights. By default,
unregistered users may view existing entries only. You may grant unregistered users the
rights to edit and delete records created by other unregistered users only. Administrators
may view / edit / delete any record created by an unregistered user.</string><translation>Ongeregistreerde gebruikers hebben hun eigen set van rechten. Standaard mogen ongeregistreerde gebruikers alleen bestaande records bekijken. U mag ongeregistreerde gebruikers de rechten geven om records die door andere ongeregistreerde gebruikers zijn gemaakt te wijzigen of te verwijderen. Beheerders mogen elke record die door een ongeregistreerde gebruiker is gemaakt bekijken/wijzigen/verwijderen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>1.2 Grant right for registered users</string><translation>1.2 Geef rechten aan geregistreerde gebruikers</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Registered users have their own set of rights. By default, registered users can create records, view records, and delete records. You can restrict access by deselecting grants. Registered users can edit records created by that user account only. All other records are view only. Records marked as private can be viewed only by the user that created the record and no one else save Administrators. Administrators may view / edit / delete any record created by a registered user.</string><translation>Geregistreerde gebruikers hebben hun eigen set van rechten. Standaard kunnen geregistreerde gebruikers records aanmaken, bekijken en verwijderen. U kunt de toegang verminderen door rechten te deselecteren. Geregistreerde gebruikers kunnen alleen records wijzigen die door die ene gebruikersaccount zijn aangemaakt. Alle andere records kunnen slechts bekeken worden. Records die zijn gemarkeerd als prive kunnen alleen bekeken worden door de gebruiker die de records heeft gemaakt en niemand anders behalve door beheerders. Beheerders kunnen alle records die door gebruikers zijn gemaakt bekijken/wijzigen/verwijderen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.1 Title of this Address Book</string><translation>2.1 Titel van dit adressenboek</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Enter the title which will appear to all users.</string><translation>Geef de titel die door alle gebruikers wordt gezien.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.3 Default and Alternate sort order / List View</string><translation>2.3 Standaard en alternatieve sorteer volgorde  / Lijst weergave</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select two columns of your choice. This setting
affects not only the sort order but also the display of columns in
the list view. Users are allowed to select between the Default and Alternate sort orders.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.4 Name display in list view and sort order for name
information</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>This setting is for the sort order and display of names in
the list view. You can change the default &amp;laquo;Last Name, First
Name&amp;raquo; to &amp;laquo;First Name Last Name&amp;raquo;, which is default in
some countries.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.5 Special character (Umlauts) replacement for sort columns</string><translation>2.5 Speciale tekens vervanging (Umlauts) voor sorteer kolommen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>MySQL 3.x uses the Latin-1 character set as
default. Most users have no permission to change these settings.
Therefore names and companies are now stored in special sort columns
for correct sorting when special characters (Umlauts) are used. There
is an admin setting where you can set up the character replacement to
correct the sort for each language.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.6 Personal address book mode</string><translation>2.6 Persoonlijke adressenboek modus</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Address Book may be used as a Global AddressBook (unchecked by default)
or a Personal AddressBook (checked). As a Global AddressBook all users with access may view records
that are NOT marked Private. As a Personal AddressBook users may only view entries they have created
and unregistered users may not view or create any entries.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.7 Do you want to use a prefix field?</string><translation>2.7 Wilt u een voorvoegsel veld gebruiken?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Prefix/Title (Mr. Mrs. etc.). Values can be set in</string><translation>Voorvoegsel/Titel (Dhr, Mevr etc) waarden kunnen ingesteld worden in</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Administration Panel and are optionally selected via a drop-down list when creating / editing an entry. This field is hidden by default.</string><translation>Administratie menu en kunnen -optioneel- geselecteerd worden via een drop-down lijst als er een record wordt aangemaakt/gewijzigd. Dit veld is standaard verborgen.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.8 Do you want to use images/logos?</string><translation>2.8 Wilt u afbeeldingen/logos gebruiken?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Administrators will see a selection box of all
files in the xarimages directory of AddressBook and can assign it to a
record. The picture is shown in the upper right of the detail page.
Currently, all pictures must be manually uploaded into the xarimages directory of
AddressBook. This field is hidden by default.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.9 Disable the menu</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>If you want to use the AddressBook as a
simple contact list, you might want to disable the menu completely.
You can also disable it for guests only. Note, Administrators always see the full menu, regardless of this setting.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.10 Disable the second line of the main menu</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>This hides the second menu line for all users who
DO NOT have edit access. Users still have access to the categories,
sort order and the search field, but not access to Private records,
A-Z / Complete list view switch, and the Add New Record link.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.11 Show zip before city</string><translation>2.11 Toon de postcode voor plaats</translation></entry>
<entry><string>In Europe the postal code (zip in USA) is shown before the city.
This option is off by default.</string><translation>In Europa wordt de postcode (Zip in USA) getoond voor de plaats. Standaard staat deze optie uit.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>2.12 Records viewed per page</string><translation>2.12 Aantal records getoond per pagina</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Pick your number between 1 and ??</string><translation>Kies een nummer tussen 1 en ??</translation></entry>
<entry><string>3.1 Custom tab</string><translation>3.1 Eigen tab</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Name of the Custom Fields tab and the
headline for custom fields in the detail page. Leave it blank, if you
do not use custom fields.</string><translation>Naam van de eigen velden tab en de headline voor eigen velden in de detail pagina. Vul hier niets in als u geen eigen velden wilt gebruiken.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>3.2 Width of TEXTAREA fields</string><translation>3.2 Breedte van TEXTAREA velden</translation></entry>
<entry><string>TEXTAREA field width can change depending on
the CSS of your theme. Sometimes this results in a very bad layout of
your form. You can set the html COLS of a TEXTAREA field. Valid size ranges from 4 to 100.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>3.3 Format for date entries</string><translation>3.3 Formaat voor datum invoegingen</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select the format for date entry and
display. Only two options at this time, MM.DD.YYYY and DD.MM.YYYY.</string><translation>Selecteer het formaat voor datum invoegingen en weergaves. Er zijn twee opties op dit moment: MM.DD.YYYY and DD.MM.YYYY.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>3.4 Format for numeric values</string><translation>3.4 Formaat voor numeriek waardes</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Select the format for numeric entry and
display. Only two options at this time, 9,999.00 and 9.999,00</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>4.1 Send error reports to Site Admin</string><translation>Stuur foutmeldingen naar de Website beheerder</translation></entry>
<entry><string>This option enables error messages to be emailed directly to
the site administrator email account. Uncheck to disable this feature.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>4.2 Alternate Site Admin email address</string><translation>Alternatief e-mail adres van de website beheerder</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Choose an alternate email address if the official Site Admin
does not wish to receive AddressBook error notifications.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>4.3 Send error reports to AddressBook Quality Control</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>This option sends an email directly to the AddressBook development
team with the error message, date and time of occurrence, and the fully qualified host name of the
server running the AddressBook module. NO OTHER INFORMATION IS SENT. This information is used solely for
the purpose of fixing issues encountered in the AddressBook module. Uncheck to disable this feature.</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
