<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="pl_PL.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Wprowadzenie</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Co to jest?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Base Module controls the behind the scenes processing for your Xaraya installation.</string>
		<translation>Moduł bazowy kontroluje spósb pracy twojego systemu Xaraya</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Jak tego używać?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have two choices.</string>
		<translation>W menu masz dwie możliwości wyboru.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>View System Information -- Allows you to print your server and php set-up for trouble shooting.</string>
		<translation>Zobacz Informację o Sytemie - Pozwala Ci wydrukować</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Config -- Allows you to change some of the settings controlling the core behaviour of the site.</string>
		<translation>Zmie Konfigurację</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Dołączone Bloki</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>RSS Class</string>
		<translation>Klasa RSS</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The RSS capabilities in Xaraya is using</string>
		<translation>Możliwości RSS w Xarayi oparte s na</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>PHP feedParser</string>
		<translation>klasie PHP feedParser</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>as its backend.   The notes for the feedParser by Reverend Jim are as follows</string>
		<translation>Uwagi dotyczące  klasy feedParser napisanej przez Wielebnego Jima:</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>feedParser was created due to the lack of a good, flexible, class-based RSS feed parser for PHP. It has been built as a class, and currently handles RSS 0.91, RSS 0.92, RSS 0.93, RSS 1.0, and RSS 2.0 feeds. For channels it grabs the title, description, link, and creator. For items it grabs the title, description, link, and date. It also provides a form of the date converted into the local timezone to facilitate chronological sorting of items. The dates are provided in UNIX timestamp format for easy manipulation by other PHP functions.</string>
		<translation>feedParser został stworzony z powodu braku dobrego, elastycznego, opartego na klasie parsera zawartości RSS dla PHP. Został zbudowany jako klasa i obecnie radzi sobie z formatem RSS 0.91, RSS 0.92, RSS 0.93, RSS 01.0, oraz RSS 2.0. Dla kanałów przechwytuje tytuł, opis, link oraz twórcę. Dla pozycji przechwytuje tytuł, opis, link i datę. Dostarcza również formę daty przekonwertowaną na lokalny czas by umożliwić chronologiczne sortowanie pozycji. Daty są róniez dostarczane jak UNIXowy znacznik czasu dla łatwego przetwarzania  przez inne funkcje PHP.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="41" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Expire a Block</string>
		<translation>Wygasanie Bloku</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="45" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Currently, the HTML and Text blocks can both expire content if you wish.  If you have a message that you would like to only have visible for a certain period of time, you can expire the block.  This functionality can be used in conjunction with any placement or block group that you assign the block.</string>
		<translation>Obecnie, bloki HTML i tekstowe mog przedawnia zawarto6 jeli sobie tego yczysz. Jeli masz wiadomo kt</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="50" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Dołączone uchwyty</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="56" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Base Module has no hooks included at this time.</string>
		<translation>Moduł bazowy nie ma dołączonych uchwytów obecnie.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="60" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Rozszerzoną informację o tym module można znaleść tutaj [modules module]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/base/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="64" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
