<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="pt_BR.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>About the Xaraya Classic theme</string>
		<translation>Sobre o tema Xaraya Clássico</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main-about.xt" line="4" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The default theme's name is Xaraya_Classic. It is supplied and
installed with every distribution package of Xaraya. The theme not only gives
you a pleasant way to explore Xaraya, but also contains a lot of example on what
is possible with Xaraya.</string>
		<translation>O tema padrão se chama Xaraya_Classic. Ele é incluído e instalado com cada pacote de distribuição do Xaraya. Além de oferecer uma forma agradável de explorer o Xaraya, este tema também contém vários exemplos das possibilidades fornecidas pelo Xaraya.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main-about.xt" line="12" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The theme is 100% table-free and is totally CSS driven. This means
the theme is now more standards compliant than ever before. However, designing
your site with the web-standards in mind requires certain degree of knowledge,
experience, attention to detail and patience. So we would advise to keep this
theme unmodified within your Xaraya installation directory, in case you need to
use it as a reference to help solve a problem.</string>
		<translation>A disposição deste tema não contém nenhuma tabela e é totalmente estruturado por CSS. Isto significa que este tema agora é ainda mais complacente com normas padrões. Porém, construir o seu próprio site considerando padrões web requer um certo grau de conhecimento, experiência, atenção para detalhes e paciência. Portanto nós sugerimos que você mantenha este tema sem alterá-lo, no diretório de instalação do Xaraya, caso você precise utilizá-lo como referência para solucionar qualquer problema.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main-about.xt" line="22" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you wish to design your own Xaraya theme based on Xaraya Classic
or alter the appearance of this theme, the graphics sources can be obtained from
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xaraya.com/~andyv/xclassic_sources&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Se você deseja criar o seu próprio tema para o Xaraya, alterando a aparência deste tema ou o utilizando como esboço, as imagens utilizadas podem ser obtidas &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.xaraya.com/~andyv/xclassic_sources&quot;&gt;aqui&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="themes/Xaraya_Classic/modules/base/user-main-about.xt" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
