<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="de_DE.utf-8">
<entry><string>Terms and Conditions / Disclaimer</string><translation>Nutzungsbedingungen und Konditionen</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icegrey/modules/eorigin/includes/attestation-disclaimer.xt" line="4"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>The verification and attestation of this document refer solely to the attached PDF-documents. The original papers and/or documents are not seen or consulted. The client and applicant above mentioned is fully and exclusively responsible for the content, correctness, authenticity and integrity of the underlying original documents. Any liability for damages in any form or kind is excluded by icetodo Ltd. Liab. Co. and Basel Chamber of Commerce, Switzerland. Any liability wich may result of the use or abuse of the present Attestation to the client and applicant and/or to any third person is excluded completely and worldwide. Damages shall mean any incidental, direct, indirect, special, consequential, or punitive damages or loss of any nature whatsoever. icetodo Ltd. Liab. Co. and Basel Chamber of Commerce, Switzerland, exclude any warranty for any form of authenticity or explanatory power of the present online-attestation in form of this PDF-document.</string><translation>Zur Ueberprüfung und Beglaubigung liegen ausschliesslich die diesem Dokument angehängten PDF-Dokumente vor. Die Originaldokumente werden nicht eingesehen. Der (die) obgenannte Kunde(in) ist ausschliesslich und vollumfänglich für den Inhalt, die Richtigkeit und die Echtheit der zugrunde liegenden Originale verantwortlich. Jegliche Haftung für Schäden in irgendeiner Form oder Art, welche dem (der) Kunden(in) oder irgendwelchen Dritten durch die Verwendung der vorliegenden Beglaubigung entstehen, wird von der Handelskammer beider Basel,E-Origin und icetodo Ltd. Liab. Co. vollumfänglich und weltweit ausgeschlossen. Jegliche Gewährleistung irgendeiner Beweiskraft oder Aussagekraft der ausgestellten online-Beglaubigung wird von der Handelskammer beider Basel, E-Origin und icetodo Ltd. Liab. Co. vollumfänglich und weltweit ausgeschlossen.</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="themes/icegrey/modules/eorigin/includes/attestation-disclaimer.xt" line="8"/>
		</references>
</entry>
</translations>
