<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>1.1 Grant rights for an unregistered user</string>
		<translation>1.1 Grunt reeghts fur un unregeestered user</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="15" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Unregistered users have their own set of rights. By default,  
        unregistered users may view existing entries only. You may grant unregistered users the 
        rights to edit and delete records created by other unregistered users only. Administrators 
        may view / edit / delete any record created by an unregistered user.</string>
		<translation>Unregeestered users hefe-a zeeur oovn set ooff reeghts. By deffoolt, unregeestered users mey feeoo ixeesting intreees oonly. Bork bork bork! Yuoo mey grunt unregeestered users zee reeghts tu ideet und delete-a recurds creeted by oozeer unregeestered users oonly.Edmeenistreturs mey feeoo / ideet / delete-a uny recurd creeted by un unregeestered user.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="19" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>1.2 Grant right for registered users</string>
		<translation>1.2 Grunt reeght fur regeestered users</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Registered users have their own set of rights. By default, registered users can create records, view records, and delete records. You can restrict access by deselecting grants. Registered users can edit records created by that user account only. All other records are view only. Records marked as private can be viewed only by the user that created the record and no one else save Administrators. Administrators may view / edit / delete any record created by a registered user.</string>
		<translation>Regeestered users hefe-a zeeur oovn set ooff reeghts. By deffoolt, regeestered users cun creete-a recurds, feeoo recurds, und delete-a recurds. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Yuoo cun restreect eccess by deselecteeng grunts. Regeestered users cun ideet recurds creeted by thet user eccuoont oonly. Ell oozeer recurds ere-a feeoo oonly. Recurds merked es preefete-a cun be-a feeooed oonly by zee user thet creeted zee recurd und nu oone-a ilse-a sefe-a Edmeenistreturs. Edmeenistreturs mey feeoo / ideet / delete-a uny recurd creeted by a regeestered user. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.1 Title of this Address Book</string>
		<translation>2.1 Teetle-a ooff thees Eddress Buuk</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Enter the title which will appear to all users.</string>
		<translation>Enter zee teetle-a vheech veell eppeer tu ell users.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.3 Default and Alternate sort order / List View</string>
		<translation>2.3 Deffoolt und Elternete-a surt oorder / Leest Feeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Select two columns of your choice. This setting 
          affects not only the sort order but also the display of columns in 
          the list view. Users are allowed to select between the Default and Alternate sort orders.</string>
		<translation>Select tvu culoomns ooff yuoor chueece-a. Thees setteeng effffects nut oonly zee surt oorder boot elsu zee deespley ooff culoomns in zee leest feeoo. Users ere-a ellooed tu select betveee zee Deffoolt und Elternete-a surt oorders. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="32" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.4 Name display in list view and sort order for name 
          information</string>
		<translation>2.4 Neme-a deespley in leest feeoo und surt oorder fur neme-a inffurmeshun</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="34" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This setting is for the sort order and display of names in 
          the list view. You can change the default &amp;laquo;Last Name, First 
          Name&amp;raquo; to &amp;laquo;First Name Last Name&amp;raquo;, which is default in 
          some countries.</string>
		<translation>Thees setteeng is fur zee surt oorder und deespley ooff nemes in zee leest feeoo. Yuoo cun chunge-a zee deffoolt &amp;laquo;Lest Neme-a, Furst Neme-a&amp;raquo; tu &amp;laquo;Furst Neme-a Lest Neme-a&amp;raquo;, vheech is deffoolt in sume-a cuoontreees.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.5 Special character (Umlauts) replacement for sort columns</string>
		<translation>2.5 Speceeel cherecter (Umloots) replecement fur surt culoomns</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>MySQL 3.x uses the Latin-1 character set as 
          default. Most users have no permission to change these settings. 
          Therefore names and companies are now stored in special sort columns 
          for correct sorting when special characters (Umlauts) are used. There 
          is an admin setting where you can set up the character replacement to 
          correct the sort for each language.</string>
		<translation>MySQL 3.x uses zee Leteen-1 cherecter set es deffoolt. Um de hur de hur de hur. Must users hefe-a nu permeessiun tu chunge-a zeese-a setteengs. Zeereffure-a nemes und cumpuneees ere-a noo stured in speceeel surt culoomns fur currect surteeng vhee speceeel cherecters (Umloots) ere-a used. Bork bork bork! Zeere-a is un edmeen setteeng vhere-a yuoo cun set up zee cherecter replecement tu currect zee surt fur iech lungooege-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="45" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.6 Personal address book mode</string>
		<translation>2.6 Persunel eddress buuk mude</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="46" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Address Book may be used as a Global AddressBook (unchecked by default) 
          or a Personal AddressBook (checked). As a Global AddressBook all users with access may view records 
          that are NOT marked Private. As a Personal AddressBook users may only view entries they have created 
          and unregistered users may not view or create any entries.</string>
		<translation>Zee Eddress Buuk mey be-a used es a Glubel EddressBuuk (unchecked by deffoolt) oor a Persunel EddressBuuk (checked). Es a Glubel EddressBuuk ell users veet eccess mey feeoo recurds thet ere-a NOT merked Preefete-a. Es a Persunel EddressBuuk users mey oonly feeoo intreees zeey hefe-a creeted und unregeestered users mey nut feeoo oor creete-a uny intreees.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="50" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.7 Do you want to use a prefix field?</string>
		<translation>2.7 Du yuoo vunt tu use-a a preffeex feeeld?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="51" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Prefix/Title (Mr. Mrs. etc.). Values can be set in</string>
		<translation>Preffeex/Teetle-a (Mr. Mrs. itc.). Felooes cun be-a set in</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="53" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Administration Panel and are optionally selected via a drop-down list when creating / editing an entry. This field is hidden by default.</string>
		<translation>Edmeenistreshun Punel und ere-a oopshunelly selected feea a drup-doon leest vhee creeteeng / ideeting un intry. Thees feeeld is heeddee by deffoolt.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="54" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.8 Do you want to use images/logos?</string>
		<translation>2.8 Du yuoo vunt tu use-a imeges/lugus?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Administrators will see a selection box of all 
          files in the xarimages directory of AddressBook and can assign it to a 
          record. The picture is shown in the upper right of the detail page. 
          Currently, all pictures must be manually uploaded into the xarimages directory of 
          AddressBook. This field is hidden by default.</string>
		<translation>Edmeenistreturs veell see-a a selecshun bux ooff ell feeles in zee xereemeges durectury ooff EddressBuuk und cun esseegn it tu a recurd. Bork bork bork! Zee peectoore-a is shoon in zee upper reeght ooff zee deteeel pege-a. Coorrently, ell peectoores moost be-a munooelly uplueded intu zee xereemeges durectury ooff EddressBuuk. Thees feeeld is heeddee by deffoolt.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="60" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.9 Disable the menu</string>
		<translation>2.9 Deeseble-a zee menoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="61" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you want to use the AddressBook as a 
          simple contact list, you might want to disable the menu completely. 
          You can also disable it for guests only. Note, Administrators always see the full menu, regardless of this setting.</string>
		<translation>Iff yuoo vunt tu use-a zee EddressBuuk es a seemple-a cuntect leest, yuoo meeght vunt tu deeseble-a zee menoo cumpletely. Yuoo cun elsu deeseble-a it fur gooests oonly. Nute-a, Edmeenistreturs elveys see-a zee fooll menoo, regerdless ooff thees setteeng.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.10 Disable the second line of the main menu</string>
		<translation>2.10 Deeseble-a zee secund leene-a ooff zee meeen menoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="66" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This hides the second menu line for all users who
              DO NOT have edit access. Users still have access to the categories,
              sort order and the search field, but not access to Private records,
              A-Z / Complete list view switch, and the Add New Record link.</string>
		<translation>Thees heedes zee secund menoo leene-a fur ell users vhu DO NOT hefe-a ideet eccess. Um gesh dee bork, bork! Users steell hefe-a eccess tu zee cetegureees, surt oorder und zee seerch feeeld, boot nut eccess tu Preefete-a recurds, A-Z / Cumplete-a leest feeoo sveetch, und zee Edd Noo Recurd leenk.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="70" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.11 Show zip before city</string>
		<translation>2.11 Shoo zeep beffure-a ceety</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="71" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>In Europe the postal code (zip in USA) is shown before the city. 
          This option is off by default.</string>
		<translation>In Ioorupe-a zee pustel cude-a (zeep in USA) is shoon beffure-a zee ceety. Thees oopshun is ooffff by deffoolt. Um de hur de hur de hur.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="73" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>2.12 Records viewed per page</string>
		<translation>2.12 Recurds feeooed per pege</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="74" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Pick your number between 1 and ??</string>
		<translation>Peeck yuoor noomber betveee 1 und ??</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="75" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>3.1 Custom tab</string>
		<translation>3.1 Coostum teb</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="81" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Name of the Custom Fields tab and the 
          headline for custom fields in the detail page. Leave it blank, if you 
          do not use custom fields.</string>
		<translation>Neme-a ooff zee Coostum Feeelds teb und zee heedleene-a fur coostum feeelds in zee deteeel pege-a. Leefe-a it blunk, iff yuoo du nut use-a coostum feeelds. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="84" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>3.2 Width of TEXTAREA fields</string>
		<translation>3.2 Veedt ooff TEXTEREA feeelds</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="85" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>TEXTAREA field width can change depending on 
          the CSS of your theme. Sometimes this results in a very bad layout of 
          your form. You can set the html COLS of a TEXTAREA field. Valid size ranges from 4 to 100.</string>
		<translation>TEXTEREA feeeld veedt cun chunge-a dependeeng oon zee CSS ooff yuoor zeeme-a. Sumeteemes thees resoolts in a fery bed leyuoot ooff yuoor furm. Yuoo cun set zee html COLS ooff a TEXTEREA feeeld. Bork bork bork! Feleed seeze-a runges frum 4 tu 100.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="88" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>3.3 Format for date entries</string>
		<translation>3.3 Furmet fur dete-a intreees</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="89" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Select the format for date entry and 
          display. Only two options at this time, MM.DD.YYYY and DD.MM.YYYY.</string>
		<translation>Select zee furmet fur dete-a intry und deespley. Bork bork bork! Oonly tvu oopshuns et thees teeme-a, MM.DD.YYYY und DD.MM.YYYY.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="91" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>3.4 Format for numeric values</string>
		<translation>3.4 Furmet fur noomereec felooes</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="92" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Select the format for numeric entry and 
          display. Only two options at this time, 9,999.00 and 9.999,00</string>
		<translation>Select zee furmet fur noomereec intry und deespley. Bork bork bork! Oonly tvu oopshuns et thees teeme-a, 9,999.00 und 9.999,00</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="94" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>4.1 Send error reports to Site Admin</string>
		<translation>4.1 Send irrur repurts tu Seete-a Edmeen</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="100" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This option enables error messages to be emailed directly to
          the site administrator email account. Uncheck to disable this feature.</string>
		<translation>Thees oopshun inebles irrur messeges tu be-a imeeeled durectly tu zee seete-a edmeenistretur imeeel eccuoont. Um de hur de hur de hur. Uncheck tu deeseble-a thees feetoore-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="102" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>4.2 Alternate Site Admin email address</string>
		<translation>4.2 Elternete-a Seete-a Edmeen imeeel eddress</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="103" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Choose an alternate email address if the official Site Admin
          does not wish to receive AddressBook error notifications.</string>
		<translation>Chuuse-a un elternete-a imeeel eddress iff zee ooffffeeciel Seete-a Edmeen dues nut veesh tu receeefe-a EddressBuuk irrur nuteefficeshuns.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="105" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>4.3 Send error reports to AddressBook Quality Control</string>
		<translation>4.3 Send irrur repurts tu EddressBuuk Qooeleety Cuntrul</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="106" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>This option sends an email directly to the AddressBook development
          team with the error message, date and time of occurrence, and the fully qualified host name of the
          server running the AddressBook module. NO OTHER INFORMATION IS SENT. This information is used solely for 
          the purpose of fixing issues encountered in the AddressBook module. Uncheck to disable this feature.</string>
		<translation>Thees oopshun sends un imeeel durectly tu zee EddressBuuk defelupment teem veet zee irrur messege-a, dete-a und teeme-a ooff ooccoorrence-a, und zee foolly qooeleeffied hust neme-a ooff zee serfer roonneeng zee EddressBuuk mudoole-a. NO OoTHER INFORMETION IS SENT. Thees inffurmeshun is used sulely fur zee poorpuse-a ooff feexing issooes incuoontered in zee EddressBuuk mudoole-a. Uncheck tu deeseble-a thees feetoore-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/addressbook/xartemplates/admin-displaydocs.xd" line="110" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
