<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authldap/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authldap/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The AuthLDAP module allows you to authenticate a user with an LDAP server.  The AuthLDAP module forwards the username and password from the login screen to the LDAP server for authentication.</string>
		<translation>Zee OothLDEP mudoole-a elloos yuoo tu oozeenteecete-a a user veet un LDEP serfer. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! Zee OothLDEP mudoole-a furverds zee userneme-a und pessvurd frum zee lugeen screee tu zee LDEP serfer fur oozeenteeceshun.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authldap/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authldap/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="21" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Authentication by AuthLDAP is automatically set once the the AuthLDAP module has been initialized.   You must configure XarLDAP before a user will be able to login to Xaraya.  To remove AuthLDAP authentication, you must remove the module.</string>
		<translation>Oozeenteeceshun by OothLDEP is ootumeteecelly set oonce-a zee zee OothLDEP mudoole-a hes beee ineetielized. Bork bork bork! Yuoo moost cunffeegoore-a XerLDEP beffure-a a user veell be-a eble-a tu lugeen tu Xereya. Tu remufe-a OothLDEP oozeenteeceshun, yuoo moost remufe-a zee mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authldap/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have one choice.  &quot;Modify Config&quot;.</string>
		<translation>Frum zee menoo, yuoo hefe-a oone-a chueece-a. &quot;Mudeeffy Cunffeeg&quot;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authldap/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Config -- From here, you can allow a user that has account information in LDAP to be automatically added to the Xaraya database and allowed to login.</string>
		<translation>Mudeeffy Cunffeeg -- Frum here-a, yuoo cun elloo a user thet hes eccuoont inffurmeshun in LDEP tu be-a ootumeteecelly edded tu zee Xereya detebese-a und ellooed tu lugeen. Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authldap/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="31" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authldap/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There are no included blocks with the AuthLDAP Module</string>
		<translation>Zeere-a ere-a nu inclooded blucks veet zee OothLDEP Mudoole</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/authldap/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="40" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
