<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="nl_NL.utf-8">
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Wat is dit?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Categories is a Xaraya Utility Module.</string><translation>Categorieën is een Xaraya hulmodule.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>It is currently responsible for accomplishing these tasks:</string><translation>De module is verantwoordelijk voor het afhandelijk van de volgende taken:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Allows the use of site wide categories for content modules to use as needed.</string><translation>Programmabrede categorisering voor content modules</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Hoe te gebruiken?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>From the menu, you have two choices. 'Add a New Category', and 'View Categories'.</string><translation>Vanuit het menu heeft u 2 keuzes. 'Toevoegen van een nieuwe categorie' en het bekijken van bestaande categorieën</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Add a new category -- Allows you to add a new category to your site categories tree.</string><translation>Toevoegen van een nieuwe categorie -- Voeg een nieuwe, programmabrede, categorie toe aan aan de categorie boomstructuur.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>View Categories -- This area allows you to view the entire categorization tree, allowing a easy way to modify it.</string><translation>Toon categorieën - Deze keuze toont een scherm met een overzicht van de complete categorie boomstructuur en een eenvoudige manier om wijzigingen door te voeren.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Bijgevoegde blokken</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Navigation block allows navigation of any module using the category hooks.</string><translation>Het navigatieblok toont een automatische navigatie voor modules de de categorie hooks gebruiken.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Bijgevoegde hooks</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Categories provides all the hooks necessary to allow categories to be available within other modules.</string><translation>De categorieën module verzorgt alle noodzakelijke hooks om categorieën aan ander modules te kunnen aanbieden</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Extended information about this module can be found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Categories Module - Xaraya Extension 147</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on Categories found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on Categories</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Categories module - Overview</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
