<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="fr_FR.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Introduction</string>
		<translation>Introduction</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our
web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as &quot;Data&quot; below)
that may be collected by us on our site. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own
or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control.</string>
		<translation>Nous prenons très au sérieux votre droit à la Vie Privée et voulons que vous vous sentiez à l'aise lors de l'utilisation de notre site. Cette Charte de Vie Privée concerne les informations d'identification personnelle (appellées &quot;Données&quot; ci-dessous) qui pourraient être collectées sur notre site. Cette Charte ne s'applique pas aux entités que nous ne possédons ou ne contrôlons pas, ou aux personnes qui ne seraient pas nos employés, nos agents, ou sous notre contrôle.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="41" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Please take time to read our &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;Terms of Use&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Veuillez prendre le temps de lire nos &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;Conditions d'Utilisation&lt;/a&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="46" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Collection of Data</string>
		<translation>Récupération de Données</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="55" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Our registration process requires only a valid e-mail address and a unique user ID and
password. Providing us with other information is at your option. Please take note that
your user name, e-mail address, or other submissions that you make on this site may contain
your real name or other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear on
this site. Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that
is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie information. Information
about how advertising may be served on this site (if at all) is set forth below.</string>
		<translation>Notre processus d'inscription requiert seulement une adresse email valide, un pseudo unique et un mot de passe. Vous pouvez aussi choisir de nous fournir d'autres informations. Veuillez noter que votre nom d'utilisateur, votre adresse email, ou toute autre information que vous pourrez fournir sur ce site, peut contenir des informations personnelles, et apparaître sur ce site. Comme beaucoup de sites web, nous pourrions aussi recevoir automatiquement des informations générales de nos fichiers de journalisation (adresses IP, informations des cookies...).
Des informations expliquant comment de la publicité peut être proposée sur ce site (si elle peut) sont données ci-dessous.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Use of Data</string>
		<translation>Utilisation des Données</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="69" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>We may use Data to customize and improve your user experience on this site.
We will make efforts so that your Data will not be provided to third parties unless (i)
provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when
you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our
site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an
Application Service Provider; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (v) we find
that your use of this site violates our this Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines
or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property; (vi) or (vi)
this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the Data
in the same manner as we can as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links
that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies
that appear on those sites.</string>
		<translation>Il se peut que nous utilisions les Données pour affiner le comportement du site. Nous ferons des efforts pour que vos données ne parviennent pas à des tierces parties sauf si (i) elles sont fournies d'une façon autre que répertoriée dans la Charte de Vie Privée; (ii) nous obtenons votre consentement, comme par exemple lorsque vous choisissez de &quot;opt-in&quot; ou de &quot;opt-out&quot; le partage des Données; (iii) un service fourni par notre site requiert l'interaction avec une tierce partie ou est fourni par une tierce partie, by way of example an Application Service Provider; (iv) pour des raisons de collaboration avec la justice ou application de la loi; (v) nous considérons que l'utilisation que vous faites de ce site est contraire à cette Charte, aux Conditions d'Utilisation, aux règles d'usages ou considérée néfaste à nos droits et/ou notre propriété; (vi) ce site est acquis par une tierce partie, tant que cette tierce partie pourra utiliser les Données de la même façon que nous le faisons comme précisé dans cette Charte. Dans l'éventualité où vous choisissez d'utiliser les liens qui apparaissent sur notre site pour visiter d'autres sites, vous êtes invité à lire les Chartes sur la Vie Privée qui apparaisent sur ces sites.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="83" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Cookies</string>
		<translation>Cookies</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="87" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience,
such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so,
may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties
providing the advertisement. However, the companies serving the advertising do not have access to
our cookies. These companies usually use non-personally identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain
information about your visits to our site.</string>
		<translation>Comme beaucoup de sites web, nous utilisons les cookies pour améliorer la qualité de nos services vis à vis de nos utilisateurs, comme par exemple retenir leurs paramètres. De la publicité peut apparaître sur notre site et, le cas échéant, il se pourrait que des cookies soient déposés et lus sur votre ordinateur. Ce procédé est soumis à la Charte de Vie Privée des parties fournissant la publicité. Cependant, ces compagnies faisant leur publicité n'ont pas accés à nos cookies. Ces compagnies utilisent habituellement des codes ne pouvant identifier les personnes ou des codes anonymes pour obtenir des informations sur les visites sur notre site.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="94" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt; to find out more information about
your options including from the following companies that may serve advertising on our site:</string>
		<translation>Vous pouvez cliquer &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;ici&lt;/a&gt; pour avoir de plus amples informations sur vos options, y compris celles provenant des compagnies qui pourraient faire de la publicité sur notre site :</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="102" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>AffiliateShop</string>
		<translation>AffiliateShop</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="107" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>AssociatePrograms.com</string>
		<translation>AssociatePrograms.com</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="108" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Be Free</string>
		<translation>Be Free</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="109" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Click Trade</string>
		<translation>Click Trade</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="110" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Commission Junction</string>
		<translation>Commission Junction</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="111" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>DoubleClick</string>
		<translation>DoubleClick</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="112" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Linkshare</string>
		<translation>Linkshare</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="113" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Children</string>
		<translation>Enfants</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="117" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>We do not allow persons who are aged #(1) (#(2)) or younger to become members of this site.</string>
		<translation>Nous n'autorisons pas les personnes âgées de #(1) (#(2)) ou moins à être membres de ce site.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="119" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>For more information, please contact &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(1)&quot;&gt;our webmaster&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Pour de plus amples informations, veuillez contacter &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(1)&quot;&gt;notre webmaster&lt;/a&gt;</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="125" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Editing or Deleting Your Account Information</string>
		<translation>Modifier ou Effacer vos Informations</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="133" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>We provide you with the ability to edit the information in your user account information
that you provided to us in registration by using &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;your personal page configuration area&lt;/a&gt;.
You may request deletion of your user account by contacting &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(2)&quot;&gt;our webmaster&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Vous avez la possibilité de modifier les informations vous concernant (que vous nous avez fournies lors de votre inscription) sur votre &lt;a href=&quot;#(1)&quot;&gt;zone de configuration de page personnelle&lt;/a&gt;. Vous pouvez demander la suppression de votre compte en contactant &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(2)&quot;&gt;notre webmaster&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="139" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that is not contained within your
user account, such as posts that may appear within our forums, may continue to remain on our site at our
discretion even though your user account is deleted.</string>
		<translation>Les informations que vous auriez pu nous fournir qui ne seraient pas comprises dans votre compte, comme les messages dans nos forums, pourraient rester sur notre site selon notre bon vouloir, même si votre compte est supprimé.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="148" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Changes to this Privacy Policy</string>
		<translation>Changements de cette Charte de Vie Privée</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="152" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial
changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message
to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.</string>
		<translation>Nous pourrons changer quelques éléments de cette Charte de temps en temps. Nous vous informerons des changements importants soit en publiant une annonce sur notre site, soit en vous envoyant un email à l'adresse que vous nous avez fournie.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="156" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>NO GUARANTEES</string>
		<translation>AUCUNE GARANTIE</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="161" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make
efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond
our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or
representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.</string>
		<translation>Tant que cette Charte établit nos standards pour l'entretien de nos Données, et tant que nous continuons à fournir les efforts pour les respecter, nous ne sommes pas en position de garantir ces standards. Il se peut que certains facteurs indépendants de notre volonté nuisent à l'intégrité des Données. En conséqence, nous déclinons toute responsabilité concernant l'intégrité des Données.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="166" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Contact Information</string>
		<translation>Nous Contacter</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="171" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free
to contact &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(1)&quot;&gt;our Webmaster&lt;/a&gt;.</string>
		<translation>Si vous avez la moindre question à propos de cette Charte de Vie Privée ou à propos de ce site, n'hésitez pas à contacter &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:#(1)&quot;&gt;notre webmaster&lt;/a&gt;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="176" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Privacy Policy Not Active</string>
		<translation>Charte de Vie Privée Non Active</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/registration/xartemplates/user-privacy.xd" line="182" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
