<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xslt/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="2" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xslt/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="7" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The XSLT module is a utility module that allows you to do XSL transformations via transform hooks.</string>
		<translation>Zee XSLT mudoole-a is a uteelity mudoole-a thet elloos yuoo tu du XSL trunsffurmeshuns feea trunsffurm huuks. Um gesh dee bork, bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xslt/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="10" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xslt/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="15" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>For each hooked module, specify the XSL file to be used in the transformation. This file should be located on the server, somewhere below the document root. Any DTD referenced by the original XML should also be available.

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In order to test this with articles, you should remove the call to xarVarPrepHTMLDisplay() on line 292 of modules/articles/xaruser/display.php (test only !), otherwise all XML tags in your content will be escaped before it gets passed to the transform hook...

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Note : this is a work in progress :)</string>
		<translation>Fur iech huuked mudoole-a, speceeffy zee XSL feele-a tu be-a used in zee trunsffurmeshun. Thees feele-a shuoold be-a luceted oon zee serfer, sumoohere-a beloo zee ducooment ruut. Um de hur de hur de hur. Uny DTD refferenced by zee ooreeginel XML shuoold elsu be-a efeeeleble-a. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In oorder tu test thees veet erteecles, yuoo shuoold remufe-a zee cell tu xarVarPrepHTMLDisplay() oon leene-a 292 ooff modules/articles/xaruser/display.php (test oonly !), oozeerveese-a ell XML tegs in yuoor cuntent veell be-a isceped beffure-a it gets pessed tu zee trunsffurm huuk... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nute-a : thees is a vurk in prugress :)</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xslt/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
