<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xlink/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="2" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xlink/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="7" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The XLink module is a utility module that allows you to establish relationships between module items and some independent identifier, e.g. for shortcut URLs or foreign key look-ups with external databases. Enable its hooks for any module where you want to use it...</string>
		<translation>Zee XLeenk mudoole-a is a uteelity mudoole-a thet elloos yuoo tu istebleesh releshunsheeps betveee mudoole-a items und sume-a independent identeeffier, i.g. fur shurtcoot URLs oor fureeegn key luuk-ups veet ixternel detebeses. Ineble-a its huuks fur uny mudoole-a vhere-a yuoo vunt tu use-a it. Um de hur de hur de hur...</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xlink/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="10" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xlink/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="15" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The independent identifier can be composed of a base name (optional) and an identifier. Examples : 200309121551.xyz, kbase 123, products &quot;This Nice Product&quot;, ...
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
For each hooked module, specify the acceptable base names for the items you want to reference.
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
When you declare a base name as alias for short URLs, you can use index.php/kbase/123 instead of index.php/xlink/kbase/123</string>
		<translation>Zee independent identeeffier cun be-a cumpused ooff a bese-a neme-a (oopshunel) und un identeeffier. Hurty flurty schnipp schnipp! Ixemples : 200309121551.xyz, kbese-a 123, prudoocts &quot;Thees Neece-a Prudooct&quot;, ... &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Fur iech huuked mudoole-a, speceeffy zee eccepteble-a bese-a nemes fur zee items yuoo vunt tu refference-a. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt; Vhee yuoo declere-a a bese-a neme-a es eleees fur shurt URLs, yuoo cun use-a index.php/kbese-a/123 insteed ooff index.php/xleenk/kbese-a/123</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xlink/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="24" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
