<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="en_BORK.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Overview</string>
		<translation>Oferfeeoo</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="4" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Vhet is it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="14" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Themes Module controls the display of your website.  Certain display variables are set from this module to allow you to control the site name, footer information, etc.</string>
		<translation>Zee Zeemes Mudoole-a cuntruls zee deespley ooff yuoor vebseete-a.  Certeeen deespley fereeebles ere-a set frum thees mudoole-a tu elloo yuoo tu cuntrul zee seete-a neme-a, fuuter inffurmeshun, itc.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="17" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Hoo tu use-a it?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>From the menu, you have three choices.  &quot;View&quot;, &quot;Modify Config&quot;, and &quot;Template Tags&quot;.</string>
		<translation>Frum zee menoo, yuoo hefe-a three-a chueeces.  Um gesh dee bork, bork!  &quot;Feeoo&quot;, &quot;Mudeeffy Cunffeeg&quot;, und &quot;Templete-a Tegs&quot;.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>View -- Allows you to see what themes are currently installed on your system, and the current state that they are in.</string>
		<translation>Feeoo -- Elloos yuoo tu see-a vhet zeemes ere-a coorrently instelled oon yuoor system, und zee coorrent stete-a thet zeey ere-a in.  Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="27" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Configuration -- Allows you to set certain display configuration values.</string>
		<translation>Mudeeffy Cunffeegooreshun -- Elloos yuoo tu set certeeen deespley cunffeegooreshun felooes.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="28" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Template tags -- Allows you view / edit / delete template tags on the system, as well as add new tags to functions.</string>
		<translation>Templete-a tegs -- Elloos yuoo feeoo / ideet / delete-a templete-a tegs oon zee system, es vell es edd noo tegs tu fooncshuns.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="29" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Blucks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Metablock</string>
		<translation>Metebluck</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The meta block allows you to configure at one time the meta values for your site.  This template can be overridden from your theme directory.</string>
		<translation>Zee meta bluck elloos yuoo tu cunffeegoore-a et oone-a teeme-a zee meta felooes fur yuoor seete-a.  Thees templete-a cun be-a ooferreeddee frum yuoor zeeme-a durectury.  Bork bork bork!</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="38" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Inclooded Huuks</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>The Themes module has a user menu hook which allows the users of your Xaraya site to change the default theme to their choosing.  This can be activated and deactivated from the modules module.</string>
		<translation>Zee Zeemes mudoole-a hes a user menoo huuk vheech elloos zee users ooff yuoor Xereya seete-a tu chunge-a zee deffoolt zeeme-a tu zeeur chuuseeng.  Thees cun be-a ecteefeted und deecteefeted frum zee mudooles mudoole-a.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="45" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Extended information about this module can be found here. [modules module]</string>
		<translation>Extended inffurmeshun ebuoot thees mudoole-a cun be-a fuoond here-a. [mudooles mudoole-a]</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/themes/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="48" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
