<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="hu_HU.utf-8">
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Mi ez?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Netquery module includes multidomain and IP/AS whois, DNS queries,
email address validation, port services lookup, HTTP requests, ping, traceroute and
looking glass router interrogation functions. Availability of each query type, local
and remote execution, and all entries in the whois, port services and looking glass
data tables are configurable.</string><translation>A Netquery modul IP/AS WHOIS lekérdezését, DNS lekérdezését, e-mail címek ellenőrzését, kapu szolgáltatások lekérdezését, HTTP lekéréseket, pingelést, útvonalkeresést és Looking Glass útválasztó szolgáltatások használatát biztosítja. Az egyes lekérdezési típusok, a helyi és távoli programok használata, a WHOIS elemek, a kapu szolgáltatások és a Looking Glass adattáblák mind konfigurálhatóak.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>How to use it?</string><translation>Hogyan kell használni?</translation></entry>
<entry><string>From Netquery's main administration menu, you have six choices:</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>: From this
menu option, you can select which Netquery functions will be available to users of
your site, configure local and remote excution and set defaults.</string><translation>: Beállítható, hogy mely Netquery szolgáltatások legyenek elérhetőek a weboldal felhasználói számára, a helyi és távoli futtatások valamint az egyes alapértelmezett értékek.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>: From this
menu option, you can edit, add or delete whois "lookup links" between top level domain
(TLD) entries and whois servers.</string><translation>: Megadhatóak az egyes legfelsőbb szintű domain nevekhez (TLD) tartozó WHOIS keresési hivatkozások és WHOIS kiszolgálók.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>: From this
menu option, you can edit, add or delete port services data entries, including
keyword comments on vulnerabilities displayed to port lookup users.</string><translation>Beállíthatjuk a kapuk szolgáltatásait, kulcsszavakat adhatunk meg az egyes sebezhetőségekhez a kaput ellenőrző felhasználók számára.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>: From this
menu option, you can edit, add or delete the flagging data used for services and
exploits, including keywords, font colors and search lookup URLs.</string><translation>Megadhatóak az egyes kapcsoló adatok a szolgáltatásokhoz és kihasználhatóságokhoz, beleértve a kulcszsavakat, betűszíneket és keresési hivatkozásokat.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>: From this
menu option, you can edit, add or delete "looking glass" router entries overriding
default settings and passwords for individual IPv4 and IPv6 daemons.</string><translation>Beállíthatjuk a Looking Glass szolgáltatásokat, felülírva az alepértelmezett értékeket és jelszavakat az IPv4 és IPv6 kiszolgálókhoz.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>: From this
menu option, you can examine or delete entries in the log that is maintained by
Netquery's access monitor and spambot blocker.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation>Kapcsolódó blokkok</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation>Kapcsolódó hurkok</translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no included hooks with this module.</string><translation>Nincsenek kapcsolódó hurkok.</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation>További információk</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the Netquery module can be found in the</string><translation>További információk a modulról:</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Netquery Module Overview</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Version</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
