<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="fr_FR.utf-8">
<entry><string>The blocks system has undergone an important rewrite in this version. Blocks now have their access rules (security checks) integrated in the block itself, giving the site administrator finer control over access rules and an easier user interface to configure them. Similarly, caching can now be¨controlled through a user interface specific to each block.</string><translation>Le système des blocs a subit un remplacement important dans cette version. Les blocs ont maintenant leurs règles d'accès (vérifications de sécurité) intégrés dans le bloc lui-même, donnant à l'administrateur du site un contrôle accru des règles d'accès et une interface d'utilisateur plus facile pour les configurer. Similièrement , l'attrapage peut maintenant être contrôlé à travers une interface d'utilisateur spécifique à chaque bloc.</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/installer/xartemplates/includes/notes-210.xt" line="8"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>Block groups are now &quot;proper&quot; blocks. Although they have no content (at present), they can have their own access rules, making it possible to display (or not) entire groups of blocks to specific users.</string><translation>Les groupes de bloc sont maintenant des blocs ''propres''. Même s'ils n'ont pas de contenu (à présent), ils peuvent avoir leurs propres règles d'accès, le rendant possible d'afficher (ou pas) les groupes de blocs entiers aux utilisateurs spécifiques.</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/installer/xartemplates/includes/notes-210.xt" line="12"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>A number of block types have been merged. The content block type now replaces the old text, html, php and finclude block types.</string><translation>Un nombre de types de bloc qui ont été fusionnés. Le type de bloc de contenu remplace le vieux texte, html, php, et inclu les types de bloc</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/installer/xartemplates/includes/notes-210.xt" line="16"/>
		</references>
</entry>
</translations>
