<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="de_DE.utf-8">
<entry><string>The blocks system has undergone an important rewrite in this version. Blocks now have their access rules (security checks) integrated in the block itself, giving the site administrator finer control over access rules and an easier user interface to configure them. Similarly, caching can now be¨controlled through a user interface specific to each block.</string><translation>Das Blocksystem hat eine wichtige Neuschreibung erfahren in dieser Version. Blöcke haben jetzt eine Zugangsberechtigung (Sicherheitsanfrage)im Block selbst integriert, die dem Administrator der Seite genauere Kontrolle über die Zugangsrechte ermöglichst und ein einfacheres Interface bereitstellt. Ebenfalls, kann Caching jetzt durch ein Benutzerinterface im jeweiligen Block kontrolliert werden.</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/installer/xartemplates/includes/notes-210.xt" line="8"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>Block groups are now &quot;proper&quot; blocks. Although they have no content (at present), they can have their own access rules, making it possible to display (or not) entire groups of blocks to specific users.</string><translation>Blockgruppen sind nun &quot;vollständige&quot; Blöcke. Obwohl sie (im MOment) keinen Inhalt haben, können sie ihre eigenen  Zugangsberechtigungen haben. Das macht es möglich (falls gewünscht) speziellen Benutzern ganze Gruppen von Blöcken anzuzeigen.</translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/installer/xartemplates/includes/notes-210.xt" line="12"/>
		</references>
</entry>
<entry><string>A number of block types have been merged. The content block type now replaces the old text, html, php and finclude block types.</string><translation>Eine Anzahl von Block-Typen wurde zusammengelegt. Der Inhalts-Block-Typ..... ersetzten die alten Text-, Html, PHP und Finclude-Block-Typen. </translation>		<references>
			<reference file="code/modules/installer/xartemplates/includes/notes-210.xt" line="16"/>
		</references>
</entry>
</translations>
