<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="pl_PL.utf-8">
	<entry>
		<string>Administration - xarBB</string>
		<translation>Administracja xarBB</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="3" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>What is it?</string>
		<translation>Co to jest?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="11" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>xarBB provides basic forum functions provided mainly from Xaraya utility modules (topics are provided by xarBB and reply posts by the comments module, for example). The forum itself is very light weight, but designed to handle large volume postings.</string>
		<translation>xarBB posiada standardowe funkcje forum i jest wpełni zintegrowane ze środowiskiem Xaraya (można np. użyć forum jako system komentarzy). Forum te jest lekkie, ale przeznaczone dla dużej ilości postów.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="13" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>How to use it?</string>
		<translation>Jak używać xarBB?</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="16" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>xarBB allows users to post Topics and reply posts to those topics. There are a number of options available from the administration menu.</string>
		<translation>xarBB pozwala użytkownikom na pisanie tematów oraz odpowiadania w nich. Znajdziesz tutaj listę opcji dostępnych w panelu administracyjnym.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="20" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Add Forums -- Allows you to add new forums to your system. Each forum has a number of configuration options.</string>
		<translation>Dodaj forum - pozwala dodać forum (dział) w Twoim xarBB. Każde forum można dodatkowo konfigurować.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="23" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>View Forums -- Allows you to view the forums that you have configured on your system.</string>
		<translation>Zobacz fora - pozwala zobaczyć wszystkie fora w xarBB.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="24" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Modify Configuration -- Allows you to set certain master configuration routines for forums.</string>
		<translation>Edytuj konfigurację - pozwala na edycję głównych ustawień xarBB.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="25" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Reorder Forums -- Allows you to reorder your existing forums</string>
		<translation>Sortuj fora - pozwala na dowolne sortowanie forów.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="26" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can add additional functionality to xarBB forums as you require it.</string>
		<translation>Jeżeli potrzebujesz dodatkowych funkcji, możesz je bez problemu dodać jako wtyczki do xarBB.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="30" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Hook BBCode or HTML to allow formatted user input and also the option to supply linebreaks for plain text.</string>
		<translation>Wtyczka BBCode lub HTML pozwala na formatowanie wiadomości przez użytkowników.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="33" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Turn off modify 'stamps' in topics and posts and hook Changelog module to allow enhanced changelog management of posts and topics</string>
		<translation>Wyłącz możliwość dodawania obrazków do postów oraz dodaj wtyczkę &quot;Changelog&quot;, która umożliwia dodawanie listy modyfikacji do postów i tematów.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="34" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>If you have imported the extra default User dynamic data such as avatars, msn, irc and so on, to your user roles, then these attributes will automatically be displayed in xarbb topics and posts.</string>
		<translation>Jeżeli w profilu użytkownika można ustawić avatar, numery komunikatorów, sygnaturkę itp., możesz przyporządkować te właściwości do użytkowników na xarBB.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="35" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Set privilges for Comments module and xarBB to allow or disallow viewing, posting of topics and replies, editing of their own posts by users, and setup of moderator groups.</string>
		<translation>Ustawienia przywileji dla komentarzy oraz forum (zezwalanie na przeglądanie, postowanie, edycję postów użytkownika oraz ustawienia grupy moderatorów).</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="36" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Administrators and moderators have additional functionality including deleting posts, marking posts as announcements or sticky topics, moving posts, and locking topics from further postings.</string>
		<translation>Administratorzy i moderatorzy mogą wpełni usuwać posty, zmieniać statusy postów na &quot;Ogłoszenie&quot; lub &quot;Przyklejony&quot;, przenosić posty i temat oraz zamykać tematy.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="39" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>You can build the functionality you would like into xarBB and use override templates to customize every aspect of the xarBB templates.</string>
		<translation>Możesz dowolnie rozbudowywać xarBB oraz używać innych szablonów do kustomizacji forum.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="42" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Blocks</string>
		<translation>Bloki</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="44" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There is currently one block provided called Latest Posts. If the block is not
showing as an option when adding a Block instance it may not have been registered. In this case
please add the block type through Admin Blocks-Add Block Type</string>
		<translation>Obecnie znajduje się tutaj tylko jeden blok pokazujący ostatnie posty. Jeżeli blok ten nie pokazuje się na stronie, przy dodawaniu nowego bloku ustaw instancję na niezarejestrowaną. W tym celu dodaj blok: Panel administracyjny -&gt; Bloki -&gt; Dodaj blok.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="48" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Included Hooks</string>
		<translation>Zawarte wtyczki</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="51" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>There is currently a Search hook. If you hook xarBB to the Search module, users will be able to search through topics and posts, and more specifically for topic and post authors.</string>
		<translation>Obecnie popięta wtyczka to moduł &quot;Szukaj&quot;. Dzięki tej wtyczce użytkownicy będą mogli przeszukiwać posty i tematy na xarBB.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="53" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Further Information</string>
		<translation>Dalsze informacje</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="56" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Further information on the XarBB module can be found at</string>
		<translation>Dalsze informacje, które będzie można znaleść na xarBB</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="59" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xarbb Extension page at</string>
		<translation>Dodatki xarBB</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="62" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>xarBB Module - Xaraya Extension 300</string>
		<translation>Moduł xarBB - Xaraya Extension 300</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="62" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string>
		<translation>Kliknij na zakładkę &quot;Historia wersji&quot; na dole, aby zobaczyć informacje o tej wersji xarBB.</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="63" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Related tutorials and documentation on XarBB found at</string>
		<translation>Poradniki i dokumentacja xarBB</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Related documentation on xarBB</string>
		<translation>Dokumentacja xarBB</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Xaraya Documentation.</string>
		<translation>Dokumentacja Xaraya</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="65" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>xarBB Module - Overview</string>
		<translation>Przegląd modułu xarBB</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="69" />
		</references>
	</entry>
	<entry>
		<string>Version</string>
		<translation>Wersja</translation>
		<references>
			<reference file="modules/xarbb/xartemplates/admin-main.xd" line="69" />
		</references>
	</entry>
</translations>
