<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<translations xmlns="http://xaraya.com/2002/ns/translations" locale="el_GR.utf-8">
<entry><string>What is it?</string><translation>Τι είναι;</translation></entry>
<entry><string>The Blogger API is a XML-RPC API used for blogging. The API is very simple and is
basically a way to exchange strings between xmlrpc clients and servers.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>In Xaraya the xmlrpcserver module is responsible for providing the xmlrpc transport
needed for the Blogger API functionality. This module will not function without
that module activated.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>In addition to that, the xmlrpcserver module needs one or more API modules
activated to actually do anything. The bloggerAPI is one such module. It is advised that the
xmlrpcsystemAPI module is also activated.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>You can find the specification of the Blogger API at</string><translation>Μπορείτε να βρείτε τις προδιαγραφές του API Blogger στην διεύθυνση</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Little survival guide for using Blogging tools with Xaraya</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Make sure you have enabled the following modules</string><translation>Επιβεβαιώστε ότι έχετε ενεργοποιήσει τα παρακάτω modules</translation></entry>
<entry><string>XmlRpcServer</string><translation>XmlRpcServer</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Categories</string><translation>Κατηγορίες</translation></entry>
<entry><string>Articles</string><translation>Άρθρα</translation></entry>
<entry><string>When these modules are activated, configure the categories modules and create some
categories which should hold the postings made from Blogs. While not necessary, it
is advised to create a publication type for blog postings specifically and link this
type to the category-tree you created for blog postings.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Go into the config section of the BloggerAPI module and configure the publication type
to use for blog postings. Select either News articles or your publication type which
you created.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Basically you're all set now to start blogging. Use your favorite tool for managing your
blog postings. For windows we recommend</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>and
for other operating systems</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>These two are the ones we test the API with and make sure that it at least works with those.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Point your blogging client to the url: http://www.yourxaraya.com/ws.php?type=xmlrpc and use
your Xaraya account for authentication. The rest should be self-explanatory.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Blocks</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no included blocks.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Included Hooks</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>There are no included hooks.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further Information</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Further information on the Bloggerapi module can be found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Bloggerapi Extension page at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Bloggerapi Module - Xaraya Extension 745</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Click on Version History tab at the bottom to get the latest release information.</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related tutorials and documentation on Bloggerapi found at</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Related documentation on Bloggerapi</string><translation></translation></entry>
<entry><string>Xaraya Documentation.</string><translation></translation></entry>
</translations>
